<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增相机水印可编辑功能，优化横屏场景悬浮球使用体验，屏幕录制支持三档分辨率可调节，新增系统声音录制开关和USB 连接用户身份认证功能，优化状态栏和收藏空间动效流畅性，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【状态栏】">
<feature>优化状态栏字体图标显示，增大字体字号，加粗图标样式，提高信息识别度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【图库】">
<feature>新增相机水印可编辑功能，可自行添加和还原水印，体验路径：拍照>打开照片>编辑>水印>水印选择：原图、文字水印、相框水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>优化横屏场景悬浮球使用体验，悬浮球停留位置避开前置摄像头区域，界面显示更美观。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统应用】">
<feature>新增录屏场景录制系统声音开关，视频或语音通话时，支持录制系统声音，录屏更完整，设置路径：设置>辅助功能>屏幕录制>录制系统声音。
新增录屏分辨率自定义功能，支持三挡可调节（480P/720P/1080P），随心选择对应的分辨率进行屏幕录制，录屏更清晰，设置路径：设置>辅助功能>屏幕录制>清晰度选择。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【收藏空间】">
<feature>优化收藏空间动效流畅性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增USB 连接用户身份认证功能，在选择“传输照片”或“传输文件 / Android Auto”时，需要进行身份认证，让您的数据传输更安全。
合入安卓2024年10月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update allows watermarks to be edited, and optimizes the user experience of assistive ball. Additionally, system sound can be recorded and three resolution levels are available for screen recordings. User authentication is required for USB connection. This release also optimizes the smoothness of motion effect in status bar and Favorites Space, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Increases the text size, and bolds the icons to make the information easier to recognize.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Watermarks can now be added and removed as desired. You can experience it by going to: Take a photo > Open the photo > Edit > Watermark > Watermark options: Original, Text watermark, Frame watermark.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Optimizes the user experience of assistive ball in landscape mode, ensuring the assistive ball stays away from the front camera, thereby offering a simpler interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System apps">
<feature>You can record system sound during video or voice calls as desired. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Screen recording > Record from system sound.
Three resolution levels (480P/720P/1080P) are available for video quality in screen recordings. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Screen recording > Video quality.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Optimizes the smoothness of the motion effect in Favorites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>User authentication is required for USB connection. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, ensuring safer data transfer.
Android security patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ ጌጥሽልሞች አርትዖት እንዲደረጉ ያስችላል እና የረዳት ኳሱን የተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮን ያተባል። በተጨማሪም፣ የስርዓት ድምጽ ሊቀዳ እና ለማያ ቀረጻዎች ሶስት የምስል ጥራት ደረጃዎች ይገኛሉ። ለUSB ግንኙነት የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። በተጨማሪም ይህ ልቀት በሁኔታ አሞሌ እና የተወዳጆች ቦታ ላይ የእንቅስቃሴ ተጽዕኖ ልስላሴን ያተባል፣ እንዲሁም የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል። ማዘመን ይመከራል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የሁኔታ አሞሌ">
<feature>መረጃውን ማወቅ ይበልጥ ለማቅለል የጽሑፍ መጠኑን ይጨምራል እና አዶዎቹን ያደምቃል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል">
<feature>ጌጥሽልሞች አሁን እንደተፈለገው ሊታከሉ እና ሊወገዱ ይችላሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ሊሞክሩት ይችላሉ፦ ፎቶ ያንሱ > ፎቶውን ይክፈቱ > አርትዕ > ጌጥሽልም > የጌጥሽልም አማራጮች፦ የመጀመሪያው፣ የጽሑፍ ጌጥሽልም፣ የክፈፍ ጌጥሽልም።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ብዙ-መስኮት">
<feature>በወርድ አቀማመጥ ላይ የረዳት ኳስ ተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮውን ያተባል፣ ይህ ረዳት ኳሱ ከፊት ካሜራው ርቆ እንደሚቆይ ያረጋግጣል፣ በዚህም የቀለለ በይነገጽ ያቀርባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የስርዓት መተግበሪያዎች">
<feature>በቪዲዮ ወይም ድምጽ ጥሪዎች ጊዜ እንደተፈለገው የስርዓት ድምጽን መቅዳት ይችላሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > የተደራሽነት ባህሪያት > የመስኮት ቅጂ > ከስርዓት ድምጽ ቅዳ።
በማያ ቀረጻዎች ውስጥ ለቪዲዮ ጥራት ሶስት የምስል ጥራት ደረጃዎች (480P/720P/1080P) ይገኛሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > የተደራሽነት ባህሪያት > የመስኮት ቅጂ > የቪዲዮ ጥራት።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የተወዳጆች ቦታ">
<feature>በተወዳጆች ቦታ ውስጥ የእንቅስቃሴ ተጽእኖ ልስላሴን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ለUSB ግንኙነት ያስፈልጋል። ፎቶዎችን አስተላልፍን ወይም ፋይሎችን አስተላልፍ / አንድሮይድ አውቶን ሲመርጡ የማረጋገጫ ወይም የደህንነት መጠየቂያ ይመጣል፣ ይህም ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ የውሂብ ማስተላለፍን ያረጋግጣል።
የአንድሮይድ ደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኦክቶበር 2024) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካትቷል። ስለHONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ ድር ጣቢያችንን https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يسمح هذا التحديث بتعديل العلامات المائية، ويحسّن تجربة المستخدم في استخدام الكرة المساعدة. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، يمكن تسجيل صوت النظام، وتتوفر ثلاثة مستويات من الدقة لتسجيلات الشاشة. يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم لاتصال USB. يحسّن هذا التحديث أيضًا سلاسة تأثير الحركة في شريط الحالة والمساحة المفضلة، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان. من المستحسن التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="شريط الحالة">
<feature>يزيد حجم النص ويطبق التنسيق الغامق على الأيقونات لتسهيل التعرف على المعلومات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المعرض">
<feature>يمكن الآن إضافة العلامات المائية وإزالتها كما تقتضي الحاجة. يمكنك تجربتها بالانتقال إلى: التقاط صورة > فتح الصورة > تعديل > علامة مائية > خيارات العلامة المائية: الأصلية، علامة مائية على هيئة نص، علامة مائية على هيئة إطار.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النوافذ المتعددة">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث تجربة المستخدم في استخدام الكرة المساعدة في الوضع الأفقي، مما يضمن بقاء الكرة المساعدة بعيدة عن الكاميرا الأمامية، وبالتالي تقديم واجهة أكثر بساطة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تطبيقات النظام">
<feature>يمكنك تسجيل صوت النظام أثناء مكالمات الفيديو أو المكالمات الصوتية، كما تقتضي الحاجة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > ميزات إمكانية الوصول > تسجيل الشاشة > التسجيل من صوت النظام.
تتوفر ثلاثة مستويات من الدقة (480P/720P/1080P) لجودة الفيديو في تسجيلات الشاشة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > ميزات إمكانية الوصول > تسجيل الشاشة > جودة الفيديو.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المساحة المفضلة">
<feature>يحسّن هذا الإصدار سلاسة تأثير الحركة في المساحة المفضلة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم لاتصال USB. تظهر مطالبة التحقق أو الأمان عندما تحدد "نقل الصور" أو "نقل الملفات/أندرويد أوتو"، مما يضمن نقل البيانات بشكل أكثر أمانًا.
تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أكتوبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কসমূহ সম্পাদনা কৰিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে আৰু সহায়ক বলৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতা অনুকূলন কৰে। ইয়াৰ উপৰিও, ছিষ্টেমৰ ধ্বনি ৰেকৰ্ড কৰিব পাৰি আৰু স্ক্ৰীণ ৰেকৰ্ডিঙৰ বাবে তিনিটা ৰিজলিউশ্বনৰ স্তৰ উপলব্ধ। USB সংযোগৰ বাবে ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। এই মুক্তিয়ে স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা আৰু প্ৰিয় স্থানত গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱৰ মসৃণতাও অনুকূলন কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। এইটো আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা">
<feature>তথ্য চিনাক্ত কৰিবলৈ সহজ বনাবলৈ পাঠৰ আকাৰ বঢ়ায় আৰু চিহ্নবোৰ ব'ল্ড কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গেলাৰী">
<feature>ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কসমূহ এতিয়া ইচ্ছা অনুসৰি যোগ কৰিব আৰু আঁতৰাব পাৰি। আপুনি ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা ল'ব পাৰে: এখন ফটো লওক > ফটো খোলক > সম্পাদনা কৰক > ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক > ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কৰ বিকল্পসমূহ: মূল, পাঠ ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক, ফ্ৰেম ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি-উইণ্ড'">
<feature>লেণ্ডস্কেপ মোডত সহায়ক বলৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতা অনুকূলন কৰে, যিয়ে সন্মুখ কেমেৰাৰ পৰা সহায়ক বল দূৰত ৰখাটো নিশ্চিত কৰে, যাৰ ফলত এক সহজ ইণ্টাৰফেচ প্ৰদান কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম এপ্প্‌সমূহ">
<feature>ইচ্ছা অনুসৰি ভিডিঅ' বা ভইচ কলৰ সময়ত আপুনি ছিষ্টেমৰ ধ্বনি ৰেকৰ্ড কৰিব পাৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > প্ৰৱেশযোগ্যতা ফিচাৰসমূহ > স্ক্ৰীণ ৰেকৰ্ডিং > ছিষ্টেমৰ ধ্বনিৰ পৰা ৰেকৰ্ড কৰক।
স্ক্ৰীণ ৰেকৰ্ডিংসমূহত ভিডিঅ'ৰ মানদণ্ডৰ বাবে তিনিটা ৰিজলিউশ্বনৰ স্তৰ (480 পিক্সেল/720 পিক্সেল/1080 পিক্সেল) উপলব্ধ। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > প্ৰৱেশযোগ্যতা ফিচাৰসমূহ > স্ক্ৰীণ ৰেকৰ্ডিং > ভিডিঅ'ৰ মানদণ্ড।</feature>
</features>
<features module="প্ৰিয় স্থান">
<feature>প্ৰিয় স্থানত গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱৰ মসৃণতা অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>USB সংযোগৰ বাবে ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। আপুনি ফটোসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক বা ফাইলসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক / Android Auto বাছনি কৰাৰ সময়ত এটা প্ৰমাণীকৰণ বা নিৰাপত্তাৰ সংকেত দেখা পায়, যিয়ে নিৰাপদ ডাটা স্থানান্তৰ নিশ্চিত কৰে।
ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (অক্টোবৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə su nişanlarının redaktə edilməsinə imkan verir və yardımçı topun istifadəçi təcrübəsini optimallaşdırır. Bundan əlavə, sistem səsi yazıla bilər və ekran qeydləri üçün üç ayırdetmə səviyyəsi əlçatandır. USB bağlantısı üçün istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Bu buraxılış həmçinin status panelində və Sevimlilər Yerində hərəkət effektinin hamarlığını optimallaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir. Yeniləmək tövsiyə olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status paneli">
<feature>Məlumatın daha asan tanınması üçün mətn ölçüsünü artırır və nişanları qalınlaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qalereya">
<feature>Su nişanları artıq istədiyiniz kimi əlavə edilə və silinə bilər. Aşağıdakı bölməyə keçərək təcrübədən keçirə bilərsiniz: Foto çəkin > Fotonu açın > Redaktə edin > Su nişanı > Su nişanı seçimləri: Orijinal, Mətn su nişanı, Çərçivə su nişanı.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İki Pəncərəli">
<feature>Mənzərə rejimində köməkçi topun istifadəçi təcrübəsini optimallaşdırır, köməkçi topun ön kameradan uzaq olmasını təmin edir və bununla da daha sadə interfeys təklif edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem proqramları">
<feature>İstədiyiniz kimi video və ya səsli zənglər zamanı sistem səsini qeydə ala bilərsiniz. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Xüsusi imkanlar xüsusiyyətləri > Ekran yazılması > Sistem səsindən qeydə alın.
Ekran qeydlərində video keyfiyyəti üçün üç ayırdetmə səviyyəsi (480P/720P/1080P) əlçatandır. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Xüsusi imkanlar xüsusiyyətləri > Ekran yazılması > Video keyfiyyəti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sevimlilər Yeri">
<feature>Sevimlilər Yerində hərəkət effektinin hamarlığını optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>USB bağlantısı üçün istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Verilənlərin daha təhlükəsiz ötürülməsini təmin edən Fotoları ötürün və ya Faylları ötürün / Android Auto seçdiyiniz zaman yoxlama və ya təhlükəsizlik sorğusu görünür.
Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (oktyabr 2024) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 veb-saytımıza daxil olun.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki mbisakake ngedit watermark, lan ngoptimalake pangalaman pangguna ing bal asistif. Saliyane iku, swara sistem bisa direkam lan telung tingkat resolusi sumadhiya kanggo rekaman layar. Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake kanggo sambungan USB. Rilis iki uga ngoptimalake lancare efek obahan ing garis status lan Enggon Favorit, sarta nggabungake patch keamanan. Sampeyan disaranake supaya nganyarake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Garis status">
<feature>Nambah ukuran teks lan ngandeli ikon supaya informasi bisa luwih gampang dikenali.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Watermark saiki bisa ditambahake lan dibusak miturut kekarepan sampeyan. Sampeyan bisa nggunakake fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Jupuk foto > Bukak foto > Edit > Watermark > Opsi watermark: Asli, Watermark teks, Watermark pigurah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Ngoptimalake pangalaman pangguna ing bal asistif ing mode lanskap, mesthekake bal asistif tetep adoh saka kamera ngarep, saengga antarmuka katon luwih prasaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apl sistem">
<feature>Sampeyan bisa ngrekam swara sistem sajrone nelpon video utawa nelpon swara kaya sing dikarepake. Cobanen kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Rekaman layar > Rekam saka swara sistem.
Telung tingkat resolusi (480P/720P/1080P) sumadhiya kanggo kwalitete video ing rekaman layar. Cobanen kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Rekaman layar > Kwalitete video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enggon Favorit">
<feature>Ngoptimalake lancare efek obahan ing Enggon Favorit.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake kanggo sambungan USB. Prentah verifikasi utawa keamanan bakal muncul yen sampeyan milih opsi Transfer foto utawa Transfer file/Android Auto, saengga njamin transfer data sing luwih aman.
Patch keamanan Android (Okt 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju vodeni žigovi mogu da se izmene i optimizuje se korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć. Osim toga, sistemski zvuk može da se snimi i dostupna su tri nivoa rezolucije za snimke ekrana. Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje glatkoću efekta kretanja na statusnoj traci i Prostoru za omiljeno i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Možete da iskusite tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć u režimu položeno, čime obezbeđuje da balončić za pomoć bude dalje od prednje kamere, i tako nudi jednostavan interfejs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemske aplikacije">
<feature>Možete da snimite sistemski zvuk tokom video ili audio poziva, prema želji. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Zapis sistemskog zvuka.
Tri nivoa rezolucije (480P/720P/1080P) su dostupna za kvalitet video zapisa u video snimcima ekrana. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Kvalitet video zapisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za omiljeno">
<feature>Optimizuje lakoću efekta kretanja u Prostoru za omiljeno.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni odziv se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) je uvršćena radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju vodeni žigovi mogu da se izmene i optimizuje se korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć. Osim toga, sistemski zvuk može da se snimi i dostupna su tri nivoa rezolucije za snimke ekrana. Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje glatkoću efekta kretanja na statusnoj traci i Prostoru za omiljeno i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Možete da iskusite tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć u režimu položeno, čime obezbeđuje da balončić za pomoć bude dalje od prednje kamere, i tako nudi jednostavan interfejs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemske aplikacije">
<feature>Možete da snimite sistemski zvuk tokom video ili audio poziva, prema želji. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Zapis sistemskog zvuka.
Tri nivoa rezolucije (480P/720P/1080P) su dostupna za kvalitet video zapisa u video snimcima ekrana. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Kvalitet video zapisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za omiljeno">
<feature>Optimizuje lakoću efekta kretanja u Prostoru za omiljeno.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni odziv se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) je uvršćena radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju vodeni žigovi mogu da se izmene i optimizuje se korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć. Osim toga, sistemski zvuk može da se snimi i dostupna su tri nivoa rezolucije za snimke ekrana. Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje glatkoću efekta kretanja na statusnoj traci i Prostoru za omiljeno i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Možete da iskusite tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo balončića za pomoć u režimu položeno, čime obezbeđuje da balončić za pomoć bude dalje od prednje kamere, i tako nudi jednostavan interfejs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemske aplikacije">
<feature>Možete da snimite sistemski zvuk tokom video ili audio poziva, prema želji. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Zapis sistemskog zvuka.
Tri nivoa rezolucije (480P/720P/1080P) su dostupna za kvalitet video zapisa u video snimcima ekrana. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Video snimak ekrana > Kvalitet video zapisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za omiljeno">
<feature>Optimizuje lakoću efekta kretanja u Prostoru za omiljeno.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika za povezivanje USB vezom. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni odziv se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) je uvršćena radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне дадае магчымасць рэдагаваць вадзяныя знакі і аптымізуе выкарыстанне дапаможнага шара. Таксама цяпер можна запісваць гук сістэмы, а для запісу экрана даступны тры ўзроўні раздзяляльнасці. Для падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. У гэтай версіі аптымізавана плаўнасць эфекту руху на панэлі стану і ў Прасторы абранага, а таксама ўключана выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Рэкамендуецца ўстанавіць гэта абнаўленне.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панэль стану">
<feature>Павялічаны памер тэксту, а значкі сталі больш выразнымі, што спрашчае ўспрыманне інфармацыі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерэя">
<feature>Цяпер вадзяныя знакі можна дадаваць і выдаляць па жаданні. Можаце паспрабаваць гэтыя функцыі, для гэтага прайдзіце ў меню «Зрабіць фота > Адкрыць фота > Рэдагаваць > Вадзяны знак > Тыпы вадзянога знака: арыгінал, тэкставы вадзяны знак, вадзяны знак-рамка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Многааконнасць">
<feature>Аптымізавана ўзаемадзеянне карыстальніка з дапаможным шарам у альбомнай арыентацыі: цяпер дапаможны шар не перашкаджае франтальнай камеры, дзякуючы чаму інтэрфейс стаў прасцей.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэмныя праграмы">
<feature>Пры неабходнасці вы можаце запісаць гук сістэмы падчас відэа- ці галасавых выклікаў. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Функцыі спецыяльных магчымасцей > Запіс экрана > Запісваць гук сістэмы».
Пры запісе экрана даступны тры ўзроўні раздзяляльнасці відэа (480P/720P/1080P). Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Функцыі спецыяльных магчымасцей > Запіс экрана > Якасць відэа».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Прастора абранага">
<feature>Аптымізавана плаўнасць эфекту руху ў Прасторы абранага.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Калі вы выбіраеце «Перадача фота» ці «Перадача файлаў / Android Auto», з’яўляецца запыт праверкі сапраўднасці або праверкі бяспекі, каб гарантаваць бяспечную перадачу даных.
Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (кастрычнік 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация позволява водните знаци да се редактират и оптимизира потребителския опит с помощната топка. Освен това може да се записва системен звук, а за записите на екрана са налични три нива на разделителна способност. За USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Тази версия също така оптимизира плавността на ефекта на движение в лентата за състоянието и в „Пространство за любими“ и включва корекция на сигурността. Препоръчва се да актуализирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Лента за състоянието">
<feature>Увеличава размера на текста и удебелява шрифта на иконите, за да направи информацията по-лесно разпознаваема.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерия">
<feature>Водните знаци вече могат да се добавят и премахват по желание. Можете да изпробвате това, като отидете на: „Направете снимка > Отворете снимката > Редактиране > Воден знак > Опции за воден знак: Без ефекти, текстови воден знак, рамка с воден знак“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Няколко прозореца">
<feature>Оптимизира потребителското изживяване с помощната топка в пейзажен режим, като гарантира, че тя остава далеч от предната камера, като по този начин се предлага по-опростен интерфейс.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Системни приложения">
<feature>По желание можете да записвате системния звук по време на видео или гласови повиквания. Изпробвайте това, като отидете на: „Настройки > Функции за достъпност > Запис на екрана > Запис от системен звук“.
За качеството на видеото при запис на екрана са налични три нива на разделителна способност (480 P/720 P/1080 P). Изпробвайте това, като отидете на: „Настройки > Функции за достъпност > Запис на екрана > Качество на видеото“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Пространство за любими">
<feature>Оптимизира плавността на ефекта на движение в „Пространство за любими“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>За USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителите. Когато изберете „Прехвърляне на снимки“ или „Прехвърляне на файлове/Android Auto“, се появява подкана за проверка на сигурността или защита, което осигурява по-безопасен трансфер на данни.
За защита на системата е включена корекция на сигурността на Android (октомври 2024 г.). За повече информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR, моля, посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি ওয়াটারমার্ক সম্পাদনা করতে দেয় এবং সহায়ক বলের ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতাকে অপটিমাইজ করে। এছাড়াও, সিস্টেম সাউন্ড রেকর্ড করা যায় এবং স্ক্রিন রেকর্ডিং-এর জন্য তিনটি রেজোলিউশন লেভেল পাওয়া যায়। USB সংযোগের জন্য ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। এই রিলিজটি স্ট্যাটাস বার এবং ফেভারিট স্পেসে মোশন এফেক্টের মসৃণতাকেও অপটিমাইজ করে এবং এতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। আপডেট করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="স্ট্যাটাস বার">
<feature>পাঠ্যের আকার বাড়ায়, এবং তথ্য শনাক্ত করাকে আরও সহজ করতে আইকনগুলিকে বোল্ড করে দেয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গ্যালারি">
<feature>এখন ইচ্ছামত ওয়াটারমার্ক যোগ করা এবং মুছে ফেলা যায়। আপনি এখানে গিয়ে এটির অভিজ্ঞতা অর্জন করতে পারেন: একটি ফটো তুলুন > ফটোটি খুলুন > সম্পাদনা করুন > ওয়াটারমার্ক > ওয়াটারমার্কের বিকল্প: মূল, টেক্সট ওয়াটারমার্ক, ফ্রেম ওয়াটারমার্ক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি উইন্ডো">
<feature>ল্যান্ডস্কেপ মোডে সহায়ক বলের ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতাকে অপটিমাইজ করে নিশ্চিত করে যে সহায়ক বলটি সামনের ক্যামেরা থেকে দূরে থাকে, এবং এইভাবে একটি আরও সহজ ইন্টারফেস অফার করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম অ্যাপ">
<feature>আপনি ভিডিও বা ভয়েস কলের সময় ইচ্ছামত সিস্টেম সাউন্ড রেকর্ড করতে পারেন। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > প্রবেশযোগ্যতার বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি > স্ক্রিন রেকর্ডিং > সিস্টেম সাউন্ড থেকে রেকর্ড করুন।
স্ক্রিন রেকর্ডিং-এ ভিডিওর গুণমানের জন্য তিনটি রেজোলিউশনের স্তর (480P/720P/1080P) পাওয়া যায়। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > প্রবেশযোগ্যতার বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি > স্ক্রিন রেকর্ডিং > ভিডিওর গুণমান।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ফেভারিট স্পেস">
<feature>ফেভারিট স্পেসে মোশন ইফেক্টের মসৃণতা অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>USB সংযোগের জন্য ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। আপনি যখন ফটো স্থানান্তর করুন বা ফাইল স্থানান্তর / Android Auto নির্বাচন করেন তখন একটি যাচাইকরণ বা নিরাপত্তা প্রম্পট দেখতে পাওয়া যায়, যা নিরাপদ ডেটা স্থানান্তর নিশ্চিত করে।
সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (অক্টোবর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་པར་ཆས་ཆུ་དཔར་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་ཆོག་པའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། འཕྲེད་བརྙན་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཀྱི་གཡེང་སྒྲོམ་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡོལ་ཐོག་བརྙན་འབེབས་ཀྱིས་རིམ་གསུམ་དབྱེ་འབྱེད་ཚད་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་སྒྲ་ཕབ་བཟོའི་བསད་སྤར་དང་ USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་དང་བསྡུ་ཉར་བར་སྟོང་གི་འགུལ་ཁྱད་གྱི་ཐོགས་ཐུག་མེད་པའི་རང་བཞིན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་།】">
<feature>རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་ཡིག་གཟུགས་མངོན་སྟོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡིག་གཟུགས་ཡིག་ཨང་ཇེ་ཆེར་བཏང་བ་དང་རིས་རྟགས་ཕྱི་ཚུལ་སྦོམ་བཟོ་བྱས་ནས། ཆ་འཕྲིན་ངོས་འཛིན་ཚད་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་མཛོད།】">
<feature>པར་ཆས་ཆུ་དཔར་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་ཆོག་པའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཆུ་དཔར་རང་ཉིད་ཀྱིས་སྣོན་པ་དང་སོར་ལོག་བྱ་ཆོག ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། པར་ལེན་ནས་འདྲ་པར་ཁ་ཕྱེ་བ། དེ་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག དེ་ནས་ཆུ་དཔར། དེ་ནས་ཆུ་དཔར་འདེམས་པ་སྟེ། ཐོག་མའི་པར་དང་ཡི་གེའི་ཆུ་དཔར། པར་སྒྲོམ་གྱི་ཆུ་དཔར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རིག་ལྡན་སྒྲོམ་མང་།】">
<feature>འཕྲེད་བརྙན་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་སུ་གཡེང་ཟླུམ་གྱི་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། གཡེང་ཟླུམ་སྡོད་པའི་གནས་ཡུལ་སྔོན་སྒྲིག་བརྙན་མིག་གི་ཁྱབ་ཁོངས་ལས་གཡོལ། མཚམས་ངོས་མངོན་སྟོན་དེ་བས་མཛེས་པ་ཡིན།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད།】">
<feature>ཡོལ་ཕབ་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་སུ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་སྒྲ་ཕབ་བཟོ་བྱེད་པའི་བསད་སྤར་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བརྙན་ཟློས་སམ་སྐད་གདངས་ཀྱི་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་ལེན་བྱེད་སྐབས། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་སྒྲ་ཕབ་བཟོ་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། ཡོལ་ཕབ་དེ་བས་ཆ་ཚང་ཡིན། སྒྲིག་འགོད་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རམ་འདེགས་རྩོལ་ནུས། དེ་ནས་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ཕབ་བཟོ། དེ་ནས་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་སྒྲ་ཕབ་བཟོ་བྱེད་པ།
ཡོལ་ཕབ་དབྱེ་འབྱེད་ཚད་རང་སྒྲིག་གི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། རིམ་པ་གསུམ་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱ་ཆོག (480P/720P/1080P) གང་འདོད་ཀྱིས་ལྟོས་ཟླའི་དབྱེ་འབྱེད་ཚད་བདམས་ནས་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ཕབ་བཟོ་བྱེད། ཡོལ་ཕབ་དེ་བས་གསལ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རམ་འདེགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས། དེ་ནས་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ཕབ་བཟོ། དེ་ནས་གསལ་ཚད་འདེམས་པ།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བསྡུ་ཉར་བར་སྟོང་།】">
<feature>བསྡུ་ཉར་བར་སྟོང་གི་འགུལ་ཁྱད་ཀྱི་ཐོགས་ཐུག་མེད་པའི་རང་བཞིན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་གིས་ར་སྤྲོད་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། འདྲ་པར་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ཡང་ན་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ / Android Auto འདེམས་སྐབས། ཐོབ་ཐང་གིས་ར་སྤྲོད་བྱེད་དགོས་ལ། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས་ཡིན་པར་བྱེད།
ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 10 བའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dragi korisniče, ovo ažuriranje omogućava uređivanje vodenih žigova i optimizira korisničko iskustvo pomoćne lopte. Dodatno, može se snimiti sistemski zvuk i dostupna su tri nivoa rezolucije za snimanje ekrana. Za USB vezu potrebna je autentifikacija korisnika. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje glatkoću efekta pokreta u statusnoj traci i Prostor za favorite, i uključuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećava veličinu teksta i podebljava ikone radi lakšeg prepoznavanja informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi se sada mogu dodavati i uklanjati po želji. Da isprobate ovu funkciju, idite u opciju Snimite fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Uredi > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Vodeni žig s tekstom, Vodeni žig s okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Višeprozorno">
<feature>Optimizira korisničko iskustvo s pomoćnom lopticom u pejzažnom načinu rada osiguravajući da se pomoćna loptica ne približava prednjem fotoaparatu, čime se pojednostavljuje interfejs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemske aplikacije">
<feature>Po želji možete snimati sistemski zvuk tokom glasovnih i video poziva. Da isprobate ovu funkciju, idite u: Postavke > Funkcije za pristupačnost > Videoklip sadržaja ekrana > Snimanje iz sistemskog zvuka.
Za kvalitet videozapisa sadržaja ekrana su dostupna tri nivoa rezolucije (480P/720P/1080P). Da isprobate ovu funkciju, idite u: Postavke > Funkcije za pristupačnost > Videoklip sadržaja ekrana > Kvalitet videozapisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za favorite">
<feature>Optimizira brzinu efekta kretanja u Prostoru za favorite.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Za USB povezivanje je obavezna provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android Auto prikazuje se potvrda ili sigurnosni upit kako bi se osigurao sigurniji prijenos podataka.
Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització permet editar les filigranes i optimitza l'experiència d'usuari de la bola d'assistència. A més, es pot enregistrar el so del sistema i hi ha disponibles tres nivells de resolució per als enregistraments de pantalla. Cal l'autenticació de l'usuari per a la connexió USB. Aquesta versió també optimitza la fluïdesa de l'efecte de moviment a la barra d'estat i l'Espai de Preferits, i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Es recomana actualitzar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra d'estat">
<feature>S'ha augmentat la mida del text i posat en negreta les icones perquè la informació sigui més fàcil de reconèixer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Ara, les filigranes es poden afegir i eliminar quan vulgueu. Podeu utilitzar aquestes funcions si aneu a Fer una foto > Obrir la foto > Editar > Filigrana > Opcions de filigrana: Original, Filigrana de text, Filigrana de marc.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Diverses finestres">
<feature>Optimitza l'experiència d'usuari de la bola d'assistència en el mode horitzontal, la qual cosa garanteix que la bola d'assistència estigui allunyada de la càmera frontal i, amb això, s'ofereix una interfície més senzilla.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicacions del sistema">
<feature>Podeu enregistrar el so del sistema durant trucades de vídeo o veu quan vulgueu. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Funcions d'accessibilitat > Enregistrament de pantalla > Enregistrar des del so del sistema.
Hi ha disponibles tres nivells de resolució (480P/720P/1080P) per a la qualitat del vídeo durant els enregistraments de pantalla. Per provar-los, aneu a: Configuració > Funcions d'accessibilitat > Enregistrament de pantalla > Qualitat del vídeo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espai de Preferits">
<feature>Optimitza la fluïdesa de l'efecte de moviment a l'Espai de Preferits.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>Cal l'autenticació de l'usuari per a la connexió USB. Apareix un missatge de verificació o de seguretat quan seleccioneu Transferir fotos o Transferir fitxers/Android Auto, per garantir una transferència de dades més segura.
S'ha incorporat un pedaç de seguretat d'Android (octubre de 2024) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, visiteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato aktualizace umožňuje upravovat vodoznaky a optimalizuje uživatelské prostředí pomocného míče. Navíc lze nahrávat systémový zvuk a pro záznam obrazovky jsou k dispozici tři úrovně rozlišení. K připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Tato verze také optimalizuje plynulost pohybového efektu ve stavovém řádku a Prostoru oblíbených a obsahuje bezpečnostní opravu. Doporučujeme aktualizovat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stavový řádek">
<feature>Zvětší velikost textu a zvýrazní ikony tučně, aby byly informace snáze rozpoznatelné.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Vodoznaky lze nyní přidávat a odstraňovat podle potřeby. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Pořídit fotografii > Otevřít fotografii > Upravit > Vodoznak > Možnosti vodoznaku: Originál, Textový vodoznak, Rámečkový vodoznak.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Více oken">
<feature>Optimalizuje uživatelský zážitek s pomocným míčem v režimu orientace na šířku a zajišťuje, že pomocný míč zůstává mimo přední fotoaparát, a nabízí tak jednodušší rozhraní.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systémové aplikace">
<feature>Během videohovorů nebo hlasových hovorů lze podle potřeby nahrávat systémový zvuk. Vyzkoušejte si to v nabídce: Nastavení > Funkce usnadnění > Záznam obrazovky > Záznam ze systémového zvuku.
Pro kvalitu videa v záznamech obrazovky jsou k dispozici tři úrovně rozlišení (480P / 720P / 1080P). Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Nastavení > Funkce usnadnění > Záznam obrazovky > Kvalita videa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor oblíbených">
<feature>Optimalizuje plynulost pohybového efektu v Prostoru oblíbených.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>K připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Když vyberete možnost Přenos fotografií nebo Přenos souborů / Android Auto, zobrazí se výzva k ověření nebo výzva zabezpečení, což zajistí bezpečnější přenos dat.
Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (říjen 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne opdatering tillader redigering af vandmærker og optimerer brugeroplevelsen med hjælpekuglen. Desuden kan systemlyden optages, og der er tre opløsningsniveauer tilgængelige for skærmoptagelser. Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet til USB-forbindelse. Denne udgave optimerer også bevægelseseffektens jævnhed på statuslinjen og i Favorites Space samt integrerer en sikkerhedsrettelse. Opdatering anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statuslinje">
<feature>Øger tekststørrelsen og fremhæver ikonerne for at gøre oplysningerne nemmere at genkende.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vandmærker kan nu tilføjes og fjernes som ønsket. Du kan opleve det ved at gå til: Tag et foto > Åbn fotoet > Rediger > Vandmærke > Vandmærkeindstillinger: Original, Tekstvandmærke, Rammevandmærke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-vindue">
<feature>Optimerer brugeroplevelsen med hjælpekuglen i liggende tilstand, hvilket sikrer, at hjælpekuglen holdes væk fra frontkameraet, så der tilbydes en enklere grænseflade.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systemapps">
<feature>Du kan optage systemlyd under video- eller taleopkald som ønsket. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Tilgængelighedsfunktioner > Skærmoptagelse > Optag fra systemlyd.
Tre opløsningsniveauer (480p/720p/1080p) er tilgængelige for videokvalitet i skærmoptagelser. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Tilgængelighedsfunktioner > Skærmoptagelse > Videokvalitet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Optimerer bevægelseseffektens jævnhed i Favorites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet til USB-forbindelse. En bekræftelses- eller sikkerhedsprompt bliver vist, når du vælger Overfør fotos eller Overfør filer/Android Auto, hvilket garanterer sikrere dataoverførsel.
Android sikkerhedsrettelse (okt 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen und optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball. Außerdem lässt sich der Systemton aufzeichnen und für Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen zur Verfügung. Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert außerdem die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte in der Statusleiste und im Favoritenbereich und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball im Querformat und stellt sicher, dass der Assistive Ball nicht in die Nähe der Frontkamera gerät und so die Benutzeroberfläche vereinfacht wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System-Apps">
<feature>Bei Video- oder Sprachanrufen können Sie den Systemton aufzeichnen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Aufnahme vom Systemton.
Für die Videoqualität bei Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen (480p/720p/1080p) zur Verfügung. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Videoqualität.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritenbereich">
<feature>Optimiert die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte im Favoritenbereich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen und optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball. Außerdem lässt sich der Systemton aufzeichnen und für Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen zur Verfügung. Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert außerdem die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte in der Statusleiste und im Favoritenbereich und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball im Querformat und stellt sicher, dass der Assistive Ball nicht in die Nähe der Frontkamera gerät und so die Benutzeroberfläche vereinfacht wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System-Apps">
<feature>Bei Video- oder Sprachanrufen können Sie den Systemton aufzeichnen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Aufnahme vom Systemton.
Für die Videoqualität bei Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen (480p/720p/1080p) zur Verfügung. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Videoqualität.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritenbereich">
<feature>Optimiert die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte im Favoritenbereich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen und optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball. Außerdem lässt sich der Systemton aufzeichnen und für Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen zur Verfügung. Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert außerdem die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte in der Statusleiste und im Favoritenbereich und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Optimiert das Benutzererlebnis für Assistive Ball im Querformat und stellt sicher, dass der Assistive Ball nicht in die Nähe der Frontkamera gerät und so die Benutzeroberfläche vereinfacht wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System-Apps">
<feature>Bei Video- oder Sprachanrufen können Sie den Systemton aufzeichnen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Aufnahme vom Systemton.
Für die Videoqualität bei Bildschirmaufnahmen stehen drei Auflösungsstufen (480p/720p/1080p) zur Verfügung. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Bildschirmaufnahme > Videoqualität.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritenbereich">
<feature>Optimiert die Laufruhe der Bewegungseffekte im Favoritenbereich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Für die USB-Verbindung ist eine Benutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση επιτρέπει την επεξεργασία υδατογραφημάτων και βελτιστοποιεί την εμπειρία χρήστη της βοηθητικής μπάλας. Επιπλέον, είναι δυνατή η καταγραφή του ήχου συστήματος και διατίθενται τρία επίπεδα ανάλυσης για καταγραφές οθόνης. Απαιτείται έλεγχος ταυτότητας χρήστη για τη σύνδεση USB. Αυτή η έκδοση βελτιστοποιεί επίσης την ομαλότητα του εφέ κίνησης στη γραμμή κατάστασης και στον Χώρο αγαπημένων και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Συνιστάται η ενημέρωση.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Γραμμή κατάστασης">
<feature>Αυξάνει το μέγεθος του κειμένου και κάνει πιο έντονα τα εικονίδια για να διευκολύνει την αναγνώριση των πληροφοριών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Συλλογή">
<feature>Τα υδατογραφήματα μπορούν πλέον να προστεθούν και να αφαιρεθούν, όπως επιθυμείτε. Μπορείτε να το δοκιμάσετε μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Λήψη φωτογραφίας > Άνοιγμα της φωτογραφίας > Επεξεργασία > Υδατογράφημα > Επιλογές υδατογραφήματος: Αρχικό, Υδατογράφημα κειμένου, Υδατογράφημα πλαισίου.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Πολλαπλά παράθυρα">
<feature>Βελτιστοποιεί την εμπειρία χρήστη της βοηθητικής σφαίρας σε οριζόντια λειτουργία, διασφαλίζοντας ότι η βοηθητική σφαίρα θα παραμένει μακριά από την μπροστινή κάμερα, προσφέροντας έτσι μια απλούστερη διεπαφή.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εφαρμογές συστήματος">
<feature>Μπορείτε να καταγράψετε τον ήχο συστήματος κατά τη διάρκεια βιντεοκλήσεων ή φωνητικών κλήσεων, όπως επιθυμείτε. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις: Ρυθμίσεις > Δυνατότητες προσβασιμότητας > Καταγραφή οθόνης > Καταγραφή από τον ήχο του συστήματος.
Τρία επίπεδα ανάλυσης (480P/720P/1080P) είναι διαθέσιμα για την ποιότητα βίντεο στις καταγραφές οθόνης. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις: Ρυθμίσεις > Δυνατότητες προσβασιμότητας > Καταγραφή οθόνης > Ποιότητα βίντεο.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Χώρος αγαπημένων">
<feature>Βελτιστοποιεί την ομαλότητα του εφέ κίνησης στον Χώρο αγαπημένων.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Απαιτείται έλεγχος ταυτότητας χρήστη για τη σύνδεση USB. Ένα μήνυμα επαλήθευσης ή ασφάλειας εμφανίζεται όταν επιλέγετε «Μεταφορά φωτογραφιών» ή «Μεταφορά αρχείων/Android Auto», εξασφαλίζοντας πιο ασφαλή μεταφορά δεδομένων.
Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Οκτώβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update allows watermarks to be edited, and optimises the user experience of assistive ball. Additionally, system sound can be recorded and three resolution levels are available for screen recordings. User authentication is required for USB connection. This release also optimises the smoothness of motion effect in status bar and Favourites Space, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Increases the text size, and bolds the icons to make the information easier to recognise.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Watermarks can now be added and removed as desired. You can experience it by going to: Take a photo > Open the photo > Edit > Watermark > Watermark options: Original, Text watermark, Frame watermark.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Optimises the user experience of assistive ball in landscape mode, ensuring the assistive ball stays away from the front camera, thereby offering a simpler interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System apps">
<feature>You can record system sound during video or voice calls as desired. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Screen recording > Record from system sound.
Three resolution levels (480P/720P/1080P) are available for video quality in screen recordings. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Screen recording > Video quality.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favourites Space">
<feature>Optimises the smoothness of the motion effect in Favourites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>User authentication is required for USB connection. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, ensuring safer data transfer.
Android security patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/ usuario/a, esta actualización permite editar marcas de agua y optimiza la experiencia de usuario del icono de asistencia. Además, se puede grabar el sonido del sistema y hay tres niveles de resolución disponibles para grabaciones de pantalla. Se requiere autenticación de usuario para la conexión USB. Esta versión también optimiza la suavidad del efecto de movimiento en la barra de estado y el Espacio de Favoritos, e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta el tamaño del texto y pone los iconos en negrita para que la información sea más fácil de reconocer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Ahora se pueden agregar y eliminar marcas de agua según se desee. Para probarlo vaya a Tomar una foto > Abrir la foto > Editar > Marca de agua > Opciones de marca de agua: Original, Marca de agua de texto, Marca de agua de marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Optimiza la experiencia del usuario del icono de asistencia en modo horizontal, garantizando que el icono de asistencia se mantenga alejado de la cámara frontal, ofreciendo así una interfaz más sencilla.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicaciones del sistema">
<feature>Puede grabar el sonido del sistema durante llamadas de voz o vídeo según se desee. Puede probarlo en: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Grabación de pantalla > Grabar desde el sonido del sistema.
Hay tres niveles de resolución (480p/720p/1080p) disponibles para la calidad de vídeo en grabaciones de pantalla. Puede probarlos en: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Grabación de pantalla > Calidad de vídeo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espacio de Favoritos">
<feature>Optimiza la suavidad del efecto de movimiento en el Espacio de Favoritos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario para la conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.
Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización permite editar marcas de agua y optimiza la experiencia de usuario de la bola de asistencia. Además, se puede grabar el sonido del sistema y hay tres niveles de resolución disponibles para grabaciones de pantalla. Se requiere autenticación de usuario para la conexión USB. Esta versión también optimiza el efecto de suavidad del movimiento en la barra de estado y el Espacio favoritos, e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta el tamaño del texto y pone los íconos en negrita para que la información sea más fácil de reconocer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Ahora se pueden agregar y eliminar marcas de agua según se desee. Puede experimentarlo en: Tomar una foto > Abrir la foto > Editar > Marca de agua > Opciones de Marca de agua: Original, Marca de agua de texto, Marca de agua del marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Optimiza la experiencia de usuario de la bola de asistencia en modo horizontal, lo que garantiza que la bola de asistencia se mantenga alejada de la cámara frontal y, así, ofrecer una interfaz más sencilla.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicaciones del sistema">
<feature>Puede grabar el sonido del sistema durante llamadas de voz o video según se desee. Pruébelo desde: Ajustes> Funciones de accesibilidad > Grabación de pantalla > Grabar desde el sonido del sistema.
Existen tres niveles de resolución (480P/720P/1080P) disponibles para la calidad de video en las grabaciones de pantalla. Pruébelo desde: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Grabación de pantalla > Calidad de video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espacio favoritos">
<feature>Optimiza el efecto de suavidad del movimiento en el Espacio favoritos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario para la conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.
Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus võimaldab vesimärke redigeerida ja optimeerib abipalli kasutajakogemust. Lisaks saab salvestada süsteemiheli ja kuvasalvestuste jaoks on saadaval kolm eraldusvõimet. USB-ühenduse korral on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. See värskendus optimeerib ka liikumisefekti sujuvust olekuribal ja Lemmikute ruumis ning sisaldab turvapaika. Soovitatav on värskendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Olekuriba">
<feature>Suurendab teksti suurust ja kuvab ikoonid paksult, et teave oleks lihtsamini äratuntav.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerii">
<feature>Nüüd saab vesimärke vabalt lisada ja eemaldada. Selleks tehke foto > avage foto > valige Redigeeri > Vesimärk > Vesimärgi suvandid: Algne, Tekstiline vesimärk või Raamiga vesimärk.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mitu akent">
<feature>Optimeerib horisontaalrežiimis abipalli kasutajakogemust, tagades, et abipall jääb esikaamerast eemale ning muutes seeläbi liidese kasutamise lihtsamaks.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteemirakendused">
<feature>Saate soovi korral salvestada süsteemiheli video- või häälkõnede ajal. Proovige seda, minnes menüüsse Sätted > Hõlbustusfunktsioonid > Kuvasalvestis > Süsteemiheliga salvestamine.
Kuvasalvestiste videokvaliteedi jaoks on saadaval kolm eraldusvõimet (480P/720P/1080P). Proovige seda, minnes menüüsse Sätted > Hõlbustusfunktsioonid > Kuvasalvestis > Video kvaliteet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lemmikute ruum">
<feature>Optimeerib liikumisefekti sujuvust Lemmikute ruumis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>USB-ühenduse korral on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. Kui valite Edasta fotosid või Edasta faile / Android Auto, kuvatakse kinnitus- või turvaviip, mis tagab turvalisema andmeedastuse.
Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (oktoober 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honetan ur-markak edita daitezke eta laguntza-bolaren erabiltzaile-esperientzia optimizatu da. Gainera, sistemaren soinua graba daiteke eta hiru bereizmen-maila daude pant. grabaketetarako. Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa behar da USB konexiorako. Bertsio honek ere optimizatu egiten du mugimendu-efektuaren leuntasuna egoera-barran eta Gogokoen gunean, eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu du. Eguneratzea gomendatzen da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Egoera-barra">
<feature>Testuaren tamaina handitu da eta ikonoak letra lodiz ageri dira informazioa errazago ezagutzeko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Orain, ur-markak nahierara gehitu eta ezaba daitezke. Horretarako, joan hona: Atera argazkia > Ireki argazkia > Editatu > Ur-marka > Ur-markaren aukerak: Jatorrizkoa, Testuaren ur-marka, Markoaren ur-marka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leiho anitz">
<feature>Modu horizontaleko laguntza-bolaren erabiltzaile-esperientzia optimizatzen du, laguntza-bola aurreko kameratik urrun mantentzen dela ziurtatuz eta, horrela, interfazea sinpleagoa eginez.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemaren aplikazioak">
<feature>Sistemaren soinua grabatu dezakezu nahi dituzun bideo-deietan edo ahots-deietan. Horretarako, jo hona: Ezarpenak > Erabilerraztasun-funtzioak > Pant. grabaketa > Sistemaren soinuaren grabaketa.
Hiru bereizmen-maila daude (480P/720P/1080P) pant. grabazioetako bideoen kalitaterako. Horretarako, jo hona: Ezarpenak > Erabilerraztasun-funtzioak > Pant. grabaketa > Bideoaren kalitatea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gogokoen gunea">
<feature>Gogokoen gunean mugimendu-efektuaren leuntasuna optimizatzen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa behar da USB konexiorako. Transferitu argazkiak edo Transferitu fitxategiak / Android Auto hautatzen duzunean, egiaztapen- edo segurtasun-abisu bat agertzen da, datuak seguruago transferitzen direla ziurtatzeko.
Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko urr) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی امکان ویرایش واترمارک‌ها را فراهم می‌کند و تجربه کاربر توپ کمکی را بهینه می‌کند. به‌علاوه، صدای سیستم را می‌توان ضبط کرد و سه سطح وضوح برای ضبط صفحه‌نمایش در دسترس است. تأیید هویت کاربر برای اتصال USB لازم است. این نسخه همچنین روان بودن جلوه حرکت را در نوار وضعیت و «فضای موارد دلخواه» بهینه می‌کند و دارای یک وصله امنیتی است. توصیه می‌شود به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوار وضعیت">
<feature>اندازۀ متن را افزایش می‌دهد و آیکون‌ها را پررنگ می‌کند تا اطلاعات راحت‌تر تشخیص داده شوند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="گالری">
<feature>اکنون می‌توانید واترمارک‌ها را به‌دلخواه اضافه و حذف کنید. می‌توانید آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: «گرفتن عکس > باز کردن عکس > ویرایش > واترمارک > گزینه‌های واترمارک: اصلی، واترمارک متنی، واترمارک قاب».</feature>
</features>
<features module="پنجره‌ها">
<feature>تجربه کاربر از توپ کمکی را در حالت افقی بهینه می‌کند که فاصله داشتن توپ کمکی از دوربین جلو را تضمین می‌کند و در نتیجه رابط کاربری ساده‌تری فراهم می‌شود.</feature>
</features>
<features module="برنامه‌های سیستم">
<feature>می‌توانید صدای سیستم را در حین تماس‌های ویدیویی یا صوتی به‌دلخواه ضبط کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: «تنظیمات > امکانات مربوط به قابلیت دسترسی > ضبط صفحه‌نمایش > ضبط از صدای سیستم».
سه سطح وضوح (480P/720P/1080P) برای کیفیت ویدیو در ضبط صفحه‌نمایش موجود است. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: «تنظیمات > امکانات مربوط به قابلیت دسترسی > ضبط صفحه‌نمایش > کیفیت ویدیو».</feature>
</features>
<features module="فضای موارد دلخواه">
<feature>روان بودن جلوه حرکت در «فضای موارد دلخواه» را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>تأیید هویت کاربر برای اتصال USB لازم است. هنگامی‌که گزینه «انتقال تصاویر» یا «انتقال فایل‌ها / Android Auto» را انتخاب می‌کنید، یک پیام‌واره تأیید یا امنیتی ظاهر می‌شود تا انتقال ایمن‌تر داده‌ها تأمین شود.
برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصله امنیتی Android (اکتبر ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر درباره به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به نشانی https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 مراجعه کنید</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات قابل‌توجه:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys mahdollistaa vesileimojen muokkaamisen ja optimoi apupallon käyttökokemuksen. Lisäksi järjestelmän äänet voidaan tallentaa, ja näytön tallennusta varten on käytettävissä kolme resoluutiotasoa. USB-liitäntää varten vaaditaan käyttäjän todentaminen. Lisäksi tämä päivitys optimoi liiketehosteen sujuvuuden tilapalkissa ja suosikkien tilassa ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen. Päivittämistä suositellaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tilapalkki">
<feature>Suurentaa tekstin kokoa ja lihavoi kuvakkeet, jotta tiedot on helpompi tunnistaa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Vesileimoja voidaan nyt lisätä ja poistaa tarpeen mukaan. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavalla tavalla: Ota valokuva > Avaa valokuva > Muokkaa > Vesileima > Vesileimavaihtoehdot: Alkuperäinen, Tekstivesileima, Kehyksen vesileima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Moni-ikkuna">
<feature>Optimoi apupallon käyttökokemuksen vaakatilassa varmistamalla, että apupallo pysyy poissa etukamerasta, mikä tarjoaa yksinkertaisemman käyttöliittymän.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmäsovellukset">
<feature>Voit tallentaa järjestelmän äänet video- tai äänipuheluiden aikana tarpeen mukaan. Kokeile sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Helppokäyttöominaisuudet > Näytön tallennus > Tallenna järjestelmän äänestä.
Näytön tallennusta varten on käytettävissä kolme resoluutiotasoa (480P/720P/1080P). Kokeile sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Helppokäyttöominaisuudet > Näytön tallennus > Videon laatu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suosikkien tila">
<feature>Optimoi liiketehosteen sujuvuuden suosikkien tilassa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>USB-liitäntää varten vaaditaan käyttäjän todentaminen. Kun valitset Siirrä valokuvia tai Siirrä tiedostoja / Android Auto sen sijaan, että valitsisit Vain lataus -vaihtoehdon, tarkastus- tai turvallisuuskehote avautuu, mikä varmistaa turvallisemman tiedonsiirron.
Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (lokakuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour permet de modifier les filigranes et optimise l'expérience utilisateur de la boule d'assistance. De plus, le son du système peut être enregistré et trois niveaux de résolution sont disponibles pour les captures vidéo d'écran. L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise pour la connexion USB. Cette version optimise également la fluidité de l'effet de mouvement dans la barre d'état et l'Espace Favoris, et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barre d'état">
<feature>Augmente la taille du texte et met en gras les icônes pour rendre les informations plus faciles à reconnaître.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Les filigranes peuvent désormais être ajoutés et supprimés à volonté. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à : Prendre une photo > Ouvrir la photo > Retoucher > Filigrane > Options de filigrane : Original, Filigrane de texte, Filigrane du cadre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Optimise l'expérience utilisateur de la boule d'assistance en mode paysage, garantissant que la boule d'assistance reste éloignée de l'appareil photo avant, offrant ainsi une interface plus simple.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Applications système">
<feature>Le son du système peut être enregistré pendant les appels vidéo ou vocaux selon vos besoins. Essayez-le en allant dans : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Capture vidéo d'écran > Enregistrer depuis son système.
Trois niveaux de résolution (480P/720P/1080P) sont disponibles pour la qualité vidéo dans les captures vidéo d'écran. Faites-en l'essai en allant dans : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Capture vidéo d'écran > Qualité vidéo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espace Favoris">
<feature>Optimise la fluidité de l'effet de mouvement dans l'Espace Favoris.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise pour la connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour permet de modifier les filigranes et optimise l'expérience utilisateur de la boule d'assistance. De plus, le son du système peut être enregistré et trois niveaux de résolution sont disponibles pour les captures vidéo d'écran. L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise pour la connexion USB. Cette version optimise également la fluidité de l'effet de mouvement dans la barre d'état et l'Espace Favoris, et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barre d'état">
<feature>Augmente la taille du texte et met en gras les icônes pour rendre les informations plus faciles à reconnaître.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Les filigranes peuvent désormais être ajoutés et supprimés à volonté. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à : Prendre une photo > Ouvrir la photo > Retoucher > Filigrane > Options de filigrane : Original, Filigrane de texte, Filigrane du cadre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Optimise l'expérience utilisateur de la boule d'assistance en mode paysage, garantissant que la boule d'assistance reste éloignée de l'appareil photo avant, offrant ainsi une interface plus simple.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Applications système">
<feature>Le son du système peut être enregistré pendant les appels vidéo ou vocaux selon vos besoins. Essayez-le en allant dans : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Capture vidéo d'écran > Enregistrer depuis son système.
Trois niveaux de résolution (480P/720P/1080P) sont disponibles pour la qualité vidéo dans les captures vidéo d'écran. Faites-en l'essai en allant dans : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Capture vidéo d'écran > Qualité vidéo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espace Favoris">
<feature>Optimise la fluidité de l'effet de mouvement dans l'Espace Favoris.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise pour la connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización permite editar as marcas de auga, e optimiza a experiencia do usuario da bóla de asistencia. Ademais, é posible gravar o son do sistema, con tres niveis de resolución da gravación da pantalla. Requerirase a autenticación do usuario para a conexión USB. Esta versión tamén optimiza a fluidez do efecto de movemento da barra de estado e o Espazo de favoritos, e incorpora un parche de seguranza. Recoméndase actualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta o tamaño do texto e destaca as iconas para que sexa máis fácil recoñecer a información.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Agora poden engadirse e eliminarse marcase de auga segundo o desexe. Pode experimentalo seguindo estes pasos: Tome unha foto > Abra a foto > Editar > Marca de auga > Opcións de marca de auga: Orixinal, De texto, De marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Múltiples ventás">
<feature>Optimiza a experiencia do usuario da bóla de asistencia no modo paisaxe para garantir que a bóla de asistencia non se mostre na cámara frontal, de xeito que se simplifique a interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicacións do sistema">
<feature>Pode gravar os sons do sistema durante chamadas de vídeo ou voz, segundo o desexe. Para probalo, vaia a: Configuración > Características de accesibilidade > Gravación de pantalla > Gravar co son do sistema.
Hai tres niveis de resolución (480P/720P/1080P) de calidade do vídeo dispoñibles para gravacións de pantallas. Para probalo, vaia a Configuración > Características de accesibilidade > Gravación de pantalla > Calidade do vídeo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espazo de favoritos">
<feature>Optimiza a fluidez do efecto de movemento no Espazo de favoritos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Requírese a autenticación do usuario para a conexión USB. Aparecerá unha verificación ou unha mensaxe de seguranza cando seleccione Transferir fotos ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, para garantir unha transferencia de datos máis segura.
Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (outubro de 2024) para mellorar a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia a un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ વૉટરમાર્ક્સને સંપાદિત કરવાની અનુમતિ આપે છે અને સહાયક બોલના વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને શ્રેષ્ઠ બનાવે છે. વધુમાં, સિસ્ટમ સાઉન્ડ રેકોર્ડ કરી શકાય છે અને સ્ક્રીન રેકોર્ડિંગ માટે ત્રણ રિઝોલ્યુશન લેવલ ઉપલબ્ધ છે. USB કનેક્શન માટે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. આ રીલીઝ સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી અને મનપસંદ જગ્યામાં ગતિ પ્રભાવની સુગમતાને પણ ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે. અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી">
<feature>ટેક્સ્ટનું કદ વધે છે અને માહિતીને ઓળખવામાં સરળ બનાવવા માટે ચિહ્નોને બોલ્ડ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગૅલેરી">
<feature>વૉટરમાર્ક હવે ઇચ્છિત તરીકે ઉમેરી અને દૂર કરી શકાય છે. તમે અહીં જઈને તેનો અનુભવ કરી શકો છો: ફોટો લો > ફોટો ખોલો > સંપાદિત કરો > વૉટરમાર્ક > વૉટરમાર્કના વિકલ્પો: મૂળભૂત, ટેક્સ્ટ વૉટરમાર્ક, ફ્રેમ વૉટરમાર્ક.</feature>
</features>
<features module="મલ્ટિ-વિન્ડો">
<feature>લેન્ડસ્કેપ મોડમાં સહાયક બૉલના વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, ખાતરી કરે છે કે સહાયક બૉલ આગળના કૅમેરાથી દૂર રહે છે, ત્યાંથી એક સરળ ઇન્ટરફેસ ઓફર કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ એપ્લિકેશન્સ">
<feature>તમે ઈચ્છા મુજબ વિડિઓઝ અથવા વૉઇસ કૉલ દરમિયાન સિસ્ટમ સાઉન્ડ રેકોર્ડ કરી શકો છો. અહીં જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > ઍક્સેસિબિલિટી સુવિધાઓ > સ્ક્રીન રેકોર્ડિંગ > સિસ્ટમ સાઉન્ડ પરથી રેકોર્ડ કરો.
સ્ક્રીન રેકોર્ડિંગમાં વિડિઓઝ ગુણવત્તા માટે ત્રણ રિઝોલ્યુશન લેવલ (480P/720P/1080P) ઉપલબ્ધ છે. અહીં જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > ઍક્સેસિબિલિટી સુવિધાઓ > સ્ક્રીન રેકોર્ડિંગ > વિડિઓઝ ગુણવત્તા.</feature>
</features>
<features module="મનપસંદ જગ્યા">
<feature>મનપસંદ જગ્યામાં ગતિ પ્રભાવની સરળતાને શ્રેષ્ઠ બનાવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>USB કનેક્શન માટે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. જ્યારે તમે સુરક્ષિત ડેટા ટ્રાન્સફરને સુનિશ્ચિત કરીને ફોટા ટ્રાન્સફર કરો અથવા ફાઇલો ટ્રાન્સફર કરો / Android Auto પસંદ કરો ત્યારે ચકાસણી અથવા સુરક્ષા પ્રોમ્પ્ટ દેખાય છે.
Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ઓકટોબર 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से वाटरमार्क संपादित करने और सहायक बॉल के उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव को अनुकूलित करने की अनुमति मिलती है। इसके अतिरिक्त, सिस्टम ध्वनि रिकॉर्ड की जा सकती है और स्क्रीन रिकॉर्डिंग के लिए तीन रिज़ॉल्यूशन स्तर उपलब्ध हैं। USB कनेक्शन के लिए उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक है। इस रिलीज़ से स्थिति बार और पसंदीदा स्पेस में गति प्रभाव के सुचारुपन को भी अनुकूलित किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता है। अद्यतन करने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति बार">
<feature>जानकारी की पहचान करना आसान बनाने के लिए पाठ का आकार बढ़ाया जाता है और आइकन को बोल्ड किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>वाटरमार्क अब मनमुताबिक जोड़े और निकाले जा सकते हैं। आप यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव पा सकते हैं: फ़ोटो लें > फ़ोटो खोलें > संपादित करें > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्क के विकल्प: मूल, पाठ वाटरमार्क, फ़्रेम वाटरमार्क।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>भूदृश्य मोड में सहायक बॉल के उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है, ताकि यह सुनिश्चित हो सके कि सहायक बॉल सामने का कैमरा से दूर रहे और आसान इंटरफ़ेस दिया जा सके।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम ऐप्स">
<feature>आप अपने हिसाब से वीडियो या वॉइस कॉल के दौरान सिस्टम ध्वनि रिकॉर्ड कर सकते हैं। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > पहुँच क्षमता सुविधाएँ > स्क्रीन रिकॉर्डिंग > सिस्टम ध्वनि से रिकॉर्ड करें।
स्क्रीन रिकॉर्डिंग में वीडियो गुणवत्ता के लिए तीन रिज़ॉल्यूशन स्तर (480P/720P/1080P) उपलब्ध हैं। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > पहुँच क्षमता सुविधाएँ > स्क्रीन रिकॉर्डिंग > वीडियो गुणवत्ता।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पसंदीदा स्पेस">
<feature>पसंदीदा स्पेस में गति प्रभाव के सुचारुपन को अनुकूलित किया गया है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन के लिए उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। जब आप फ़ोटो ट्रांसफ़र करें या फ़ाइलें ट्रांसफ़र करें / Android Auto चुनते हैं, तो सत्यापन या सुरक्षा का संकेत दिखता है जिससे सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित होता है।
सिस्टम सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem omogućuje uređivanje vodenih žigova i optimizira korisničko iskustvo pomoćne kuglice. Osim toga, moguće je snimiti zvuk sustava i tri razine razlučivosti dostupne su za snimku zaslona. Za USB vezu potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Ovo izdanje također optimizira ujednačenost efekta kretanja u statusnoj traci i prostoru za omiljene stavke te uključuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećava se veličina teksta i podebljavaju se ikone radi lakšeg prepoznavanja informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada se mogu dodavati i uklanjati po želji. Isprobajte ih odlaskom na: Snimi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Uredi > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Izvornik, Tekst vodenog žiga, Okvirni vodeni žig.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prikaz u više prozora">
<feature>Optimizira korisničko iskustvo pomoćnog kruga u pejzažnom načinu, osiguravajući da pomoćni krug ostane dalje od prednjeg fotoaparata, čime se nudi jednostavnije sučelje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije sustava">
<feature>Možete snimati zvuk sustava tijekom video ili glasovnih poziva po želji. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Značajke dostupnosti > Snimka zaslona > Snimanje iz zvuka sustava.
Tri su razine razlučivosti (480P/720P/1080P) dostupne za kvalitetu videozapisa tijekom snimanja zaslona. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Značajke dostupnosti > Snimka zaslona > Kvaliteta videozapisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za omiljene stavke">
<feature>Optimizira ujednačenost efekta kretanja u Prostoru za omiljene stavke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Za USB vezu potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka / Android Auto, pojavljuje se upit za provjeru ili sigurnost, čime se osigurava sigurniji prijenos podataka.
Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (listopad 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés lehetővé teszi a vízjelek szerkesztését, és optimalizálja a kisegítő labdák felhasználói élményét. Ezenfelül lehetővé teszi a rendszer hangjának a rögzítését, és három felbontási szintet kínál a képernyőfelvételekhez. Az USB-kapcsolat kialakításához felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ez a verzió emellett optimalizálja a mozgási effektusok egyenletességét az állapotsávon és a Kedvencek terében, valamint egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Állapotsáv">
<feature>Növeli a szöveg méretét és félkövérrel jeleníti meg az ikonokat, hogy az információk átláthatóbbak legyenek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Mostantól tetszés szerint hozzáadhat és eltávolíthat vízjeleket. Próbálja ki, készítsen egy fényképet > nyissa meg a fényképet > Szerkesztés > Vízjel > a vízjelekhez elérhető opciók: Eredeti, Szöveges vízjel, Keretes vízjel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Többablakos">
<feature>Optimalizáltuk a segédlabda felhasználói élményét fekvő módban: a segédlabda távol marad az előlapi kamerától, így egyszerűbbé vált a kezelőfelület.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszeralkalmazások">
<feature>Mostantól tetszés szerint rögzítheti a rendszer hangját a video- és hanghívások közben. Próbálja ki: Beállítások > Kisegítő lehetőségek > Képernyőfelvétel > Rögzítés a rendszerhangból.
A képernyőfelvételek videominőségéhez három felbontás (480P/720P/1080P) érhető el. Próbálja ki: Beállítások > Kisegítő lehetőségek > Képernyőfelvétel > Videóminőség.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kedvencek tere">
<feature>Optimalizáltuk a mozgási hatás egyenletességét a Kedvencek terén.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Az USB-kapcsolat kialakításához felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ha a Fotók átvitele vagy a Fájlok átvitele/Android Auto opciót választja, megjelenik egy hitelesítési vagy biztonsági üzenet, amelynek célja, hogy az adatátvitel garantáltan biztonságos legyen.
A rendszerbiztonság érdekében a frissítés tartalmazza az Android biztonsági frissítését (2024. október) is. A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memungkinkan tanda air diedit, dan mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan. Selain itu, suara sistem dapat direkam dan tiga level resolusi tersedia untuk perekaman layar. Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan untuk koneksi USB. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan kelancaran efek gerakan di bilah status dan Ruang Favorit, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Sebaiknya Anda melakukan pembaruan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bilah status">
<feature>Menambah ukuran teks, dan menebalkan ikon agar informasi lebih mudah dikenali.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tanda air kini dapat ditambahkan dan dihapus sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tanda air > Opsi tanda air: Asli, Tanda air teks, Tanda air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan dalam mode lanskap, memastikan bola bantuan tetap menjauh dari kamera depan, sehingga memberikan antarmuka yang lebih sederhana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi sistem">
<feature>Anda dapat merekam suara sistem selama panggilan suara atau video sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Perekaman layar > Rekam dari suara sistem.
Tiga level resolusi (480P/720P/1080P) tersedia untuk kualitas video dalam perekaman layar. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Perekaman layar > Kualitas video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ruang Favorit">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan kelancaran efek di Ruang Favorit.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan untuk koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, sehingga memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.
Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memungkinkan tanda air diedit, dan mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan. Selain itu, suara sistem dapat direkam dan tiga level resolusi tersedia untuk perekaman layar. Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan untuk koneksi USB. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan kelancaran efek gerakan di bilah status dan Ruang Favorit, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Sebaiknya Anda melakukan pembaruan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bilah status">
<feature>Menambah ukuran teks, dan menebalkan ikon agar informasi lebih mudah dikenali.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tanda air kini dapat ditambahkan dan dihapus sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tanda air > Opsi tanda air: Asli, Tanda air teks, Tanda air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan dalam mode lanskap, memastikan bola bantuan tetap menjauh dari kamera depan, sehingga memberikan antarmuka yang lebih sederhana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi sistem">
<feature>Anda dapat merekam suara sistem selama panggilan suara atau video sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Perekaman layar > Rekam dari suara sistem.
Tiga level resolusi (480P/720P/1080P) tersedia untuk kualitas video dalam perekaman layar. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Perekaman layar > Kualitas video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ruang Favorit">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan kelancaran efek di Ruang Favorit.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan untuk koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, sehingga memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.
Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consente di modificare le filigrane e ottimizza l'esperienza utente della sfera di assistenza. Inoltre, è possibile registrare l'audio del sistema e sono disponibili tre livelli di risoluzione per le registrazioni schermo. Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente per la connessione USB. Questa versione ottimizza inoltre la fluidità dell'effetto movimento nella barra di stato e nello Spazio preferiti e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra di stato">
<feature>È stata aumentata la dimensione del testo e formattato in grassetto il testo delle icone per facilitare la lettura delle informazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>È ora possibile aggiungere e rimuovere le filigrane come desiderato. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Scatta una foto > Apri la foto > Modifica > Filigrana > Opzioni filigrana: Originale, Filigrana di testo, Filigrana cornice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>Per semplificare l'interfaccia, è stata ottimizzata l'esperienza utente della sfera di assistenza in modalità orizzontale evitando che si sovrapponga alla fotocamera frontale.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App di sistema">
<feature>È possibile registrare l'audio del sistema durante le videochiamate o le chiamate vocali. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Registrazione schermo > Registra dall'audio del sistema.
Sono disponibili tre livelli di risoluzione per la qualità video delle registrazioni dello schermo: 480p, 720p e 1080p. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Registrazione schermo > Qualità video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spazio preferiti">
<feature>È stata ottimizzata la fluidità dell'effetto movimento nello Spazio preferiti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente per la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consente di modificare le filigrane e ottimizza l'esperienza utente della sfera di assistenza. Inoltre, è possibile registrare l'audio del sistema e sono disponibili tre livelli di risoluzione per le registrazioni schermo. Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente per la connessione USB. Questa versione ottimizza inoltre la fluidità dell'effetto movimento nella barra di stato e nello Spazio preferiti e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra di stato">
<feature>È stata aumentata la dimensione del testo e formattato in grassetto il testo delle icone per facilitare la lettura delle informazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>È ora possibile aggiungere e rimuovere le filigrane come desiderato. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Scatta una foto > Apri la foto > Modifica > Filigrana > Opzioni filigrana: Originale, Filigrana di testo, Filigrana cornice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>Per semplificare l'interfaccia, è stata ottimizzata l'esperienza utente della sfera di assistenza in modalità orizzontale evitando che si sovrapponga alla fotocamera frontale.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App di sistema">
<feature>È possibile registrare l'audio del sistema durante le videochiamate o le chiamate vocali. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Registrazione schermo > Registra dall'audio del sistema.
Sono disponibili tre livelli di risoluzione per la qualità video delle registrazioni dello schermo: 480p, 720p e 1080p. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Registrazione schermo > Qualità video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spazio preferiti">
<feature>È stata ottimizzata la fluidità dell'effetto movimento nello Spazio preferiti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente per la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מאפשר לערוך סימני מים, וממטב את חוויית המשתמש של כדור העזר. בנוסף, ניתן להקליט צלילי מערכת ושלוש רמות רזולוציה זמינות להקלטות מסך. אימות משתמש נדרש לחיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את החלקות של אפקט התנועה בשורת מצב וב'מרחב מועדפים', ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="שורת מצב">
<feature>מגדיל את גודל הטקסט ומבליט את הסמלים כדי להקל על זיהוי המידע.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להוסיף ולהסיר סימני מים לפי הצורך. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל: 'צלם תמונה' > 'פתח את התמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'סימן מים' > אפשרויות 'סימן מים': מקור, סימן מים של טקסט, סימן מים של מסגרת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>ממטב את חוויית המשתמש של כדור העזר במצב לרוחב, כדי להבטיח שכדור העזר יישאר רחוק מהמצלמה הקדמית, ובכך מציע ממשק פשוט יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישומי מערכת">
<feature>ניתן להקליט צלילי מערכת במהלך שיחות וידאו או שיחות קוליות לפי הצורך. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל: 'הגדרות' > 'תכונות נגישות' > 'הקלטת מסך' > 'השתמש בצלילי מערכת בעת הקלטה'.
שלוש רמות רזולוציה (480P/720P/1080P) זמינות לאיכות וידאו בהקלטות מסך. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל: 'הגדרות' > 'תכונות נגישות' > 'הקלטת מסך' > 'איכות וידאו'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מרחב מועדפים">
<feature>ממטב את החלקות של אפקט התנועה ב'מרחב מועדפים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש לחיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.
‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מאפשר לערוך סימני מים, וממטב את חוויית המשתמש של כדור העזר. בנוסף, ניתן להקליט צלילי מערכת ושלוש רמות רזולוציה זמינות להקלטות מסך. אימות משתמש נדרש לחיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את החלקות של אפקט התנועה בשורת מצב וב'מרחב מועדפים', ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="שורת מצב">
<feature>מגדיל את גודל הטקסט ומבליט את הסמלים כדי להקל על זיהוי המידע.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להוסיף ולהסיר סימני מים לפי הצורך. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל: 'צלם תמונה' > 'פתח את התמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'סימן מים' > אפשרויות 'סימן מים': מקור, סימן מים של טקסט, סימן מים של מסגרת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>ממטב את חוויית המשתמש של כדור העזר במצב לרוחב, כדי להבטיח שכדור העזר יישאר רחוק מהמצלמה הקדמית, ובכך מציע ממשק פשוט יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישומי מערכת">
<feature>ניתן להקליט צלילי מערכת במהלך שיחות וידאו או שיחות קוליות לפי הצורך. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל: 'הגדרות' > 'תכונות נגישות' > 'הקלטת מסך' > 'השתמש בצלילי מערכת בעת הקלטה'.
שלוש רמות רזולוציה (480P/720P/1080P) זמינות לאיכות וידאו בהקלטות מסך. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל: 'הגדרות' > 'תכונות נגישות' > 'הקלטת מסך' > 'איכות וידאו'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מרחב מועדפים">
<feature>ממטב את החלקות של אפקט התנועה ב'מרחב מועדפים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש לחיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.
‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の更新によって、ウォーターマークの編集が可能になり、アシストボールのユーザー体験が最適化されます。また、システムサウンドの録音が可能になり、スクリーン録画で3段階の解像度を利用できるようになります。USB接続にはユーザー認証が必要になります。また、今回のリリースではステータスバーとお気に入りスペースでのモーション効果のスムーズさが最適化され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。更新することをおすすめします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ステータスバー">
<feature>文字サイズを大きくして、アイコンを太字にすることで、情報を認識しやすくなります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ギャラリー">
<feature>ウォーターマークを自由に追加したり削除したりできるようになりました。この機能は、写真を撮影 > 写真を開く > [編集] > [ウォーターマーク] > [ウォーターマークの選択肢]（オリジナル、テキストウォーターマーク、フレームウォーターマーク）に移動して体験することができます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="マルチウィンドウ">
<feature>横表示モードでのアシストボールのユーザー体験が最適化され、アシストボールをインカメラに近づけないようにすることで、インターフェースがよりシンプルになります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システムアプリ">
<feature>テレビ電話や音声通話中のシステムサウンドの録音を自由に行えます。[設定] > [ユーザー補助機能] > [スクリーン録画] > [システムサウンドから録音]に移動して試してみてください。
スクリーン録画でビデオ画質の3段階の解像度（480P/720P/1080P）が利用できるようになります。[設定] > [ユーザー補助機能] > [スクリーン録画] > [ビデオ画質]に移動して試してみてください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="お気に入りスペース">
<feature>お気に入りスペースでのモーション効果のスムーズさが最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>USB接続の際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。[写真を転送]または[ファイルを転送/Android Auto]を選択すると、認証プロンプトまたはセキュリティプロンプトが表示され、より安全なデータ転送が確保されます。
システムセキュリティのために、Androidセキュリティパッチ（2024年10月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება იძლევა წყლის ნიშნების რედაქტირების საშუალებას და ახდენს დამხმარე ბურთის მუშაობის ოპტიმიზებას. გარდა ამისა, შესაძლებელია სისტემის ხმის ჩაწერა და ეკრანის ჩანაწერებისთვის ხელმისაწვდომია გარჩევადობის სამი დონე. USB კავშირისთვის საჭიროა მოხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. აღნიშნული გამოცემა ასევე ახდენს სტატუსის ზოლში და რჩეულების სივრცეში მოძრაობის ეფექტის შეუფერხებლობის ოპტიმიზებას და შემოაქვს უსაფრთხოების შესწორება. განახლება რეკომენდებულია.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სტატუსის ზოლი">
<feature>ზრდის ტექსტის ზომას და ამუქებს პიქტოგრამებს, რომ ინფორმაცია მარტივად ამოსაცნობი იყოს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გალერეა">
<feature>წყლის ნიშნები ახლა სურვილისამებრ შეგიძლიათ დაამატოთ და ამოშალოთ. ამის გამოცდა შეგიძლიათ შემდეგი გზით: ფოტოს გადაღება > ფოტოს გახსნა > რედაქტირ. > წყლის ნიშანი > წყლის ნიშნის ოფციები: ორიგინალი, ტექსტური წყლის ნიშანი, ჩარჩო-წყლის ნიშანი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მულტიფანჯარა">
<feature>ახდენს პეიზაჟის რეჟიმში დამხმარე ბურთის მუშაობის ოპტიმიზებას – უზრუნველყოფს, რომ დამხმარე ბურთი დარჩეს წინა კამერისგან მოშორებით, რაც გაცილებით ამარტივებს ინტერფეისს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემის აპები">
<feature>სურვილისამებრ, ვიდეო ან ხმოვანი ზარების დროს შეგიძლიათ ჩაწეროთ სისტემის ხმა. ამის გამოცდა შეგიძლიათ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > ხელმისაწვდომობის ფუნქციები > ეკრანის ჩანაწერი > სისტემის ხმიდან ჩაწერა.
ეკრანის ჩანაწერებში ვიდეოს ხარისხისთვის ხელმისაწვდომია გარჩევადობის სამი დონე (480P/720P/1080P). მისი გამოცდა შეგიძლიათ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > ხელმისაწვდომობის ფუნქციები > ეკრანის ჩანაწერი > ვიდეოს ხარისხი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="რჩეულების სივრცე">
<feature>ახდენს რჩეულების სივრცეში მოძრაობის ეფექტის შეუფერხებლობის ოპტიმიზებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>USB კავშირისთვის საჭიროა მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. როცა ირჩევთ ფოტოების გადაცემას ან ფაილების გადაცემას/Android Auto-ს, მონაცემთა გადაცემის უსაფრთხოების უზრუნველსაყოფად ჩნდება დადასტურების ან უსაფრთხოების შემოწმების მოთხოვნა.
სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ოქტომბერი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту су таңбаларын өңдеуге мүмкіндік береді және көмекші шардың пайдаланушы тәжірибесін оңтайландырады. Сондай-ақ жүйе дыбысын жазуға болады және экран жазбалары үшін үш ажыратымдылық деңгейі қолжетімді. USB байланысы үшін пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым күй жолағындағы және Таңдаулылар кеңістігіндегі қозғалыс әсерінің бірқалыптылығын оңтайландырады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жаңарту ұсынылады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Күй жолағы">
<feature>Ақпаратты тануды жеңілдету үшін мәтін өлшемін үлкейтеді және белгішелерді қалыңдатады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Енді су таңбаларын қалауыңызша қосуға және жоюға болады. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көруіңізге болады: «Фотосурет түсіру» > «Фотосуретті ашу» > «Өңдеу» > «Су таңбасы» > «Су таңбасы опциялары: Түпнұсқа, Мәтіннің су таңбасы, Жақтау су таңбасы».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бірнеше терезе">
<feature>Альбом режимінде көмекші шардың пайдаланушы тәжірибесін оңтайландырып, көмекші шардың алдыңғы камерадан алшақ болуын қамтамасыз етеді, осылайша қарапайым интерфейсті ұсынады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе қолданбалары">
<feature>Жүйе дыбысын қалауыңызша бейне немесе дауыстық қоңыраулар кезінде жазуға болады. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Арнайы мүмкіндіктер» > «Экранды жазу» > «Жүйе дыбысынан жазу».
Экран жазбаларында бейне сапасы үшін үш ажыратымдылық деңгейі (480P/720P/1080P) қолжетімді. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Арнайы мүмкіндіктер» > «Экранды жазу» > «Бейне сапасы».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Таңдаулылар кеңістігі">
<feature>Таңдаулылар кеңістігіндегі қозғалыс әсерінің бірқалыптылығын оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>USB байланысы үшін пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Деректерді қауіпсіз тасымалдауды қамтамасыз ететін «Фотосуреттерді тасымалдау» немесе «Файлдарды тасымалдау/Android Auto» параметрін таңдаған кезде растау немесе қауіпсіздік сұрауы пайда болады.
Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қазан, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យកែរូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត និងធ្វើឱ្យបទពិសោធអ្នកប្រើដុំជំនួយប្រសើរឡើង។ លើសពីនេះ សំឡេងប្រព័ន្ធអាចថតបាន ហើយកម្រិតគុណភាពបង្ហាញបីមានសម្រាប់ការថតអេក្រង់។ តម្រូវឱ្យធ្វើការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់ភាពត្រឹមត្រូវរបស់អ្នកប្រើសម្រាប់ការតភ្ជាប់តាម USB។ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះក៏ធ្វើឱ្យភាពរលូននៃបែបផែនចលនាប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងរបារស្ថានភាព និងលំហសំណព្វ និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។ សូមណែនាំឱ្យធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="របារ​ស្ថានភាព">
<feature>បង្កើនទំហំអត្ថបទ និងធ្វើឱ្យរូបតំណាងដិត ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យព័ត៌មានកាន់តែងាយស្រួលចំណាំ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="វិចិត្រសាល">
<feature>ឥឡូវ អាចបញ្ចូល និងយករូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតចេញតាមការចង់បាន។ អ្នកអាចទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ថតរូប > បើករូបថត > កែ > រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត > ជម្រើសរូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត៖ ដើម, រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតជាអក្សរ, រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតជាស៊ុម។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ពហុវិនដូ">
<feature>ធ្វើឱ្យបទពិសោធអ្នកប្រើដុំជំនួយប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងម៉ូដផ្ដេក ដែលធានាថា ដុំជំនួយបន្តនៅឆ្ងាយពីកាមេរ៉ា​មុខ ដូច្នេះផ្ដល់ផ្ទៃកាន់តែសាមញ្ញ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កម្មវិធីប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>អ្នកអាចថតសំឡេងប្រព័ន្ធក្នុងអំឡុងការហៅទូរស័ព្ទជាវីដេអូ ឬសំឡេងតាមការចង់បាន។ សាកល្បងប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > មុខងារភាពងាយស្រួលប្រើប្រាស់ > ការថតអេក្រង់ > ថតពីសំឡេងប្រព័ន្ធ។
កម្រិតគុណភាពបង្ហាញបី (480P/720P/1080P) មានសម្រាប់គុណភាពវីដេអូនៅក្នុងការថតអេក្រង់។ សាកល្បងប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > មុខងារភាពងាយស្រួលប្រើប្រាស់ > ការថតអេក្រង់ > គុណភាពវីដេអូ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="លំហសំណព្វ">
<feature>ធ្វើឱ្យភាពរលូននៃបែបផែនចលនាប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងលំហសំណព្វ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>តម្រូវឱ្យធ្វើការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់ភាពត្រឹមត្រូវរបស់អ្នកប្រើសម្រាប់ការតភ្ជាប់តាម USB។ សារតម្រុយផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់ ឬសារតម្រុយសន្តិសុខមួយបង្ហាញ នៅពេលអ្នកជ្រើសរើស "ផ្ទេររូបថត" ឬ "ផ្ទេរ​ឯកសារ / Android Auto" ដែលធានាបាននូវការផ្ទេរទិន្នន័យដែលកាន់តែមានសុវត្ថិភាព។
បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (តុលា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಸಹಾಯಕ ಚೆಂಡಿನ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಧ್ವನಿಯನ್ನು ರೆಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್‍‍ಗಾಗಿ ಮೂರು ರೆಸಲ್ಯೂಶನ್ ಮಟ್ಟಗಳು ಲಭ್ಯವಿವೆ. USB ಸಂಪರ್ಕಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿದೆ. ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ ಮತ್ತು ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಸ್ಪೇಸ್‍‍ನಲ್ಲಿ ಮೋಷನ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ನ ಸ್ಮೂಥ್‌ನೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಹ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ನೀವು ನವೀಕರಿಸಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ">
<feature>ಪಠ್ಯದ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿ ಗುರುತಿಸಲು ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಬೋಲ್ಡ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ">
<feature>ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಈಗ ನೀವು ಬಯಸಿದಂತೆ ಸೇರಿಸಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ತೆಗೆದುಹಾಕಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನೀವು ಇದರ ಅನುಭವ ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು: ಫೋಟೋ ತೆಗೆದುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ > ಫೋಟೋ ತೆರೆಯಿರಿ > ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಿ > ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್ > ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್ ಆಯ್ಕೆಗಳು: ಮೂಲ, ಪಠ್ಯ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್, ಫ್ರೇಮ್ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮಲ್ಟಿ-ವಿಂಡೋ">
<feature>ಲ್ಯಾಂಡ್‌ಸ್ಕೇಪ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಸಹಾಯಕ ಚೆಂಡಿನ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಸಹಾಯಕ ಚೆಂಡು ಮುಂಭಾಗದ ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾದಿಂದ ದೂರವಿರುವುದನ್ನು ಇದು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಈ ಮೂಲಕ ಸರಳವಾದ ಇಂಟರ್ಫೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಆ್ಯಪ್‍‍ಗಳು">
<feature>ನೀವು ಬಯಸಿದಂತೆ ವೀಡಿಯೊ ಅಥವಾ ಧ್ವನಿ ಕರೆಗಳ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಧ್ವನಿಯನ್ನು ರೆಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಪ್ರವೇಶಾರ್ಹತೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳು > ಪರದೆ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್ > ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಧ್ವನಿಯಿಂದ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಮಾಡಿ.
ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ವೀಡಿಯೊ ಗುಣಮಟ್ಟಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ಮೂರು ರೆಸಲ್ಯೂಶನ್ ಹಂತಗಳು (480P/720P/1080P) ಲಭ್ಯವಿವೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಪ್ರವೇಶಾರ್ಹತೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳು > ಪರದೆ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್ > ವೀಡಿಯೊ ಗುಣಮಟ್ಟ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಸ್ಪೇಸ್">
<feature>ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಸ್ಪೇಸ್‍‍ನಲ್ಲಿ ಚಲನೆಯ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ನ ಸ್ಮೂಥ್‌ನೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ಗಾಗಿ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ಫೋಟೋಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ ಅಥವಾ ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ / Android Auto ಎಂಬುದನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಿದಾಗ ಪರಿಶೀಲನೆ ಅಥವಾ ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ರಾಂಪ್ಟ್ ಕಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಡೇಟಾ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.
Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಅಕ್ಟೋಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트를 통해 워터마크 편집이 가능해졌으며, 도우미 볼의 사용자 경험을 최적화할 수 있게 되었습니다. 또한 시스템 사운드를 녹음할 수 있으며 화면 녹화를 위해 세 가지 해상도 레벨을 사용할 수 있습니다. USB 연결 시에는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 이번 릴리스에서는 상태 표시줄과 즐겨찾기 공간의 모션 효과의 부드러움을 최적화하고 보안 패치도 적용했습니다. 업데이트하는 것이 좋습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="상태 표시줄">
<feature>텍스트 크기를 늘리고 아이콘을 굵게 표시하여 정보를 더 쉽게 알아볼 수 있도록 합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="갤러리">
<feature>이제 워터마크를 원하는 대로 추가하고 제거할 수 있습니다. 사진 촬영 > 사진 열기 > 편집 > 워터마크 > 워터마크 옵션: 원본, 텍스트 워터마크, 프레임 워터마크로 이동하여 직접 체험해 보실 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="멀티 윈도우">
<feature>가로 모드에서 어시스턴트 볼의 사용자 경험을 최적화하여 어시스턴트 볼이 전면 카메라에서 멀어지도록 하여 더 간단한 인터페이스를 제공합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템 앱">
<feature>원하는 대로 영상 통화 또는 음성 통화 중에 시스템 사운드를 녹음할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 접근성 기능 > 화면 녹화 > 시스템 사운드에서 녹음으로 이동하여 사용해 보십시오.
화면 녹화에서 비디오 화질은 세 가지 해상도 수준(480P/720P/1080P)을 사용할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 접근성 기능 > 화면 녹화 > 비디오 화질로 이동하여 사용해 보십시오.</feature>
</features>
<features module="즐겨찾기 공간">
<feature>즐겨찾기 공간에서 모션 효과의 부드러움을 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>USB 연결 시에는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 사진 전송 또는 파일 전송/Android Auto를 선택하면 인증 또는 보안 메시지가 표시되어 더욱 안전하게 데이터를 전송할 수 있습니다.
시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 10월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ແ​ກ້​ໄຂ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ ແລະ ປັບ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້ລູກບອ​ລ​ຊ່ວຍ​ເຫຼືອ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ. ນອກ​ຈາກ​ນີ້, ​ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກສຽງ​ລະ​ບົບ ແລະ ມີລະ​ດັບ​ຄວາມ​ລະ​ອຽດ 3 ລະ​ດັບ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ລັບ​ການ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ. ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້ສຳ​ລັບການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວ​ນີ້​ຍັງ​ປັບ​ຄວາມ​ລຽບ​ນຽນ​ຂອງ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມໃນ​ແຖບ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ ແລະ Favorites Space ແລະ ລ​ວ​ມ​ເອົາ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ. ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ອັບ​ເດດ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແຖບສະຖານະ">
<feature>ເພີ່ມ​ຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ ແລະ ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ເປັນ​ຕົວ​ໜາ ເພື່ອ​ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ຮັບ​ຮູ້​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ໄດ້​ງ່າຍ​ຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແກເລີຣີ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້​ສາ​ມາດ​ເພີ່ມ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ ແລະ ເອົາ​ອອກໄດ້​ຕາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການ. ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ > ເປີດ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ > ແກ້​ໄຂ > ລາຍ​​ນ້ຳ > ຕົວ​ເລືອກ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ: ຕົ້ນ​ສະ​ບັບ, ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ, ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ກອບ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຫຼາຍໜ້າ​ຈໍ">
<feature>​ປັບ​ປະສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ຂອງ​ໝາກບານ​ຊ່ວຍ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ແນວ​ນອນ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ, ​ເຊິ່ງຮັບປະກັນ​ໃຫ້​ໝາກບານ​ຊ່ວຍ​ຢູ່​ຫ່າງ​ຈາກ​ກ້ອງ​ໜ້າ,​ ​ເຊິ່ງ​ໃຫ້​ສ່ວນ​ຕໍ່​ປະສານ​ທີ່​ງ່າຍກວ່າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແອັບ​ລະ​ບົບ">
<feature>ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກສຽງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ໃນ​ລະ​ຫວ່າງການ​ໂທວິ​ດີ​ໂອ ຫຼື ການ​ໂທ​ສຽງ​ຕາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການ​ໄດ້. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ການເຂົ້າເຖິງໄດ້ > ການບັນທຶກ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ > ບັນ​ທຶກ​ຈາກ​ສຽງ​ລະ​ບົບ.
ສາມ​ລະ​ດັບ​ຄວາມ​ລະ​ອຽດ (480P/720P/1080P) ສາ​ມາດ​ໃຊ້​ໄດ້​ສຳ​ລັບ​ຄຸນ​ນະ​ພາບ​ວິ​ດີ​ໂອ​ໃນ​ການ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ການເຂົ້າເຖິງໄດ້ > ການບັນທຶກ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ > ຄຸນ​ນະ​ພາບ​ວິ​ດີ​ໂອ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>ປັບ​ຄວາມ​ຄ່ອງ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ເອັບ​ເຟັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ໃນ​ Favorites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ຈໍ​າ​ເປັນ​ຕ້ອງ​ມີ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ສຳລັບການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ການກວດ​ສອບ ຫຼື ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ປະ​ກົດຂຶ້ນ​ເມື່ອ​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ ໂອນຍ້າຍ​ຮູບ ຫຼື ໂອນຍ້າຍ​ໄຟ​ລ໌ / Android ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ, ເຊິ່ງ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ການ​ໂອນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ທີ່​ປອດ​ໄພ​ກວ່າ.
ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ຕຸ​ລາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo naujiniu leidžiama redaguoti vandens ženklus ir optimizuojama pagalbinio kamuoliuko naudojimo patirtis. Be to, galima įrašyti sistemos garsą, o ekrano vaizdo įrašams galimi trys skyros lygiai. Norint prisijungti per USB jungtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Šioje laidoje taip pat optimizuojamas judesio efekto sklandumas būsenos juostoje ir parankinių erdvėje bei įtraukiama saugumo pataisa. Rekomenduojama atnaujinti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Būsenos juosta">
<feature>Padidinamas tekstas ir paryškinamos piktogramos, kad būtų lengviau atpažinti informaciją.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nuo šiol galima pagal pageidavimą įtraukti ir šalinti vandens ženklus. Tai galite išbandyti taip: padarykite nuotrauką, atverkite nuotrauką ir eikite į „Redaguoti > Vandens ženklas > Vandens ženklo parinktys“ („Originalas“, „Tekstinis vandens ženklas“, „Vandens ženklas rėmelyje“).</feature>
</features>
<features module="Daugialangis režimas">
<feature>Optimizuojama pagalbinio kamuoliuko naudojimo patirtis horizontaliuoju režimu, užtikrinant, kad pagalbinis kamuoliukas būtų atokiau nuo priekinės kameros. Taip supaprastinama sąsaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sisteminės programėlės">
<feature>Pageidaujant vaizdo arba garso pokalbių metu galima įrašyti sistemos garsą. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pritaikymo neįgaliesiems funkcijos > Ekrano vaizdo įrašymas > Įrašymas iš sistemos garso“.
Ekrano vaizdą galima įrašyti vienu iš trijų skyros lygių (480p / 720p / 1080p). Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pritaikymo neįgaliesiems funkcijos > Ekrano vaizdo įrašymas > Vaizdo įrašo kokybė“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Parankinių erdvė">
<feature>Optimizuojamas judesio efekto sklandumas parankinių erdvėje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Norint prisijungti per USB, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Pasirinkus „Persiųsti nuotraukas“ arba „Persiųsti failus („Android Auto“)“, pateikiamas patvirtinimo arba saugumo raginimas, užtikrinantis saugesnį duomenų persiuntimą.
Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. spalio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu var rediģēt ūdenszīmes un optimizēt palīgbumbu lietošanas iespējas. Turklāt var ierakstīt sistēmas skaņu, un ekrāna ierakstiem ir pieejami trīs izšķirtspējas līmeņi. USB savienojumam ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Šis laidiens arī optimizē kustības efekta vienmērīgumu statusa joslā un sadaļā Izlases vieta, un tajā ir iekļauts drošības ielāps. Ieteicams atjaunināt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusa josla">
<feature>Palielina teksta izmēru un izveido ikonas treknrakstā, lai informācija būtu vieglāk atpazīstama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Tagad ūdenszīmes var pievienot un noņemt pēc vēlēšanās. Varat to izbaudīt, atverot: Uzņemt fotoattēlu > Atvērt fotoattēlu > Rediģēt > Ūdenszīme > Ūdenszīmes opcijas: Sākotnējais, Teksta ūdenszīme, Rāmja ūdenszīme.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vairāki logi">
<feature>Optimizē palīgbumbas lietošanas iespējas ainavas režīmā, nodrošinot, ka palīgbumba atrodas tālāk no priekšējās kameras, tādējādi piedāvājot vienkāršāku interfeisu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēmas lietotnes">
<feature>Video vai balss zvanu laikā pēc vajadzības varat ierakstīt sistēmas skaņu. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Pieejamības funkcijas > Ekrāna ieraksts > Ierakstīt no sistēmas skaņas.
Ekrāna ierakstu video kvalitātei ir pieejami trīs izšķirtspējas līmeņi (480P/720P/1080P). Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Pieejamības funkcijas > Ekrāna ieraksts > Video kvalitāte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Izlases vieta">
<feature>Optimizē kustības efekta vienmērīgumu sadaļā Izlase vieta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>USB savienojumam ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Izvēloties Pārsūtīt fotoattēlus vai Pārsūtīt failus/Android Auto, tiek parādīta verifikācijas vai drošības uzvedne, garantējot drošāku datu pārsūtīšanu.
Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada oktobris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट वाटरमार्क केँ संपादित करबाक अनुमति दैत अछि आओर सहायक बॉल केर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, सिस्टम साउंड केँ रिकॉर्ड कयल जा सकैत अछि आओर स्क्रीन रिकॉर्डिंग सभक लेल तीनटा रिजॉल्यूशन स्तर उपलब्ध अछि। USB कनेक्शनक लेल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। ई रिलीज स्थिति बार आ पसिन्नगर स्पेस मे मोशन प्रभाव केर सहजता केँ अनुकूलित सेहो करैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि। अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति बार">
<feature>जानकारी केँ आसानी सँ पहिचान करबाक लेल टेक्स्टक आकार बढ़बैत अछि आओर आइकन सभ केँ बोल्ड करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>वाटरमार्क सभ केँ आब सुविधानुसार जोड़ल आ हटाओल जा सकैत अछि। अहाँ एहि मे जा कए एकरा अनुभव कए सकैत छी: एकटा फोटो लिअ > फोटो खोलू > संपादित करू > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्क विकल्प सभ: मूल, टेक्स्ट वाटरमार्क, फ्रेम वाटरमार्क।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>सहायक बॉल केँ फ्रंट कैमरा सँ दूर रहब सुनिश्चित करबाक लेल, लैंडस्केप मोड मे सहायक बॉल केर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, जाहि सँ एकटा साधारण इंटरफेस प्रस्तुत कयल जा सकए।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम एप सभ">
<feature>वीडियो वा वॉयस कॉल सभक दरमियान अहाँ सिस्टम साउंड केँ आवश्यकतानुसार रिकॉर्ड कए सकैत छी। एकरा एहि मे जा कए आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > एक्सेसिबिलिटी फीचर > स्क्रीन रिकॉर्ड भ रहल अछि > सिस्टम साउंड सँ रिकॉर्ड करू।
स्क्रीन रिकॉर्ड भ रहल अछि मे वीडियो गुणवत्ता केर लेल तीनटा रिजॉल्यूशन स्तर (480P/720P/1080P) उपलब्ध अछि। एकरा एहि मे जा कए आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > एक्सेसिबिलिटी फीचर > स्क्रीन रिकॉर्ड भ रहल अछि > वीडियो गुणवत्ता।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पसिन्नगर स्पेस">
<feature>पसिन्नगर स्पेस मे मोशन प्रभाव केर सहजता केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन केर लेल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। जखन अहाँ फोटो सभ ट्रांसफर करू वा फाइल सभ / Android ऑटो ट्रांसफर करू चुनैत छी, तखन एकटा सत्यापन वा सुरक्षा संकेत देखाय पड़ैत अछि, जाहि सँ सुरक्षित डेटा ट्रांसफर सुनिश्चित होइत अछिॆ।
सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टू 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, mā tēnei whakahōu e taea ai te whakatika i ngā tohuwai, ā, ka arotau i te wheako kaiwhakamahi o te pōro āwhina. Tērā anō, ka taea te whakapūkete i te oro pūnaha, ā, e toru ngā taumata taumira e wātea ana mō ngā hopukanga mata. E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi mō te tūhononga USB. Ka arotautia hoki e tēnei putanga te māeneene o te pānga nekeneke ki te pae tūnga me te Mokowā ngā Makau, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. E tūtohutia ana kia whakahōu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pae tūnga">
<feature>Ka whakanui ake i te rahi kuputuhi, ā, ka taekaha hoki i ngā ata kia māmā ake ai te mōhio ki ngā mōhiohio.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Taiwhanga">
<feature>Ināianei ka taea te tāpiri me te tango i ngā Tohuwai e hiahiatia ana. Ka taea e koe te wheako mā te haere: Tangohia tētahi whakaahua > Te whakatuwhera i te whakaahua > Whakatika i > Tohuwai> Ngā kōwhiringa Tohuwai: Tūturu, Tohuwai kuputuhi, Tohuwai tāpare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matapihi-Maha">
<feature>Ka arotautia ai te wheako kaiwhakamahi o te pōro āwhina i roto i te aratau horanuku, me whakarite kia noho mamao atu te pōro āwhina i te kāmera o mua, mā reira e tuku ana i tētahi atanga māmā ake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā taupānga pūnaha">
<feature>Ka taea e koe te tāhopu oro pūnaha i te wā e hiahiatia ana ngā waea ataata, reo rānei. Whakamātauria mā te haere: Ngā tautuhinga > Ngā āhuahira urutanga > Tuhi mata > Tāhopu mai i te oro pūnaha.
E toru ngā taumata taumira (480P/720P/1080P) e wātea ana mō te kounga ataata i ngā tuhi mata. Whakamātauria mā te haere: Ngā tautuhinga > Ngā āhuahira urutanga > Tuhi mata > Kounga ataata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mokowā ngā Makau">
<feature>Ka arotautia ai te māeneene o te pānga nekeneke i te Mokowā ngā Makau.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi mō te tūhononga USB. Ka puta mai tētahi manatokonga, tohuāki haumarutanga rānei ina tīpako koe i Whakawhiti whakaahua, i Whakawhitia ngā kōnae / Android Auto, me te whakarite i te whakawhiti raraunga haumaru ake.
Kua whakaurua te āpure haumarutanga Android (Oketopa 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање овозможува да се уредуваат водните знаци и го оптимизира корисничкото искуство со помошна топка. Дополнително, може да се снима звукот од системот и достапни се три нивоа на резолуцијата за снимањата на екранот. Потребна е автентикација од корисникот за поврзување преку USB. Ова издание исто така ја оптимизира глаткоста на ефектот на движење во статусната лента и Простор за омилени и вградува безбедносна крпеница. Се препорачува да оптимизирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Статусна лента">
<feature>Големината на текстот се зголемува и иконите за задебелуваат за да биде полесно препознавањето на информациите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерија">
<feature>Водните знаци сега може да се додаваат и отстрануваат како што се посакува. Искусете преку одење во: Направете фотографија > Отворете ја фотографијата > Уреди > Воден знак > Опции за воден знак: Оригинал, Воден знак со текст, Воден знак со рамка.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Повеќе прозорци">
<feature>Го оптимизира корисничкото искуство на помошна топка во режим на пејзаж, со што се осигурува дека помошната топка останува подалеку од предната камерата и се нуди поедноставен интерфејс.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Системски апликации">
<feature>Може да снимате звук од системот за време на видеоповици или говорни повици, како што се посакува. Пробајте преку одење во: Нагодување > Карактеристики за пристапност > Снимка од екранот > Снимај од звукот на системот.
Достапни се три нивоа на резолуција (480P/720P/1080P) за квалитет на видеото во снимања на екранот. Пробајте преку одење во: Нагодување > Карактеристики за пристапност > Снимка од екранот > Квалитет на видео.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Простор за омилени">
<feature>Ја оптимизира глаткоста на ефектот на движење во Простор за омилени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Потребна е автентикација од корисникот за поврзување преку USB. Се појавува укажување за потврдување или безбедносно укажување кога ќе изберете Пренос на фотографии или Пренос на датотеки / Android Auto, со што се осигурува побезбеден пренос на податоци.
Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (октомври 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за Ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് വാട്ടർമാർക്കുകൾ എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ അനുവദിക്കുകയും അസിസ്റ്റീവ് ബോളിന്റെ ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, സിസ്റ്റം ശബ്‌ദം റെക്കോർഡ് ചെയ്യാനുമാകും, സ്‌ക്രീൻ റെക്കോർഡിംഗുകൾക്കായി മൂന്ന് റെസലൂഷൻ ലെവലുകൾ ലഭ്യമാണ്. USB കണക്ഷനായി ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടതുണ്ട്. കൂടാതെ, ഈ റിലീസ് സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാറിലെയും ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ് സ്‌പെയ്‌സിലെയും ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റിന്റെ അനായാസത ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ">
<feature>വിവരങ്ങൾ എളുപ്പത്തിൽ തിരിച്ചറിയുന്നതിനായി ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് വലുപ്പം വർദ്ധിപ്പിക്കുകയും ഐക്കണുകൾ ബോൾഡാക്കുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഗാലറി">
<feature>ഇപ്പോൾ വാട്ടർമാർക്കുകൾ ഇഷ്‌ടാനുസൃതം ചേർക്കാനും നീക്കംചെയ്യാനും കഴിയും. നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയാം: ഒരു ഫോട്ടോ എടുക്കുക > ഫോട്ടോ തുറക്കുക > എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക > വാട്ടർമാർക്ക് > വാട്ടർമാർക്ക് ഓപ്‌ഷനുകൾ: ഒറിജിനൽ, ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് വാട്ടർമാർക്ക്, ഫ്രെയിം വാട്ടർമാർക്ക്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മൾട്ടി-വിൻഡോ">
<feature>ലാൻഡ്‌സ്‌കേപ്പ് മോഡിൽ അസിസ്റ്റീവ് ബോളിന്റെ ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു, അസിസ്റ്റീവ് ബോൾ മുൻ ക്യാമറയിൽ നിന്ന് അകന്ന് നിൽക്കുന്നത് ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നതിലൂടെ ഒരു ലളിതമായ ഇന്റർഫേസ് നൽകുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം ആപ്പുകൾ">
<feature>വീഡിയോ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ ശബ്‌ദ കോളുകൾക്കിടെ താൽപ്പര്യാനുസരണം സിസ്റ്റം ശബ്‌ദം റെക്കോർഡ് ചെയ്യാവുന്നതാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ആക്സസബിലിറ്റി സവിശേഷതകൾ > സ്ക്രീൻ റെക്കോർഡിംഗ് > സിസ്റ്റം ശബ്‌ദത്തിൽ നിന്ന് റെക്കോർഡ് ചെയ്യുക.
സ്‌ക്രീൻ റെക്കോർഡിംഗുകളിൽ വീഡിയോ നിലവാരത്തിനായി മൂന്ന് റെസലൂഷൻ ലെവലുകൾ (480P/720P/1080P) ലഭ്യമാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ആക്സസബിലിറ്റി സവിശേഷതകൾ > സ്ക്രീൻ റെക്കോർഡിംഗ് > വീഡിയോ നിലവാരം.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ് സ്‌പെയ്‌സ്">
<feature>ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ് സ്‌പെയ്‌സിലെ ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റിന്റെ അനായാസത ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>USB കണക്ഷനായി ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടതുണ്ട്. നിങ്ങൾ 'ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈമാറുക' അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 'ഫയലുകൾ കൈമാറുക / Android Auto' എന്നത് തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുമ്പോൾ ഒരു പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സുരക്ഷാ നിർദ്ദേശം ദൃശ്യമാകുന്നു, ഇത് സുരക്ഷിതമായ ഡാറ്റാ കൈമാറ്റം ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നു.
സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഒക്‌ടോബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр усан тэмдгийг засахыг зөвшөөрч, туслах бөмбөлгийн хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг оновчлов. Түүнчлэн системийн дууг бичих боломжтой болж, дэлгэцийг гурван нягтралын түвшинтэй бичих боломжтой боллоо. USB холболтод хэрэглэгчийн бататгалыг шаарддаг болсон. Энэ шинэчлэлтээр мөн төлөвийн мөр, Favorites Space-н хөдөлгөөний нөлөөний жигд байдлыг оновчилж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаав. Шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Төлөвийн мөр">
<feature>Бичвэрийн хэмжээг томруулж, шигтгээ зургийг тодруулсан тул мэдээллийг илүү хялбар таних боломжтой боллоо.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерей">
<feature>Усны тэмдгийг одоо хүссэнээрээ нэмж, арилгаж болно. Үүнийг Зураг авах > Зургийг нээх > Засах > Усан тэмдэг > Усан тэмдгийн сонголт руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү: Эх хувилбар, Бичвэрийн усан тэмдэг, Хүрээний усан тэмдэг.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Олон цонх">
<feature>Хөндлөн горимд туслах бөмбөлгийн хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг оновчилсноор туслах бөмбөг урд камераас зайтай болж, интерфейсийг илүү хялбарчиллаа.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Системийн апликэйшн">
<feature>Видео болон энгийн дуудлагын үеэр хүссэнээрээ системийн дууг бичих боломжтой боллоо. Тохиргоо > Хялбар ашиглалт > Дэлгэцийн бичлэг > Системийн дуунаас бичих рүү очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.
Дэлгэцийн бичлэгийн видеоны чанарыг гурван түвшний нягтралтай (480P/720P/1080P) гаргах боломжтой болов. Тохиргоо > Хялбар ашиглалт > Дэлгэцнээс бичлэг хийх > Видео чанар луу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Favorites Space-н хөдөлгөөний нөлөөний жигд байдлыг оновчлов.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>USB холболтод хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардана. Өгөгдлийн аюулгүй дамжуулалтыг нягтлах үүднээс таныг Зургуудыг дамжуулах эсвэл Файл шилжүүлэх/Андройд автоматыг сонгох үед баталгаажуулах эсвэл аюулгүй байдлын сануулга гарч ирнэ.
Системийн аюулгүй байдлын үүднээс Андройдын хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны 10-р сар) багтаав. HONOR Хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаарх нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 вэбсайтад зочилно уу</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन वॉटरमार्क्स संपादित करण्याची अनुमती देते आणि सहाय्यक बॉलचा वापरकर्ता अनुभव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते. याव्यतिरिक्त, सिस्टम आवाज रेकॉर्ड केला जाऊ शकतो आणि स्क्रीन रेकॉर्डिंग्जसाठी तीन रिझोल्यूशन स्तर उपलब्ध आहेत. USB कनेक्शनसाठी वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. हे रिलीझ स्टेटस बार आणि फेव्हरेट स्पेसमध्ये मोशन प्रभावाची सहजता देखील ऑप्टिमाइझ करते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते. अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्टेटस बार">
<feature>माहिती ओळखणे सोपे करण्यासाठी मजकूराचा आकार वाढवते आणि चिन्हे ठळक करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गॅलरी">
<feature>वॉटरमार्क्स आता जोडले जाऊ शकतात आणि हवे तसे काढले जाऊ शकतात. येथे जाऊन आपण त्याचा अनुभव घ्या: फोटो घ्या > फोटो उघडा > संपादित करा > वॉटरमार्क > वॉटरमार्क पर्याय: मूळ, मजकूर वॉटरमार्क, फ्रेम वॉटरमार्क.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>लँडस्केप मोडमध्ये सहाय्यक बॉलचा वापरकर्ता अनुभव ऑप्टिमाइझ करतो, सहाय्यक बॉल समोरच्या कॅमेरापासून दूर राहतो याची खात्री करतो, ज्यामुळे एक सोपा इंटरफेस मिळतो.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम अ‍ॅप्स">
<feature>आपण आपल्या व्हिडिओ किंवा व्हॉईस कॉल्स दरम्यान सिस्टम आवाज रेकॉर्ड करू शकता. येथे जाऊन हे वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुलभता वैशिष्ट्ये > स्क्रीन रेकॉर्डिंग > सिस्टमच्या आवाजावरून रेकॉर्ड करा.
स्क्रीन रेकॉर्डिंग्जमध्ये व्हिडिओच्या गुणवत्तेसाठी तीन रिझोल्यूशन स्तर (480P/720P/1080P) उपलब्ध आहेत. येथे जाऊन हे वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुलभता वैशिष्ट्ये > स्क्रीन रेकॉर्डिंग > व्हिडिओची गुणवत्ता.</feature>
</features>
<features module="फेव्हरेट स्पेस">
<feature>फेव्हरेट स्पेसमध्ये मोशन प्रभावाची सहजता ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>USB कनेक्शनसाठी वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. आपण सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरणाची खात्री करून, फोटोज स्‍थानांतरित करा किंवा फाइल्स / Android स्वयं स्‍थानांतरित करा निवडता तेव्हा पडताळणी किंवा सुरक्षितता सूचना दिसून येते.
सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (ऑक्टो 2024) समाविष्ट केला गेला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini membolehkan tera air diedit dan mengoptimumkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan. Selain itu, bunyi sistem boleh dirakam dan tiga tahap resolusi tersedia untuk rakaman skrin. Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan untuk sambungan USB. Keluaran ini juga mengoptimumkan kelancaran kesan pergerakan dalam bar status dan Ruang Kegemaran serta memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Anda disyorkan agar mengemas kini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bar status">
<feature>Besarkan saiz teks dan tebalkan ikon untuk menjadikan maklumat lebih mudah dikenal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tera air kini boleh ditambahkan dan dikeluarkan seperti yang dikehendaki. Anda boleh mencuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tera air > Pilihan tera air: Asal, Tera air teks, Tera air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multitetingkap">
<feature>Optimumkan pengalaman pengguna bola bantuan dalam mod landskap, memastikan bola bantuan jauh daripada kamera hadapan, dengan itu menawarkan antara muka yang lebih mudah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi sistem">
<feature>Anda boleh merakam bunyi sistem semasa panggilan video atau suara seperti yang dikehendaki. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Kebolehaksesan > Rakaman skrin > Rakam daripada bunyi sistem.
Tiga tahap resolusi (480P/720P/1080P) tersedia untuk kualiti video dalam rakaman skrin. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Kebolehaksesan > Rakaman skrin > Kualiti video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ruang Kegemaran">
<feature>Optimumkan kelancaran kesan pergerakan dalam Ruang Kegemaran.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan untuk sambungan USB. Pengesahan atau gesaan keselamatan muncul apabila anda memilih Pindahkan foto atau Pindahkan fail / Auto Android, demi memastikan pemindahan data yang lebih selamat.
Tampalan keselamatan Android (Okt 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် ရေစာများကို တည်းဖြတ်နိုင်စေပြီး အထောက်အကူပြုဘောလုံး သုံးစွဲရသည့်အတွေ့အကြုံကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။ ထို့အပြင် စနစ်အသံကို မှတ်တမ်းတင်နိုင်ပြီး မျက်နှာပြင် မှတ်တမ်းများအတွက် ပုံရိပ်ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု အဆင့်သုံးခုကို အသုံးပြုနိုင်သည်။ USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှုအတွက် သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်သည် Favorites Space နှင့် အခြေအနေပြဘားတွင် လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကိုလည်း ချောမွေ့အောင် အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကိုလည်း ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အခြေအနေပြဘား">
<feature>စာလုံး အရွယ်အစားကို ကြီးမားအောင်လုပ်ပေးထားပြီး အိုင်ကွန်များကို စာလုံးမည်းပေးထားသဖြင့် အချက်အလက်များကို ပိုမိုလွယ်ကူစွာ သိရှိနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံပြခန်း">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ရေစာများကို ဆန္ဒရှိသလို ထည့်နိုင် ဖယ်ရှားနိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြထားသည့်အတိုင်းသွား၍ ၎င်းကို သုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်- ဓာတ်ပုံရိုက်မည် > ဓာတ်ပုံ ဖွင့်မည် > တည်းဖြတ်မည် > ရေစာ > ရေစာ ရွေးချယ်မှုများ- မူရင်း၊ စာသားရေစာ၊ ဖရိန် ရေစာ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>အလျားလိုက်စနစ်တွင် အထောက်အကူပြုဘောလုံး သုံးစွဲရသည့်အတွေ့အကြုံကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးပြီး အထောက်အကူပြုဘောလုံးကို ရှေ့ကင်မရာနှင့် ဝေးရာတွင် ထားပေးသဖြင့် ကြားခံစနစ်ကို ပို၍ရှင်းလင်းစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ် အက်ပ်များ">
<feature>ဗီဒီယို သို့မဟုတ် အသံဖြင့် ခေါ်ဆိုမှုများပြုလုပ်စဉ် စနစ်အသံကို ဆန္ဒရှိသလို မှတ်တမ်းတင်နိုင်သည်။ ဆက်တင် > အထောက်အကူပြု လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ > မျက်နှာပြင် မှတ်တမ်း > စနစ်အသံမှ မှတ်တမ်းတင်ရန်သို့ သွား၍ ၎င်းကို စမ်းသုံးကြည့်ပါ။
မျက်နှာပြင် မှတ်တမ်းတင်ရာတွင် ဗီဒီယို အရည်အသွေးအတွက် ပုံရိပ်ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု အဆင့်သုံးခု (480P/720P/1080P) ရရှိနိုင်သည်။ ဆက်တင် > အထောက်အကူပြု လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ > မျက်နှာပြင် မှတ်တမ်း > ဗီဒီယို အရည်အသွေးသို့ သွားပြီး ၎င်းကို စမ်းသုံးကြည့်ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Favorites Space တွင် လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို ချောမွေ့အောင် အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှုအတွက် သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဓာတ်ပုံများ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် သို့မဟုတ် ဖိုင်များ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် / Android Auto ကို ရွေးချယ်ပါက အတည်ပြုမှု သို့မဟုတ် လုံခြုံရေး ညွှန်ကြားချက် ပေါ်လာပြီး ဒေတာ လွှဲပြောင်းမှုကို ပို၍လုံခြုံစေသည်။
စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (အောက်တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေးအပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း အချက်အလက်များ ပိုမိုသိရှိလိုပါက ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ် https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ ေရစာမ်ားကို တည္းျဖတ္ႏိုင္ေစၿပီး အေထာက္အကူျပဳေဘာလုံး သုံးစြဲရသည့္အေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ စနစ္အသံကို မွတ္တမ္းတင္ႏိုင္ၿပီး မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ မွတ္တမ္းမ်ားအတြက္ ပုံရိပ္ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ အဆင့္သုံးခုကို အသုံးျပဳႏိုင္သည္။ USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈအတြက္ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္သည္ Favorites Space ႏွင့္ အေျခအေနျပဘားတြင္ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကိုလည္း ေခ်ာေမြ႕ေအာင္ အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကိုလည္း ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အေျခအေနျပဘား">
<feature>စာလုံး အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ႀကီးမားေအာင္လုပ္ေပးထားၿပီး အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို စာလုံးမည္းေပးထားသျဖင့္ အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ပိုမိုလြယ္ကူစြာ သိရွိႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံျပခန္း">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ေရစာမ်ားကို ဆႏၵရွိသလို ထည့္ႏိုင္ ဖယ္ရွားႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပထားသည့္အတိုင္းသြား၍ ၎ကို သုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္- ဓာတ္ပုံ႐ိုက္မည္ > ဓာတ္ပုံ ဖြင့္မည္ > ျပင္ဆင္မည္ > ေရစာ > ေရစာ ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္မႈမ်ား- မူရင္း၊ စာသားေရစာ၊ ဖရိန္ ေရစာ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>အလ်ားလိုက္စနစ္တြင္ အေထာက္အကူျပဳေဘာလုံး သုံးစြဲရသည့္အေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးၿပီး အေထာက္အကူျပဳေဘာလုံးကို ေရွ႕ကင္မရာႏွင့္ ေဝးရာတြင္ ထားေပးသျဖင့္ ၾကားခံစနစ္ကို ပို၍ရွင္းလင္းေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္ အက္ပ္မ်ား">
<feature>ဗီဒီယို သို႔မဟုတ္ အသံျဖင့္ ေခၚဆိုမႈမ်ားျပဳလုပ္စဥ္ စနစ္အသံကို ဆႏၵရွိသလို မွတ္တမ္းတင္ႏိုင္သည္။ ဆက္တင္ > အေထာက္အကူျပဳ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား > မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ မွတ္တမ္း > စနစ္အသံမွ မွတ္တမ္းတင္ရန္သို႔ သြား၍ ၎ကို စမ္းသုံးၾကည့္ပါ။
မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ မွတ္တမ္းတင္ရာတြင္ ဗီဒီယို အရည္အေသြးအတြက္ ပုံရိပ္ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ အဆင့္သုံးခု (480P/720P/1080P) ရရွိႏိုင္သည္။ ဆက္တင္ > အေထာက္အကူျပဳ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား > မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ မွတ္တမ္း > ဗီဒီယို အရည္အေသြးသို႔ သြားၿပီး ၎ကို စမ္းသုံးၾကည့္ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Favorites Space တြင္ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို ေခ်ာေမြ႕ေအာင္ အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈအတြက္ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ပုံမ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ဖိုင္မ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ / Android Auto ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္ပါက အတည္ျပဳမႈ သို႔မဟုတ္ လုံၿခဳံေရး ၫႊန္ၾကားခ်က္ ေပၚလာၿပီး ေဒတာ လႊဲေျပာင္းမႈကို ပို၍လုံၿခဳံေစသည္။
စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ေအာက္တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရးအပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း အခ်က္အလက္မ်ား ပိုမိုသိရွိလိုပါက ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne oppdateringen gjør det mulig å redigere vannmerker og optimaliserer brukeropplevelsen med assisterende kule. I tillegg kan systemlyden tas opp, og tre oppløsningsnivåer for skjermopptak er tilgjengelig. Brukerautentifisering påkreves for USB-tilkobling. Denne utgivelsen optimaliserer også glattheten av bevegelseseffekt i statuslinjen og Favorites Space, samt integrerer en sikkerhetsoppdatering. Det anbefales å oppdatere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statuslinje">
<feature>Øker tekststørrelsen og fremhever ikonene for å gjøre informasjonen lettere å gjenkjenne.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vannmerker kan nå legges til og fjernes etter ønske. Du kan oppleve det ved å gå til: Ta et bilde > Åpne bildet > Rediger > Vannmerke > Vannmerke-alternativer: Original, Tekstvannmerke, Vannmerkestripe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flere vinduer">
<feature>Optimaliserer brukeropplevelsen for assisterende kule i landskapsmodus, noe som sikrer at den assisterende kulen holdes borte fra frontkameraet, dermed tilbys en enklere overflate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systemapper">
<feature>Du kan ta opp systemlyd i løpet av video- eller taleanrop etter eget ønske. Prøv den ut ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Tilgjengelighetsfunksjoner > Skjerminnspilling > Ta opp fra systemlyd.
Tre bildeoppløsingsnivåer (480 p / 720 p / 1080 p) er tilgjengelige for videokvalitet i skjermopptak. Prøv ut ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Tilgjengelighetsfunksjoner > Skjerminnspilling > Videokvalitet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Optimerer glattheten til bevegelseseffekten i Favorites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Brukerbekreftelse kreves for USB-tilkobling. En bekreftelse eller sikkerhetsmelding dukker opp når du velger Overfør bilder eller Overfør filer / Android Auto sikrer dermed tryggere dataoverføring.
Android sikkerhetsoppdatering (okt. 2024) har blitt integrert for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om HONOR Sikkerhet-oppdateringer, se vårt nettsted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले वाटरमार्कहरू सम्पादन गर्न अनुमति दिन्छ, र सहायक बलको प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभवलाई अनुकूल पार्छ । यसका साथै, प्रणालीको ध्वनि रेकर्ड गर्न सकिन्छ र स्क्रिन रेकर्डिङका लागि तीन रिजोलुसन स्तरहरू उपलब्ध छन् । USB जडानका लागि प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । यो रिलिजले स्थिति पट्टीमा मोसनको प्रभावको सहजता र मनपर्नेहरू स्पेस पनि अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ । अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति पट्टी">
<feature>यसले पाठको आकार बढाउँछ र जानकारी सजिलै पहिचान गर्न सकियोस् भन्नाका लागि आइकनहरू बोल्ड बनाउँछ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्यालरी">
<feature>अबदेखि आफ्नो इच्छाअनुसार वाटरमार्क हाल्न र हटाउन सकिन्छ । तपाईं यहाँ गएर यसको अनुभव लिन सक्नुहुन्छ: फोटो खिच्नुहोस् > फोटो खोल्नुहोस् > सम्पादन गर्नुहोस् > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्कसम्बन्धी विकल्पहरू: मौलिक, पाठको वाटरमार्क, फ्रेमको वाटरमार्क ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="बहु-विन्डो">
<feature>सहायतामूलक बलले अगाडिको क्यामेरा छेक्दैन भन्ने कुरा सुनिश्चित गर्दै ल्यान्डस्केप मोडमा सहायतामूलक बलको प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र यसले गर्दा इन्टरफेस सरल हुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणालीका एपहरू">
<feature>तपाईं भिडियो वा भ्वाइस कलका बेला इच्छाअनुसार प्रणालीका साउन्ड रेकर्ड गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > उपलब्धता सुविधाहरू > स्क्रिन रेकर्डिङ > प्रणालीको साउन्डबाट रेकर्ड गर्नुहोस् ।
स्क्रिन रेकर्डिङ गर्दा भिडियोको गुणस्तरका रूपमा रिजोलुसनका तीन स्तर (480P/720P/1080P) उपलब्ध हुन्छन् । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > उपलब्धता सुविधाहरू > स्क्रिन रेकर्डिङ > भिडियोको गुणस्तर ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मनपर्नेहरू स्पेस">
<feature>मनपर्नेहरू स्पेसमा मोसन प्रभावको सहजता अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>USB जडानका लागि प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । तपाईंले फोटोहरू स्थानान्तरण गर्नुहोस् वा फाइल स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् / एन्ड्रोइड अटो चयन गर्नुभयो भने प्रमाणीकरण वा सुरक्षा प्रम्प्ट देखिने छ ।
एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अक्टोबर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update maakt het mogelijk om watermerken te bewerken en optimaliseert de gebruikerservaring van de hulpbal. Bovendien kan systeemgeluid worden opgenomen en zijn er drie resolutieniveaus beschikbaar voor schermopnamen. Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist voor USB-verbinding. Deze release optimaliseert ook de soepelheid van het bewegingseffect in de statusbalk en Favorietenruimte en bevat een beveiligingspatch. Het wordt aanbevolen om bij te werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusbalk">
<feature>Vergroot de tekstgrootte en maakt de pictogrammen vet om de informatie gemakkelijker herkenbaar te maken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Foto's">
<feature>Watermerken kunnen nu naar wens worden toegevoegd en verwijderd. U kunt het ervaren via: Een foto maken > De foto openen > Bewerken > Watermerk > Watermerkopties: Origineel, Tekstwatermerk, Framewatermerk.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multivenster">
<feature>Optimaliseert de gebruikerservaring van de hulpbal in landschapsmodus en zorgt ervoor dat de hulpbal uit de buurt van de camera aan de voorzijde blijft, waardoor een eenvoudigere interface wordt geboden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeemapps">
<feature>U kunt naar wens systeemgeluid opnemen tijdens video- of spraakoproepen. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Toegankelijkheidsfuncties > Schermopname > Opnemen vanaf systeemgeluid.
Er zijn drie resolutieniveaus (480p/720p/1080p) beschikbaar voor videokwaliteit in schermopnamen. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Toegankelijkheidsfuncties > Schermopname > Videokwaliteit.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorietenruimte">
<feature>Optimaliseert de soepelheid van het bewegingseffect in Favorietenruimte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist voor USB-verbinding. Er verschijnt een verificatie- of beveiligingsprompt wanneer u Foto's overdragen of Bestanden overdragen / Android Auto selecteert, wat zorgt voor een veiligere gegevensoverdracht.
Android-beveiligingspatch (oktober 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କଗୁଡିକ ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରିବାକୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ, ଏବଂ ସହାୟକ ବଲ୍‌ର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତି ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ଧ୍ୱନି ରେକର୍ଡ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ ଏବଂ ତିନି ରିଜୋଲ୍ୟୁସନ୍ ସ୍ତର ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ରେକର୍ଡିଂଗୁଡ଼ିକରେ ଉପଲବ୍ଧ। USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ପାଇଁ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌ ଏବଂ ମନପସନ୍ଦ ସ୍ପେସ୍‌ରେ ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବର ସ୍ମୁଦନେସ୍ ମଧ୍ୟ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌">
<feature>ସୂଚନାକୁ ସହଜରେ ଚିହ୍ନଟ କରାଇବାକୁ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍‌ ଆକାରକୁ ବଢାଏ ଏବଂ ଆଇକନ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ବୋଲ୍ଡ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ">
<feature>ନିଜ ମନ ଅନୁସାରେ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ ଯୋଡ଼ାଯାଇ ପାରିବ କିମ୍ବା ଅପସାରଣ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ନିମ୍ନଲିଖିତକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନେଇପାରିବେ: ଏକ ଫଟୋ ଉଠାନ୍ତୁ > ଫଟୋ ଖୋଲନ୍ତୁ > ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରନ୍ତୁ > ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ > ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ ବିକଳ୍ପସମୂହ: ମୂଳ, ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ, ଫ୍ରେମ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମଲ୍ଟି-ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ">
<feature>ସହାୟକ ବଲ୍ ସମ୍ମୁଖ କ୍ୟାମେରାରୁ ଦୂରେଇ ରହିବା ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି, ଲ୍ୟାଣ୍ଡସ୍କେପ୍‌ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ ସହାୟକ ବଲ୍‌ର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତି ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, ଯାହା ଏକ ସରଳ ଇଣ୍ଟରଫେସ୍ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ଆପସ୍‌">
<feature>ଆପଣ ମନ ଅନୁସାରେ ଭିଡ଼ିଓ କିମ୍ବା ଭଏସ୍‌ କଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଚାଲୁଥିବା ବେଳେ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ଧ୍ୱନି ରେକର୍ଡ କରିପାରିବେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ପ୍ରବେଶଯୋଗ୍ୟ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ > ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ରେକର୍ଡିଂ > ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ଧ୍ୱନିରୁ ରେକର୍ଡ କରନ୍ତୁ।
ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ରେକର୍ଡିଂରେ ଭିଡ଼ିଓର ଗୁଣବତ୍ତା ପାଇଁ ତିନୋଟି ରିଜୋଲ୍ୟୁସନ୍ ସ୍ତର (480P/720P/1080P) ଉପଲବ୍ଧ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ପ୍ରବେଶଯୋଗ୍ୟ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ > ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ରେକର୍ଡିଂ > ଭିଡ଼ିଓ ଗୁଣବତ୍ତା।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମନପସନ୍ଦ ସ୍ପେସ୍">
<feature>ମନପସନ୍ଦ ସ୍ପେସ୍‌ରେ ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବର ସ୍ମୁଦନେସ୍ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ପାଇଁ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଆପଣ ଫଟୋଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରନ୍ସଫର୍ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ / Android Auto ଚୟନ କରିବା ବେଳେ, ନିରାପଦ ଡାଟା ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି ଏକ ଯାଞ୍ଚ କିମ୍ବା ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ରମ୍ପଟ୍‌ ଦେଖାଯଏ।
ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅକ୍ଟୋବର 2024) ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੋਧ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾ ਸਕਦੀ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਬਾਲ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਧੁਨੀ ਨੂੰ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ ਅਤੇ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗਾਂ ਲਈ ਤਿੰਨ ਰੈਜ਼ੋਲੂਸ਼ਨ ਪੱਧਰ ਉਪਲਬਧ ਹਨ। USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਲਈ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਲੋੜੀਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ ਅਤੇ ਮਨਪਸੰਦ ਥਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਦੀ ਨਿਰਵਿਘਨਤਾ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕੀਤੇ ਜਾਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ">
<feature>ਟੈਕਸਟ ਆਕਾਰ ਨੂੰ ਵਧਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਪਛਾਣਨਾ ਆਸਾਨ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਗੂੜ੍ਹਾ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਗੈਲਰੀ">
<feature>ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹੁਣ ਲੋੜ ਅਨੁਸਾਰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਅਤੇ ਹਟਾਇਆ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇਸਦਾ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ: ਇੱਕ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਖਿੱਚੋ > ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਖੋਲ੍ਹੋ > ਸੋਧੋ > ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ > ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ ਵਿਕਲਪ: ਮੂਲ, ਟੈਕਸਟ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ, ਫ੍ਰੇਮ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮਲਟੀ-ਵਿੰਡੋ">
<feature>ਲੈਂਡਸਕੇਪ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਬਾਲ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਇਹ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਜਾਂਦਾ ਹੈ ਕਿ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਬਾਲ ਫ੍ਰੰਟ ਕੈਮਰੇ ਤੋਂ ਦੂਰ ਰਹਿੰਦੀ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਇੱਕ ਸਰਲ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾਂਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ ਐਪਾਂ">
<feature>ਤੁਸੀਂ ਲੋੜ ਅਨੁਸਾਰ ਵੀਡੀਓ ਜਾਂ ਵੌਇਸ ਕਾਲਾਂ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਨੂੰ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਪਹੁੰਚਣਯੋਗਤਾ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ > ਸਕਰੀਨ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗ > ਸਿਸਟਮ ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਤੋਂ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਕਰੋ।
ਸਕਰੀਨ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਵੀਡੀਓ ਕੁਆਲਿਟੀ ਲਈ ਤਿੰਨ ਰੈਜ਼ੋਲੂਸ਼ਨ ਪੱਧਰ (480P/720P/1080P) ਉਪਲਬਧ ਹਨ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਪਹੁੰਚਣਯੋਗਤਾ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ > ਸਕਰੀਨ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗ > ਵੀਡੀਓ ਕੁਆਲਿਟੀ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮਨਪਸੰਦ ਥਾਂ">
<feature>ਮਨਪਸੰਦ ਥਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਦੀ ਨਿਰਵਿਘਨਤਾ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਲਈ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਡੇਟਾ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ, ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ / Android Auto ਨੂੰ ਚੁਣਦੇ ਹੋ ਤਾਂ ਇੱਕ ਤਸਦੀਕ ਜਾਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪ੍ਰੌਂਪਟ ਦਿਖਾਈ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।
ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਕਤੂਬਰ 2024) ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Drogi użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja wprowadza możliwość edycji znaków wodnych oraz optymalizuje funkcje połączeń oraz komfort użytkowania podręcznej ikony kuli. Ponadto można nagrywać dźwięk systemowy, a do nagrań ekranu dostępne są trzy poziomy rozdzielczości. Do połączenia USB jest wymagane uwierzytelnienie użytkownika. Ta wersja optymalizuje również płynność efektu ruchu na pasku stanu i w Przestrzeni ulubionych oraz zawiera poprawkę bezpieczeństwa. Zaleca się zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pasek stanu">
<feature>Zwiększono rozmiar tekstu i pogrubiono ikony, aby poprawić czytelność informacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Można już swobodnie dodawać i usuwać znaki wodne. W tym celu: zrób zdjęcie > otwórz zdjęcie > Edytuj > Znak wodny > Opcje znaku wodnego: Oryginalny, Tekstowy znak wodny, Znak wodny w formie ramki.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Wiele okien">
<feature>Optymalizuje komfort użytkowania podręcznej ikony kuli tak, że kula nie pojawia się przy aparacie przednim, tym samym oferując prostszy interfejs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacje systemowe">
<feature>Dźwięk systemowy można nagrywać podczas połączeń wideo lub głosowych. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając: Ustawienia > Funkcje ułatwień dostępu > Nagrywanie ekranu > Nagrywaj dźwięk systemowy.
Dostępne są trzy poziomy rozdzielczości (480p/720p/1080p) wideo w nagraniach ekranu. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając: Ustawienia > Funkcje ułatwień dostępu > Nagrywanie ekranu > Jakość wideo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Przestrzeń ulubionych">
<feature>Zoptymalizowano płynność efektu ruchu w Przestrzeni ulubionych.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Wymagane jest uwierzytelnienie użytkownika do nawiązania połączenia USB. Monit o weryfikację lub monit dotyczący bezpieczeństwa pojawia się po wybraniu opcji Przenosić zdjęcia lub Przenosić pliki / Android Auto, zapewniając bezpieczniejszy transfer danych.
Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (październik 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro(a) usuário(a), esta atualização permite que marcas d'água sejam editadas e otimiza a experiência de usuário da bola de assistência. Além disso, o som do sistema pode ser gravado e três níveis de resolução estão disponíveis para gravações de tela. A autenticação do usuário é necessária para a conexão USB. Esta versão também otimiza a suavidade do efeito de movimento na barra de status e no Espaço de favoritos, além de incorporar um patch de segurança. Recomenda-se a atualização.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de status">
<feature>Aumenta o tamanho do texto e coloca os ícones em negrito para facilitar o reconhecimento das informações.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>As marcas d'água agora podem ser adicionadas e removidas conforme desejado. Você pode experimentar acessando: Tirar uma foto > Abrir a foto > Editar > Marca d'água > Opções de marca d'água: Original, Marca d'água de texto, Marca d'água do quadro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Várias janelas">
<feature>Otimiza a experiência de usuário do círculo de assistência no modo paisagem, garantindo que a bola assistida fique longe da câmera frontal, oferecendo assim uma interface mais simples.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicativos do sistema">
<feature>Você pode gravar o som do sistema durante chamadas de vídeo ou voz, conforme desejado. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Recursos de acessibilidade > Gravação de tela > Gravar som do sistema.
Três níveis de resolução (480p/720p/1080p) estão disponíveis para qualidade de vídeo em gravações de tela. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Recursos de acessibilidade > Gravação de tela > Qualidade de vídeo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espaço de favoritos">
<feature>Otimiza a suavidade do efeito de movimento no Espaço de favoritos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>A autenticação do usuário é necessária para conexão USB. Um aviso de verificação ou segurança aparece quando você seleciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir arquivos/Android Auto, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.
O patch de segurança do Android (outubro de 2024) foi incorporado para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização permite a edição de marcas de água e otimiza a experiência de utilização da esfera de assistência. Além disso, o som do sistema pode ser gravado e estão disponíveis três níveis de resolução para as gravações de ecrã. A autenticação do utilizador é necessária para a ligação USB. Esta versão também otimiza a suavidade do efeito de movimento na barra de estado e no Espaço Favoritos e incorpora uma correção de segurança. Recomenda-se a atualização.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta o tamanho do texto e realça os ícones para tornar a informação mais fácil de reconhecer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>As marcas de água podem agora ser adicionadas e removidas conforme pretendido. Experimente, acedendo a: Tirar uma fotografia > Abrir a fotografia > Editar > Marca de água > Opções da Marca de água: Original, Marca de água de texto, Marca de água na moldura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijanela">
<feature>Otimiza a experiência do utilizador da esfera de assistência no modo panorâmico, assegurando que a esfera de assistência se mantém afastada da câmara frontal, conferindo assim uma interface mais simples.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicações do sistema">
<feature>Pode gravar o som do sistema durante chamadas de vídeo ou de voz conforme desejado. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Funcionalidades de acessibilidade > Gravar ecrã > Registar a partir do som do sistema.
Estão disponíveis três níveis de resolução (480P/720P/1080P) para a qualidade de vídeo nas gravações de ecrã. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Funcionalidades de acessibilidade > Gravar ecrã > Qualidade de vídeo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espaço Favoritos">
<feature>Otimiza a suavidade do efeito de movimento no Espaço Favoritos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>É necessária a autenticação do utilizador para a ligação USB. É apresentado um comando de verificação ou segurança ao selecionar Transferir fotografias ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.
Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (outubro de 2024) para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare permite editarea inscripționărilor și optimizează experiența de utilizare a sferei de asistență. În plus, poate fi înregistrat sunetul sistemului și sunt disponibile trei niveluri de rezoluție pentru înregistrările de ecran. Este necesară autentificarea utilizatorului pentru utilizarea conexiunii USB. Această versiune optimizează, de asemenea, nivelul de fluiditate al efectului de mișcare pentru bara de stare și meniul Spațiu favorite și încorporează o corecție de securitate. Se recomandă instalarea acestei actualizări.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bară de stare">
<feature>Mărește dimensiunea textului și accentuează pictogramele pentru a face informațiile mai ușor de recunoscut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Inscripționările pot fi acum adăugate și eliminate după cum doriți. Această funcție o puteți încerca în următorul mod: faceți o fotografie > Deschideți fotografia > Editare > Inscripționare > Opțiuni inscripționare: Original, Inscripționare text, Inscripționare cadru.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ferestre multiple">
<feature>Optimizează experiența de utilizare a bilei de asistență în modul peisaj, asigurându-se că bila de asistență rămâne departe de camera frontală, oferind astfel o interfață mai simplă.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicații de sistem">
<feature>Puteți înregistra sunetul de sistem în timpul apelurilor video sau vocale, după cum doriți. Încercați funcția accesând: Setări > Funcții de accesibilitate > Înregistrare ecran > Înregistrare de la sunet de sistem.
Sunt disponibile trei niveluri de rezoluție (480P/720P/1080P) pentru calitatea videoclipului în înregistrările ecranului. Încercați funcția accesând: Setări > Funcții de accesibilitate > Înregistrare ecran > Calitatea videoclipului.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spațiu favorite">
<feature>Optimizează fluiditatea efectului de mișcare din Spațiu favorite.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Autentificarea utilizatorului este necesară pentru conexiunea USB. Atunci când selectați Transfer de fotografii sau Transferare fișiere / Android Auto apare o solicitare de verificare sau de securitate, asigurând un transfer de date mai sigur.
Corecția de securitate Android (octombrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea actualizării nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это обновление, чтобы добавить возможность редактирования водяных знаков, оптимизировать использование плавающей кнопки, добавить возможность записи системных звуков и три уровня разрешения при записи с экрана, добавить аутентификацию пользователя при подключении с помощью USB, оптимизировать плавность анимации движения в строке состояния и разделе «Избранные файлы», а также внедрить исправление безопасности. Рекомендуем вам установить это обновление.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Строка состояния">
<feature>Увеличен размер текста и добавлено выделение значков жирным шрифтом для более удобного распознавания.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Водяные знаки теперь можно добавлять и удалять. Для этого перейдите в раздел «Сделать снимок > Открыть фото > Изменить > Водяной знак > Параметры водяного знака»: «Оригинал», «Водяной знак с текстом», «Водяной знак в кадре».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Мультиоконный режим">
<feature>Улучшен интерфейс благодаря оптимизации взаимодействия с плавающей кнопкой в горизонтальном режиме, чтобы плавающая кнопка не загораживала фронтальную камеру.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Системные приложения">
<feature>Доступна запись системных звуков во время видеовызовов или голосовых вызовов. Для этого перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Специальные возможности > Запись с экрана > Запись системных звуков».
Для качества видео в записях экрана доступны три уровня разрешения (480P/720P/1080P). Перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Специальные возможности > Запись с экрана > Качество видео».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Избранные файлы">
<feature>Оптимизирована плавность анимации движения в разделе Избранные файлы.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>При подключении с помощью USB требуется аутентификация пользователя. При выборе режима «Передача фото», «Передача файлов/Android Auto» появляется запрос проверки или безопасности, что обеспечивает более безопасную передачу данных.
В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (октябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලය දිය සලකුණු සංස්කරණය කරනු ලැබීමට ඉඩ දෙන අතර සහ සහායක බෝලයේ පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි. අතිරේකව, පද්ධති ශබ්දය පටිගත කළ හැකිවනු ඇති අතර තිර පටිගත කිරීම් සඳහා විභේදන මට්ටම් තුනක් තිබේ. USB සම්බන්ධතාවය සඳහා පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. මෙම නිකුතුව තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩේ සහ ප්‍රියතමයන් ඉඩෙහි චලන ප්‍රයෝගයේ සුමට බව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි, සහ ආරක්ෂක පිළියමක් ඇතුළත් කරයි. යාවත් කරන්නට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ">
<feature>පාඨ විශාලත්වය ඉහළ නංවන අතර තොරතුරු හඳුනා ගැනීම වඩා පහසු කිරීමට අයිකන තද පැහැ කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ගැලරිය">
<feature>දැන් දිය සලකුණු අවශ්‍ය පරිදි එක් කිරීමට සහ ඉවත් කිරීමට හැකිවනු ඇත. ඔබට මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය අත්විඳින්නට හැකිවේ: ඡායාරූපයක් ගන්න > ඡායාරූපය විවෘත කරන්න > සංස්කරණය කරන්න > දිය සලකුණ > දිය සලකුණු විකල්ප: මුල්, පෙළ දිය සලකුණ, රාමු දිය සලකුණ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බහු කවුළුව">
<feature>සහායක බෝලය ඉදිරිපස කැමරාවෙන් බැහැරව සිටීම තහවුරු කරමින්, එමගින් වඩා සරල අතුරු මුහුණතක් ලබා දෙමින් තිරස් ප්‍රකාරයේ දී සහායක බෝලයේ පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධති යෙදුම්">
<feature>අපේක්ෂිත පරිදි වීඩියෝ හෝ කටහඬ ඇමතුම් අතරතුර ඔබට පද්ධති ශබ්දය පටිගත කළ හැකිවේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ප්‍රවේශ්‍යතා විශේෂාංග > තිර පටිගත කිරීම > පද්ධති ශබ්දයෙන් පටිගත කරන්න.
තිර පටිගත කිරීම්වල වීඩියෝ ගුණත්වය සඳහා විභේදන මට්ටම් තුනක් (480P/720P/1080P) තිබේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ප්‍රවේශ්‍යතා විශේෂාංග > තිර පටිගත කිරීම > වීඩියෝ ගුණාත්වය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ප්‍රියතමයන් ඉඩ">
<feature>ප්‍රියතමයන් ඉඩ තුළ චලන ප්‍රයෝගයේ සුමට බව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>USB සම්බන්ධතාවය සඳහා පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. ඔබ ඡායාරූප මාරු කරන්න හෝ ගොනු මාරු කරන්න / Android Auto තෝරාගත් විට, වඩා ආරක්ෂිත දත්ත මාරුව තහවුරු කරමින් සත්‍යාපන හෝ ආරක්ෂක ප්‍රේරණයක් දිස්වේ.
පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ඔක්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia umožňuje úpravu vodotlače a optimalizuje používateľskú skúsenosť s pomocnou guľôčkou. Okrem toho možno nahrávať systémový zvuk a pre záznamy obrazovky sú k dispozícii tri úrovne rozlíšenia. Pre pripojenie USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Toto vydanie tiež optimalizuje efekt plynulosti pohybu v stavovom riadku a v Priestore obľúbených a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizácia sa odporúča.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stavový riadok">
<feature>Zväčší veľkosť textu a zvýrazní ikony, aby sa informácie dali ľahšie rozpoznať.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Vodotlače možno pridávať a odstraňovať podľa potreby. Môžete to vyskúšať podľa tohto postupu: nasnímajte fotografiu > otvorte fotografiu > Upraviť > Vodotlač > Možnosti vodotlače: Originál, Textová vodotlač, Rámová vodotlač.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Viacero okien">
<feature>Optimalizuje používateľskú skúsenosť s pomocnou guľôčkou v režime na šírku. To zaručí, že pomocná guľôčka zostane ďaleko od predného fotoaparátu, čím ponúka jednoduchšie rozhranie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systémové aplikácie">
<feature>Počas videohovorov alebo hlasových hovorov môžete podľa potreby zaznamenávať systémový zvuk. Vyskúšajte si to v časti: Nastavenia > Funkcie uľahčenia prístupu > Záznam obrazovky > Záznam zo systémového zvuku.
Pre kvalitu videa v záznamoch obrazovky sú k dispozícii tri úrovne rozlíšenia (480P/720P/1080P). Vyskúšajte si to v časti: Nastavenia > Funkcie uľahčenia prístupu > Záznam obrazovky > Kvalita videa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Priestor obľúbených">
<feature>Optimalizuje efekt plynulosti pohybu v Priestore obľúbených.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Pre pripojenie USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Pri výbere možnosti Prenos fotografií alebo Prenos súborov/Android Auto sa zobrazí výzva na overenie alebo zabezpečenie, čím sa zaistí bezpečnejší prenos dát.
Obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu systému Android (okt. 2024) na zabezpečenie systému. Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev omogoča urejanje vodnih žigov in optimizira uporabniško izkušnjo kroglice za pomoč. Poleg tega je mogoče posneti sistemski zvok, za snemanje zaslona pa so na voljo tri ravni ločljivosti. Za uporabo povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ta izdaja tudi optimizira gladko delovanje učinka gibanja v vrstici stanja in Prostoru za priljubljene ter vključuje varnostni popravek. Priporočamo posodobitev.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vrstica stanja">
<feature>Povečana je velikost besedila in ikone so poudarjene za enostavnejše branje podatkov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodne žige je zdaj mogoče po želji dodati in odstraniti. Preizkusite jih na naslednji način: zajemite fotografijo > odprite fotografijo > Uredi > Vodni žig > Možnosti vodnega žiga so: Izvirna slika, Besedilni vodni žig, Vodni žig z okvirjem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Več oken">
<feature>Optimizira uporabniško izkušnjo kroglice za pomoč v ležečem načinu, saj zagotavlja, da se kroglica za pomoč ne približa sprednji kameri, kar omogoča enostavnejši vmesnik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistemske aplikacije">
<feature>Sistemski zvok lahko po želji posnamete med videoklici ali glasovnimi klici. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tukaj: Nastavitve > Funkcije za dostopnost > Snemanje zaslona > Snemaj z zvokom sistema.
Za kakovost videa pri snemanju zaslona so na voljo tri ravni ločljivosti (480p/720p/1080p). Preizkusite tukaj: Nastavitve > Funkcije za dostopnost > Snemanje zaslona > Kakovost videoposnetka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prostor za priljubljene">
<feature>Optimizira gladko delovanje učinka gibanja v vrstici stanja in Prostoru za priljubljene.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Za uporabo povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ko izberete možnost Prenos fotografij ali Prenos datotek/Android Auto, se prikaže poziv za preverjanje ali varnostni poziv, s tem pa je zagotovljen varnejši prenos podatkov.
Varnostni popravek za Android (oktober 2024) je vključen za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen gör det möjligt att redigera vattenstämplar och optimerar användarupplevelsen av hjälpboll. Dessutom kan systemljud spelas in och det finns tre upplösningsnivåer för skärminspelningar. Användarautentisering krävs för USB-anslutning. Den här utgåvan optimerar också rörelseeffektens jämnhet i statusfältet och Utrymme för favoriter samt implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering. Du rekommenderas att uppdatera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusfält">
<feature>Ökar textstorleken och visar ikonerna i fetstil så att informationen lättare kan kännas igen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vattenstämplar kan nu läggas till och tas bort efter önskemål. Du kan prova genom att gå till: Ta ett foto > Öppna fotot > Redigera > Vattenstämpel > Vattenstämpelalternativ: Original, Textvattenstämpel, Vattenstämpel med ram.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flera fönster">
<feature>Optimerar användarupplevelsen av hjälpboll i liggande läge, vilket gör att hjälpbollen försvinner från frontkameran och gränssnitt blir enklare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systemappar">
<feature>Du kan spela in systemljud under video- eller röstsamtal om så önskas. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Tillgänglighetsfunktioner > Skärminspelning > Spela in från systemljud.
Tre upplösningsnivåer (480p/720p/1080p) är tillgängliga för videokvalitet i skärminspelningar. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Tillgänglighetsfunktioner > Skärminspelning > Videokvalitet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utrymme för favoriter">
<feature>Optimerar rörelseeffektens jämnhet i Utrymme för favoriter.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Användarautentisering krävs för USB-anslutning. En verifierings- eller säkerhetsuppmaning visas när du väljer Överföra foton eller Överföra filer/Android Auto, vilket ger en säkrare dataöverföring.
Android-säkerhetskorrigering (oktober 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linawezesha alama fifi kuhaririwa na linaboresha uzoefu wa mtumiaji wa kitufe cha usaidizi. Pia, sauti ya mfumo inaweza kurekodiwa na viwango vitatu vya onyesho vinapatikana kwa ajili ya kurekodi skrini. Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika kwa ajili ya muunganisho wa USB. Toleo hili pia linaboresha ulaini wa hali ya mwendo kwenye upau wa hali na Nafasi ya Vipendwa na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama. Inapendekezwa usasishe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Upau wa hali">
<feature>Linaongeza ukubwa wa maandishi na linaongeza uzito wa aikoni ili kufanya kuwa rahisi kutambua maelezo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matunzio">
<feature>Alama fifi sasa zinaweza kuongezwa na kuondolewa kama upendavyo. Unaweza kuifurahia kwa kwenda kwenye: Piga picha > Fungua picha > Hariri > Alama fifi > Machaguo ya alama fifi: Asilia, Alama fifi ya maandishi, Alama fifi ya fremu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madirisha Kadhaa">
<feature>Linaboresha uzoefu wa mtumiaji wa kitufe cha usaidizi katika hali ya mkao mlalo, hivyo basi kuhakikisha kitufe cha usaidizi hakikaribii kamera ya mbele, hivyo basi kukupa kiolesura rahisi zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programu za mfumo">
<feature>Unaweza kurekodi sauti ya mfumo unapopiga simu za video au sauti kama upendavyo. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Vipengele vya zana za walemavu > Kurekodi skrini > Rekodi kutoka kwenye sauti ya mfumo.
Viwango vitatu vya mwonekano (480P/720P/1080P) vinapatikana kwa ajili ya ubora wa video katika rekodi za skrini. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Vipengele vya zana za walemavu > Kurekodi skrini > Ubora wa video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nafasi ya Vipendwa">
<feature>Huboresha ulaini wa athari ya mwendo katika Nafasi ya Vipendwa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitaji ili kubadilisha muunganisho wa USB. Kidokezo cha uthibitishaji au usalama hutokea ukichagua Hamisha picha au Hamisha faili/Android Otomatiki, hivyo basi kuhakikisha uhamishaji data salama zaidi.
Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Okt 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு வாட்டர்மார்க்குகளைத் திருத்த அனுமதிக்கிறது, உதவி பந்தின் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது. கூடுதலாக, சிஸ்டம் ஒலியைப் பதிவுசெய்ய முடியும் மற்றும் திரைப் பதிவுகளுக்கு மூன்று தெளிவுத்திறன் நிலைகள் கிடைக்கின்றன. USB இணைப்புக்குப் பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. இந்த வெளியீடு நிலைப் பட்டி மற்றும் பிடித்தவை ஸ்பேஸில் இயக்க விளைவின் மென்மையையும் உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பையும் கொண்டுள்ளது. இதைப் புதுப்பிக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="நிலைப் பட்டி">
<feature>தகவல்களை எளிதாக அடையாளம் காண, உரை அளவை அதிகரிக்கிறது மற்றும் ஐகான்களைத் தடிமனாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேலரி">
<feature>வாட்டர்மார்க்குகளை இப்போது விருப்பப்படி சேர்க்கலாம் மற்றும் அகற்றலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் நீங்கள் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்: புகைப்படம் எடு > புகைப்படத்தைத் திற > திருத்து > வாட்டர்மார்க் > வாட்டர்மார்க் விருப்பங்கள்: அசல், உரை வாட்டர்மார்க், ஃபிரேம் வாட்டர்மார்க்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பல சாளரம்">
<feature>லேண்ட்ஸ்கேப் பயன்முறையில் உதவிப் பந்தின் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, உதவிப் பந்து முன்புற கேமராவிலிருந்து விலகி இருப்பதை உறுதிசெய்கிறது, இதன் மூலம் எளிமையான இடைமுகத்தை வழங்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம் செயலிகள்">
<feature>நீங்கள் விரும்பியபடி வீடியோ அல்லது குரல் அழைப்புகளின்போது சிஸ்டம் ஒலியைப் பதிவு செய்யலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > அணுகல்திறன் அம்சங்கள் > திரையைப் பதிவுசெய்தல் > சிஸ்டம் ஒலியிலிருந்து பதிவுசெய்தல்.
திரைப் பதிவுகளில் வீடியோ தரத்திற்கு மூன்று தெளிவுத்திறன் நிலைகள் (480P/720P/1080P) உள்ளன. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > அணுகல்திறன் அம்சங்கள் > திரையைப் பதிவுசெய்தல் > வீடியோ தரம்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பிடித்தவை ஸ்பேஸ்">
<feature>பிடித்தவை ஸ்பேஸில் இயக்க விளைவின் மென்மையை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>USB இணைப்புக்குப் பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. பாதுகாப்பான தரவுப் பரிமாற்றத்தை உறுதிசெய்யும் வகையில், புகைப்படங்களைப் பரிமாற்று அல்லது கோப்புகளைப் பரிமாற்று / Android Auto என்பதைத் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கும்போது சரிபார்ப்பு அல்லது பாதுகாப்புத் தூண்டுதல் தோன்றும்.
சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (அக் 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ వాటర్‌మార్క్‌లను సవరించడానికి అనుమతిస్తుంది మరియు సహాయక బాల్ యొక్క వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది. అదనంగా, సిస్టమ్ ధ్వనులను రికార్డ్ చేయవచ్చు మరియు స్క్రీన్ రికార్డింగ్‌ల కోసం మూడు దృశ్య నాణ్యత స్థాయిలు అందుబాటులో ఉన్నాయి. USB కనెక్షన్ కోసం వినియోగదారు ప్రమాణీకరణ అవసరం. ఈ విడుదల స్టేటస్ బార్ మరియు ఇష్టాల స్పేస్‌లో మోషన్ ప్రభావం యొక్క సరళతను కూడా ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేసింది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ చేర్చబడింది. అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="స్టేటస్ బార్">
<feature>సమాచారాన్ని సులభంగా గుర్తించడానికి టెక్స్ట్ పరిమాణాన్ని పెంచుతుంది మరియు చిహ్నాలను బోల్డ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గ్యాలరీ">
<feature>వాటర్‌మార్క్‌లను ఇప్పుడు కావల్సిన విధంగా జోడించవచ్చు మరియు తీసివేయవచ్చు. మీరు దీనిని ఫోటో తీయండి > ఫోటోను తెరవండి > సవరించు > వాటర్‌మార్క్ > వాటర్‌మార్క్ ఎంపికలు: అసలు, టెక్స్ట్ వాటర్‌మార్క్, ఫ్రేమ్ వాటర్‌మార్క్ ఎంపికకు వెళ్లి ప్రయత్నించవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
<features module="బహుళ-విండో">
<feature>ల్యాండ్‌స్కేప్ మోడ్‌లో సహాయక బాల్ యొక్క వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది, దీని వలన సహాయక బాల్ ముందు కెమెరాకు దూరంగా ఉంటుంది మరియు సులభమైన ఇంటర్‌ఫేస్ లభిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్ అప్లికేషన్‌లు">
<feature>మీరు అవసరమైన విధంగా వీడియో లేదా వాయిస్ కాల్‌ల్లో సిస్టమ్ ధ్వనిని రికార్డ్ చేయవచ్చు. దీనిని ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > యాక్సెసబిలిటీ ఫీచర్‌లు > స్క్రీన్ రికార్డింగ్ > సిస్టమ్ ధ్వని నుండి రికార్డ్ చేయి.
స్క్రీన్ రికార్డింగ్‌లో వీడియో నాణ్యత కోసం మూడు దృశ్యనాణ్యతలు (480P/720P/1080P) అందుబాటులో ఉన్నాయి. వాటిని ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > యాక్సెసబిలిటీ ఫీచర్‌లు > స్క్రీన్ రికార్డింగ్ > వీడియో నాణ్యత.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ఇష్టాల స్పేస్">
<feature>ఇష్టాల స్పేస్‌లో మోషన్ ప్రభావం యొక్క సరళతను ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>USB కనెక్షన్ కోసం వినియోగదారు ప్రామాణీకరణ అవసరం. మీరు ఫోటోలను బదిలీ చేయండి లేదా ఫైల్స్ బదిలీ చేయి / Android Autoను ఎంచుకున్నప్పుడు, సురక్షితమైన డేటా బదిలీని నిర్ధారించడానికి ఒక ధృవీకరణ లేదా భద్రతా ప్రాంప్ట్ కనిపిస్తుంది.
Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (అక్టో 2024) అనేది సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రతా అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా ఈ వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้อนุญาตให้แก้ไขลายน้ำ และปรับปรุงประสบการณ์การใช้งานลูกบอลช่วยเหลือ นอกจากนี้คุณจะสามารถบันทึกเสียงจากระบบและจะมีความละเอียดสามระดับให้ใช้สำหรับการบันทึกหน้าจอ และจำเป็นต้องใช้การเชื่อมต่อ USB สำหรับการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้ นอกจากนี้การอัปเดตครั้งนี้จะปรับปรุงความลื่นไหลของเอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวในแถบการค้นหาและพื้นที่รายการโปรด และรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย เราขอแนะนำให้คุณทำการอัปเดต</feature>
</features>
<features module="แถบสถานะ">
<feature>เพิ่มขนาดข้อความ และทำให้ไอคอนหนาขึ้น เพื่อให้รับรู้ข้อมูลได้ง่ายดายยิ่งขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="แกลเลอรี">
<feature>เพิ่มและลบลายน้ำออกได้ตามต้องการ คุณสามารถสัมผัสประสบการณ์ได้โดยไปที่: ถ่ายภาพ > เปิดภาพถ่าย > แก้ไข > ลายน้ำ > ตัวเลือกลายน้ำ: ต้นฉบับ, ลายน้ำข้อความ, ลายน้ำที่เป็นกรอบรูป</feature>
</features>
<features module="หลายหน้าต่าง">
<feature>เพิ่มประสบการณ์การใช้งานลูกบอลช่วยเหลือในโหมดแนวนอน ทำให้ลูกบอลช่วยเหลืออยู่ห่างจากกล้องหน้าและทำให้อินเทอร์เฟซมีความเรียบง่ายยิ่งขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="แอประบบ">
<feature>คุณสามารถบันทึกเสียงระบบระหว่างการโทรด้วยเสียงหรือวิดีโอได้ตามต้องการ ทดลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ฟีเจอร์การเข้าถึง > การบันทึกหน้าจอ > บันทึกจากเสียงระบบ
มีความละเอียดสามระดับ (480 พิกเซล/720 พิกเซล /1080 พิกเซล) สำหรับคุณภาพของวิดีโอในการบันทึกหน้าจอ ทดลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ฟีเจอร์การเข้าถึง > การบันทึกหน้าจอ > คุณภาพของวิดีโอ</feature>
</features>
<features module="พื้นที่รายการโปรด">
<feature>เพิ่มประสิทธิภาพความลื่นไหลของเอฟเฟกต์การเคลื่อนไหวในพื้นที่รายการโปรด</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้สำหรับการเชื่อมต่อ USB การยืนยันหรือข้อความแจ้งเตือนความปลอดภัยจะปรากฏเมื่อคุณเลือกถ่ายโอนภาพถ่ายหรือถ่ายโอนไฟล์ / Android Auto เพื่อให้แน่ใจถึงการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลที่ปลอดภัยขึ้น
มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ต.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, nagbibigay-daan ang update na ito na ma-edit ang mga watermark, at ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user sa assistive ball. Bukod pa rito, puwedeng i-record ang tunog ng system at available ang tatlong antas ng resolution para sa mga recording ng screen. Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user para sa koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize din ng release na ito ang pagiging smooth ng effect sa paggalaw sa status bar at Espasyo ng Mga Paborito, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Pinapalaki ang text, at ginagawang bold ang mga icon para gawing mas madaling matukoy ang impormasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Puwede nang idagdag at alisin ang mga watermark kung kailangan. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Kumuha ng larawan > Buksan ang larawan > I-edit > Watermark > Mga opsyon ng watermark: Orihinal, Watermark na text, Watermark na frame.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user ng assistive ball sa landscape mode, na tumitiyak na nananatiling malayo mula sa camera sa harap ang assistive ball, samakatuwid ay nag-aalok ng mas simpleng interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga app ng system">
<feature>Puwedeng kang mag-record ng tunog ng system habang nasa mga video o voice call kung kinakailangan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Pagre-record ng screen > Mag-record mula sa tunog ng system.
Available ang tatlong antas ng resolution (480P/720P/1080P) para sa kalidad ng video sa mga recording ng video. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Recording ng screen > Kalidad ng video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espasyo ng Mga Paborito">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang pagiging smooth ng effect sa paggalaw sa Espasyo ng Mga Paborito.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate para sa koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang prompt ng pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.
Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, nagbibigay-daan ang update na ito na ma-edit ang mga watermark, at ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user sa assistive ball. Bukod pa rito, puwedeng i-record ang tunog ng system at available ang tatlong antas ng resolution para sa mga recording ng screen. Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user para sa koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize din ng release na ito ang pagiging smooth ng effect sa paggalaw sa status bar at Espasyo ng Mga Paborito, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Pinapalaki ang text, at ginagawang bold ang mga icon para gawing mas madaling matukoy ang impormasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Puwede nang idagdag at alisin ang mga watermark kung kailangan. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Kumuha ng larawan > Buksan ang larawan > I-edit > Watermark > Mga opsyon ng watermark: Orihinal, Watermark na text, Watermark na frame.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user ng assistive ball sa landscape mode, na tumitiyak na nananatiling malayo mula sa camera sa harap ang assistive ball, samakatuwid ay nag-aalok ng mas simpleng interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga app ng system">
<feature>Puwedeng kang mag-record ng tunog ng system habang nasa mga video o voice call kung kinakailangan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Pagre-record ng screen > Mag-record mula sa tunog ng system.
Available ang tatlong antas ng resolution (480P/720P/1080P) para sa kalidad ng video sa mga recording ng video. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Recording ng screen > Kalidad ng video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Espasyo ng Mga Paborito">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang pagiging smooth ng effect sa paggalaw sa Espasyo ng Mga Paborito.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate para sa koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang prompt ng pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.
Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız bu güncelleme ile filigran düzenleme özelliği eklenmiş ve yardımcı topun kullanıcı deneyimi optimize edilmiştir. Sistem ses kaydı özelliği eklenmiş ve ekran kayıtları için üç çözünürlük seviyesi sunulmuştur. USB bağlantısı için kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması zorunlu hale getirilmiştir. Bu sürüm ile ayrıca durum çubuğundaki ve Favoriler Alanındaki hareket efektinin düzgünlüğü optimize edilmiş ve bir güvenlik yaması eklenmiştir. Güncelleme yapılması tavsiye edilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Durum çubuğu">
<feature>Metin boyutu büyütülmüş ve bilgiler daha kolay anlaşılsın diye simgeler kalınlaştırılmıştır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Filigranlar artık istenildiği gibi eklenebilir ve kaldırılabilir. Bu işlevi şuraya giderek deneyimleyebilirsiniz: Fotoğraf çek > Fotoğrafı aç > Düzenle > Filigran > Filigran seçenekleri: Orijinal, Metin filigranı, Çerçeve filigranı.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Çoklu Pencere">
<feature>Yatay modda yardımcı topun kullanıcı deneyimi optimize edilerek yardımcı topun ön kameradan uzak durması sağlanmış ve böylece arayüz basitleştirilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem uygulamaları">
<feature>Görüntülü veya sesli aramalar sırasında sistem sesini istediğiniz gibi kaydedebilirsiniz. Bu işlevi şuraya giderek deneyimleyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Erişilebilirlik özellikleri > Ekran kaydı > Sistem sesinden kayıt.
Ekran kayıtlarında video kalitesi için üç çözünürlük seviyesi (480P/720P/1080P) seçeneği bulunmaktadır. Bu işlevi şuraya giderek deneyimleyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Erişilebilirlik özellikleri > Ekran kaydı > Video kalitesi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoriler Alanı">
<feature>Favoriler Alanı'ndaki hareket efektinin pürüzsüzlüğü optimize edildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>USB bağlantısı için kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekli hale getirilmiştir. Fotoğrafları aktar veya Dosyaları aktar / Android Auto'yu seçtiğinizde bir doğrulama ya da güvenlik istemi açılması sağlanarak veri aktarımı daha güvenli hale getirilmiştir.
Android güvenlik yaması (Ekim 2024) sistem güvenliği için dahil edilmiştir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/10 web sitemizi ziyaret edin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا كامېرا سۇباسمىسىنى تەھرىرلەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، تۈزبوي ئېكران كۆرۈنۈشىدىكى لەيلىمە شار ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، ئېكران خاتىرىلەش ئېنىقلىقنى ئۈچ دەرىجە بويىچە تەڭشەشنى قوللايدىغان بولدى، سىستېما ئاۋازىنى ئۈنگە ئېلىش ئۈزچاتى ۋە USB ئۇلىنىشى ئارقىلىق ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ھالەت بالدىقى ۋە يىغىش بوشلۇقىنىڭ ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىنىڭ راۋانلىقى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ھالەت بالدىقى»">
<feature>ھالەت بالدىقىدىكى خەت نۇسخىسى سىنبەلگىسىنى كۆرسىتىش، خەت نۇسخىسىنى چوڭايتىش، توملىتىش سىنبەلگىسى ئۇسلۇبى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلۇپ، ئۇچۇر تونۇش نىسبىتى ئۆستۈرۈلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئامبار»">
<feature>كامېرا سۇباسمىسىنى تەھرىرلەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، سۇ باسمىنى ئۆزىڭىز قوشسىڭىز ۋە ئەسلىگە كەلتۈرسىڭىز بولىدۇ، سىناش يولى: رەسىمگە تارتىش > رەسىمنى ئېچىش > تەھرىرلەش > سۇباسما > سۇباسما دېگەن ئورۇندىن تۆۋەندىكىلەرنى تاللاڭ: ئەسلى رەسىم، تېكىست سۇباسما، رامكا سۇباسما.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«كۆپ كۆزنەك»">
<feature>تۈزبوي كۆرۈنۈشىدە لەيلىمە شارچىنى ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، لەيلىمە شارچىنىڭ توختاش ئورنى ئالدى كامېرا رايونىدىن ساقلىنىدىغان بولدى، ئارايۈز تېخىمۇ كۆركەم بولدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«سىستېما ئەپى»">
<feature>ئېكران خاتىرىلەش كۆرۈنۈشىدە سىستېما ئاۋازىنى ئۈنگە ئېلىش ئۈزچاتى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، سىنلىق ياكى ئاۋازلىق سۆزلەشكەندە، سىستېما ئاۋازىنى ئۈنگە ئېلىشنى قوللايدۇ، ئېكران خاتىرىلەش تېخىمۇ تولۇق بولىدۇ، تەڭشەش يولى: تەڭشەك > ياردەمچى ئىقتىدار > ئېكران خاتىرىلەش > سىستېما ئاۋازىنى ئۈنگە ئېلىش.
ئېكران خاتىرىلەش ئېنىقلىقىنى ئىختىيارىيلاشتۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئۈچ دەرىجە بويىچە تەڭشەش (480P/720P/1080P) نى قوللايدۇ، مۇناسىپ ئېنىقلىقنى خالىغانچە تاللاپ ئېكران خاتىرىلىيەلەيسىز، ئېكران خاتىرىلەش تېخىمۇ سۈزۈك بولىدۇ، تەڭشەش يولى: تەڭشەك > ياردەمچى ئىقتىدار > ئېكران خاتىرىلەش > ئېنىقلىق تاللاندى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«يىغىش بوشلۇقى»">
<feature>يىغىش بوشلۇقى ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىنىڭ راۋانلىقى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>‏USB ئۇلىنىشى ئارقىلىق ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، «رەسىم يوللاش» ياكى «ھۆججەت يوللاش/Android Auto» نى تاللىغاندا سالاھىيەت دەلىللەش كېرەك، مەلۇمات يوللىشىڭىز تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر.
ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 10-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення дає змогу змінювати водяні знаки, а також оптимізує зручність використання допоміжного меню. Крім того, можна записувати звук системи й користуватися трьома рівнями роздільної здатності під час записування з екрана. Для підключення через USB користувач має пройти автентифікацію. У цьому випуску також підвищено плавність ефекту руху в рядку стану й Favorites Space і реалізовано виправлення системи безпеки. Радимо встановити оновлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Рядок стану">
<feature>Збільшено розмір шрифту та виділено жирним піктограми, щоб полегшити розпізнавання інформації.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Тепер можна за бажанням додавати й вилучати водяні знаки. Для цього виберіть "Зробити фото" > "Відкрити фотографію" > "Змінити" > "Водяний знак" > "Варіанти водяного знака": "Оригінал", "Текстовий водяний знак", "Водяний знак із рамкою".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Багатовіконний режим">
<feature>Стало зручніше користуватися допоміжним меню на екрані в горизонтальній орієнтації: тепер меню розташовано на відстані від фронтальної камери.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Системні додатки">
<feature>Ви можете за бажанням записувати системні звуки під час голосових викликів чи відеовикликів. Для цього виберіть "Налаштування" > "Функції спеціальних можливостей" > "Запис вмісту екрана" > "Записування звуку системи".
Під час записування з екрана можна користуватися трьома рівнями роздільної здатності (480P, 720P, 1080P), щоб обирати відповідну якість відео. Для цього виберіть "Налаштування" > "Функції спеціальних можливостей" > "Запис вмісту екрана" > "Якість відео".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorites Space">
<feature>Підвищено плавність ефекту руху в області Favorites Space.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Для підключення через USB тепер потрібна автентифікація користувача. Коли ви вибираєте "Передавання фото" або "Передавання файлів / Android Auto", з’являється запит на підтвердження або запит щодо безпеки, завдяки чому підвищується захист даних, що передаються.
Для захисту системи реалізовано виправлення системи безпеки Android (від жовтня 2024 року). Щоб дізнатися більше про оновлення системи безпеки HONOR, відвідайте сторінку https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ واٹر مارکس میں ترمیم کرنے اور معاون بال کے صارف کے تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، سسٹم کی آواز کو ریکارڈ کیا جا سکتا ہے اور اسکرین ریکارڈنگ کے لیے ریزولوشن کی تین سطحیں دستیاب ہیں۔ USB کنکشن کے لیے صارف کی تصدیق درکار ہے۔ یہ ریلیز اسٹیٹس بار اور من پسند اسپیس میں حرکت کے اثر کی ہمواری کو بھی بہتر بناتی ہے، اور ایک سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="اسٹیٹس بار">
<feature>متن کے سائز کو بڑھاتی ہے، اور معلومات کو آسانی سے پہچاننے کے لیے آئیکنز کو بولڈ کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="گیلری">
<feature>واٹر مارکس کو اب حسب ضرورت شامل کیا جا سکتا اور ہٹایا جا سکتا ہے۔ آپ یہاں جا کر اس کا تجربہ کر سکتے ہیں: تصویر لیں > تصویر کھولیں > ترمیم کریں > واٹر مارک > واٹر مارک کے اختیارات: اصل، متنی واٹر مارک، فریم واٹر مارک۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ملٹی ونڈو">
<feature>لینڈ اسکیپ موڈ میں معاون بال کے صارف کے تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اس بات کو یقینی بناتی ہے کہ معاون بال سامنے والے کیمرہ سے دور رہے، اس طرح ایک سادہ انٹرفیس پیش کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم ایپس">
<feature>آپ ویڈیو یا وائس کالز کے دوران سسٹم کی آواز کو حسب خواہش ریکارڈ کر سکتے ہیں۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > رسائی پذیری کی خصوصیات > اسکرین ریکارڈنگ > سسٹم کی آواز سے ریکارڈ کریں۔
اسکرین ریکارڈنگز میں ویڈیو کے معیار کے لیے ریزولوشن کی تین سطحیں (480P/720P/1080P) دستیاب ہیں۔ یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: ترتیبات > رسائی پذیری کی خصوصیات > اسکرین ریکارڈنگ > ویڈیو کا معیار۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="من پسند اسپیس">
<feature>من پسند اسپیس میں حرکت کے اثر کی ہمواری کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کے لیے صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ جب آپ تصاویر منتقل کریں یا فائلز منتقل کریں / Android خود کار کو منتخب کرتے ہیں ایک تصدیقی یا سکیورٹی پرامپٹ ظاہر ہوتا ہے، جو ڈیٹا کی محفوظ منتقلی کو یقینی بناتا ہے۔
سسٹم سکیورٹی کے لیے Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اکتوبر 2024) کو شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ملاحظہ کریں</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanishda shaffof belgilarni tahrirlash imkoniyati taqdim etildi va yordamchi koptokning foydalanuvchi taassuroti optimallandi. Bundan tashqari, tizim tovushini yozib olish imkoniyati va ekran yozuvlari uchun uchta aniqlik darajasi taqdim etildi. USB orqali aloqa uchun foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. Shuningdek, ushbu versiyada holat paneli va Saralanganlar xotirasidagi harakat effektining ravonligi optimallandi hamda xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi. Uni yangilash tavsiya etiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Holat qatori">
<feature>Axborotni oʻqishni osonlashtirish uchun matn oʻlchami kattalashtirildi va belgilar qalinlashtirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galereya">
<feature>Endi shaffof belgilarni xohlagancha qoʻshish yoki olib tashlash mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinashingiz mumkin: Surat oling > Suratni oching > Tahrirlash > Shaffof belgi > Shaffof belgi parametrlari: Original, Matnli shaffof belgi, Hoshiyali shaffof belgi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bir nechta oyna">
<feature>Yordamchi koptokning manzara rejimidagi foydalanuvchi taassuroti optimallandi, yordamchi koptokning old kameradan uzoqda turishini taʼminlash orqali interfeys soddalashtirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim ilovalari">
<feature>Video yoki ovozli chaqiruvlar paytida xohlasangiz tizim tovushini yozib olishingiz mumkin. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Maxsus imkoniyatlar funksiyalari > Ekrandan yozib olish > Tizim tovushidan yozib olish.
Ekran yozuvlarida video sifati uchun uchta aniqlik darajasidan (480P/720P/1080P) tanlash mumkin. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Maxsus imkoniyatlar funksiyalari > Ekrandan yozib olish > Video sifati.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saralanganlar xotirasi">
<feature>Saralanganlar xotirasidagi harakat effektining ravonligi optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>USB orqali aloqa uchun foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. “Suratlarni uzatish” yoki “Fayllarni o‘tkazish / Android Auto” tanlaganida, maʼlumotlarni xavfsiz uzatishni taʼminlash uchun tasdiqlash yoki xavfsizlik haqida ogohlantirish oynasi ochiladi.
Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, oktabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này cho phép sửa hình chìm mờ và tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm người dùng về bóng hỗ trợ. Ngoài ra, có thể ghi lại âm thanh hệ thống và có ba mức độ phân giải cho bản ghi màn hình. Cần xác thực người dùng để kết nối USB. Bản phát hành này cũng tối ưu hóa độ mượt mà của hiệu ứng chuyển động trong thanh trạng thái và Không gian ưa thích, đồng thời tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Bạn nên cập nhật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Thanh trạng thái">
<feature>Tăng kích thước văn bản và in đậm các biểu tượng để dễ nhận biết thông tin hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bộ sưu tập">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể thêm và xóa hình chìm mờ theo ý muốn. Hãy trải nghiệm bằng cách vào: Chụp ảnh > Mở ảnh > Sửa > Hình chìm mờ > Tùy chọn hình chìm mờ: Ảnh gốc, Hình chìm mờ dạng văn bản, Hình chìm mờ dạng khung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Đa cửa sổ">
<feature>Tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm của người dùng về bóng hỗ trợ ở chế độ ngang, đảm bảo bóng hỗ trợ không chạm vào máy ảnh trước, do đó, mang đến giao diện đơn giản hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ứng dụng hệ thống">
<feature>Bạn có thể ghi lại âm thanh hệ thống trong các cuộc gọi video hoặc thoại tùy ý. Hãy thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Tính năng Trợ năng > Ghi màn hình > Ghi từ âm thanh hệ thống.
Có 3 mức độ phân giải (480P/720P/1080P) cho chất lượng video trong bản ghi màn hình. Hãy thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Tính năng Trợ năng > Ghi màn hình > Chất lượng video.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Không gian ưa thích">
<feature>Tối ưu hóa độ mượt mà của hiệu ứng chuyển động trong Không gian ưa thích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Yêu cầu xác thực người dùng để kết nối USB. Một thông báo nhắc xác minh hoặc bảo mật sẽ xuất hiện khi bạn chọn Truyền tải ảnh hoặc Truyền tệp tin/Android Auto, đảm bảo truyền dữ liệu an toàn hơn.
Bản cập nhật này tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 10 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增相機浮水印可編輯功能，優化橫向屏幕場景浮動球使用體驗，屏幕錄影支援三檔解析度可調節，新增系統聲音錄製開關和 USB 連接用戶身份驗證功能，優化狀態欄和最愛空間動畫效果流暢性，整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【狀態欄】">
<feature>優化狀態欄字體圖標顯示，增大字體大小，加粗圖標樣式，提高資訊識別度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增相機浮水印可編輯功能，可自行新增和還原浮水印，體驗路徑：拍攝 > 開啟相片 > 編輯 > 浮水印 > 浮水印選擇：原圖、文字浮水印、相框浮水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智能多窗】">
<feature>優化橫向屏幕場景浮動球使用體驗，浮動球停留位置避開前置鏡頭區域，介面顯示更美觀。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統應用程式】">
<feature>新增錄屏場景錄製系統聲音開關，視像或語音通話時，支援錄製系統聲音，使錄屏更完整。設定路徑：設定 > 輔助功能 > 屏幕錄影 > 錄製系統聲音。
新增錄屏解析度自訂功能，支援三擋可調節（480P/720P/1080P），隨心選擇對應的解析度進行屏幕錄影，使錄屏更清晰，設定路徑：設定 > 輔助功能 > 屏幕錄影 > 清晰度選擇。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【最愛空間】">
<feature>優化最愛空間動畫效果流暢性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增 USB 連接用戶身份驗證功能，在選擇「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」時，需要進行身份驗證，讓您的數據傳輸更安全。
整合 Android 2024年10月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增相機浮水印可編輯功能，最佳化在橫向場景下的懸浮球使用體驗，螢幕錄影支援三檔可調整解析度，新增系統聲音錄製開關和 USB 連接使用者身分驗證功能，最佳化狀態列和我的最愛空間動畫流暢性，並整合安全修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【狀態列】">
<feature>最佳化狀態列字體和圖示顯示，增大字體大小，加粗圖示樣式，並提高資訊辨識度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增相機浮水印可編輯功能，可自行新增和還原浮水印，體驗路徑：拍照 > 開啟相片 > 編輯 > 浮水印 > 浮水印選取：原始版本、文字浮水印、相框浮水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>最佳化在橫向場景下的懸浮球使用體驗，懸浮球停留位置避開前置鏡頭區域，畫面顯示更美觀。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統應用程式】">
<feature>新增螢幕錄影場景錄製系統聲音開關，視訊或語音通話時，支援錄製系統聲音，使螢幕錄影更完整，設定路徑：設定 > 無障礙功能 > 螢幕錄影 > 錄製系統聲音。
新增螢幕錄影解析度自訂功能，支援三檔可調整 (480P/720P/1080P)，隨心選取對應的解析度進行螢幕錄影，使螢幕錄影更清晰，設定路徑：設定 > 無障礙功能 > 螢幕錄影 > 解析度選取。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【我的最愛空間】">
<feature>最佳化我的最愛空間動畫流暢性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增 USB 連接使用者身分驗證功能，在選取「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」時，需要進行身分驗證，讓您的資料傳輸更安全。
整合 Android 2024 年 10 月安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
