<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增隐私打码、分屏保存以及隐藏应用桌面图标功能，优化部分场景桌面使用体验，更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【隐私打码】">
<feature>选择需要打码的图片后点击“分享->隐私打码”，将自动对您图片中头像、昵称、手机号等敏感信息进行一键打码，保护您的隐私安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>新增分屏保存功能，分屏状态下点击分屏线中间按钮，可将分屏组合以图标形式保存在桌面，后续通过点击该图标即可快捷打开此分屏组合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面】">
<feature>部分系统服务支持胶囊开关，满足用户自主设置的需求，体验路径：“设置>通知和状态栏>灵动胶囊”。
优化部分场景通知栏布局、动效以及图标显示效果。
应用图标长按即可快捷进入权限设置界面。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，从“仅充电”切换至“传输照片”或“传输文件 / Android Auto”模式时，弹出验证界面或安全提示，让您的数据传输更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隐藏应用桌面图标功能，体验路径：设置>安全和隐私>设备与数据保护>隐藏应用桌面图标。
合入安卓2024年10月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update introduces Blur Private Info feature. Additionally, home screen icons can be hidden. App combinations in split-screen mode can be saved. User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. This release also incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blur Private Info">
<feature>Select an image and tap Share -> Blur Private Info. The profile picture, nickname, phone number and other sensitive data in the image will be automatically blurred. This is to protect your privacy.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App combinations in split-screen mode can now be saved. In split-screen mode, tap the button in the middle of the divider to save the combination as an icon on the home screen. Tap the icon enables quick access to the combination.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen">
<feature>Magic Capsule can be switched on or turned off in some system services. Go to Settings > Notifications and status bar > Magic Capsule to try it out.
The layout, motion effect and icon display effect of the notification panel are optimized in some scenarios.
Long press an app icon to quickly go to permission settings.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>You can now hide home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen.
Android Security Patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ የግል መረጃን አደብዝዝ ባህሪን ያስተዋውቃል። በተጨማሪም የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች ሊደበቁ ይችላሉ። የመተግበሪያ ጥምረቶች በተከፈለ ማያ ሁነታ ሊቀመጡ ይችላሉ። የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ይህ ልቀት የደህንነት መጠገኛንም ያካትታል። እንዲያዘምኑ ይመከራል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የግል መረጃን አደብዝዝ">
<feature>ምስል ይምረጡ እና አጋራ -> የግል መረጃን አደብዝዝ የሚለውን ይንኩ። በምስሉ ላይ ያለው የመገለጫ ስዕል፣ ቅጽል ስም፣ ስልክ ቁጥር እና ሌሎች ትብነት ያላቸው መረጃዎች በራስ-ሰር ይደበዝዛሉ። ይህ የእርስዎን ግላዊነት ለመጠበቅ ነው።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ብዙ-መስኮት">
<feature>አሁን በተከፈለ ማያ ገጽ ያሉ የመተግበሪያ ውህዶች ሊቀመጡ ይችላሉ። በተከፈለ ማያ ገጽ ሁነታ፣ ውህዱን በመነሻ ማያ ገጽ ላይ እንደ አዶ ለማስቀመጥ በአከፋፋዩ መሃል ያለውን አዝራር መታ ያድርጉ። አዶውን መታ ማድረግ ወደ ውህዱ ፈጣን መዳረሻ ያስችላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="መነሻ ማያ">
<feature>አስማታዊ ካፕሱል በአንዳንድ የስርዓት አገልግሎቶች ውስጥ ሊበራ ወይም ሊጠፋ ይችላል። እሱን ለመሞከር ወደ ቅንብሮች > ማሳወቂያዎች እና የሁኔታ አሞሌ > አስማታዊ ካፕሱል ይሂዱ።
የማሳወቂያ ፓነሉ አቀማመጥ፣ የእንቅስቃሴ ውጤት እና የአዶ ማሳያ ውጤት በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የተመቻቹ ናቸው።
ወደ የፈቃድ ቅንብሮች በፍጥነት ለመሄድ የመተግበሪያ አዶን በረጅሙ ይጫኑ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ የውሂብ ማስተላለፍን የሚያረጋግጥ ኃይል መሙላት ብቻ የሚለውን አጥፍተው ፎቶዎችን አስተላልፍ ወይም ፋይሎችን አስተላልፍ / Android Autoን ሲመርጡ የማረጋገጫ ወይም የደህንነት ጥያቄ ይመጣል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>አሁን የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎችን መደበቅ ይችላሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ደህንነት እና ግላዊነት > የመሳሪያ እና የውሂብ ጥበቃ > መተግበሪያዎችን ከመነሻ ገጽ ደብቅ።
የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኦክቶበር 2024) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ሲባል ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝመናዎች የበለጠ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድረ ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ላይ ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يقدم هذا التحديث ميزة تمويه المعلومات الخاصة. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، يمكن إخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية. يمكن حفظ مجموعات التطبيقات في وضع تقسيم الشاشة. يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB. ويضمّن هذا الإصدار أيضًا تصحيح أمان. من المستحسن التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تمويه المعلومات الخاصة">
<feature>حدد صورة ثم اضغط على مشاركة -> تمويه المعلومات الخاصة. سيتم تمويه صورة الحساب الشخصي والكنية ورقم الهاتف والبيانات الحساسة الأخرى الموجودة في الصورة بشكل تلقائي. يهدف هذا الأمر إلى حماية خصوصيتك.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النوافذ المتعددة">
<feature>يمكن الآن حفظ مجموعات التطبيقات في وضع تقسيم الشاشة. في وضع تقسيم الشاشة، اضغط على الزر الموجود في منتصف المقسم لحفظ المجموعة كأيقونة على الشاشة الرئيسية. يؤدي الضغط على الأيقونة إلى تمكين الوصول السريع إلى المجموعة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الشاشة الرئيسية">
<feature>يمكنك تشغيل Magic Capsule أو إيقاف تشغيلها في بعض خدمات النظام. انتقل إلى الإعدادات > الإشعارات وشريط الحالة > Magic Capsule لتجربة الميزة.
تم تحسين تأثير التخطيط والحركة وعرض الأيقونات على لوحة الإشعارات في بعض السيناريوهات.
اضغط لفترة طويلة على أيقونة التطبيق للانتقال بسرعة إلى إعدادات الأذونات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB. تظهر مطالبة التحقق أو الأمان عندما تحدد "نقل الصور" أو "نقل الملفات / أندرويد أوتو"، بدلاً من "الشحن فقط"، مما يضمن نقل البيانات بشكل أكثر أمانًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>يمكنك الآن إخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الأمان والخصوصية > حماية الجهاز والبيانات > إخفاء التطبيقات من الشاشة الرئيسية.
تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أكتوبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটে গোপনীয় তথ্য ব্লাৰ কৰক ফিচাৰটোৰ পৰিচয় কৰায়। ইয়াৰ উপৰিও, হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাব পাৰি। স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত এপ্প্‌ৰ সংমিশ্ৰণ সংৰক্ষণ কৰিব পাৰি। USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। এই মুক্তিয়ে লগতে এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। এইটো আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গোপনীয় তথ্য ব্লাৰ কৰক">
<feature>এখন প্ৰতিচ্ছবি বাছনি কৰক আৰু ভাগ-বতৰা কৰক -> গোপনীয় তথ্য ব্লাৰ কৰক টিপক। প্ৰতিচ্ছবিখনত থকা প্ৰ'ফাইল চিত্ৰ, উপনাম, ফোন নম্বৰ আৰু অন্য সংবেদনশীল ডাটা স্বয়ংক্ৰিয়ভাৱে ব্লাৰ কৰা হ'ব। আপোনাৰ গোপনীয়তা সুৰক্ষিত কৰিবলৈ এইটো কৰা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি-উইণ্ড'">
<feature>এতিয়া স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত এপ্প্‌ৰ সংমিশ্ৰণ সংৰক্ষণ কৰিব পাৰি। স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত, হোম স্ক্ৰীণত সংমিশ্ৰণক এটা চিহ্ন ৰূপে সংৰক্ষণ কৰিবলৈ ডিভাইডাৰৰ মাজত থকা বুটামটো টিপক। চিহ্নটো টিপিলে সংমিশ্ৰণলৈ দ্ৰুত প্ৰৱেশ সক্ষম কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণ">
<feature>কিছুমান ছিষ্টেমৰ সেৱাত মেজিক কেপচুল চুইচ অন বা অফ কৰিব পাৰি। ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাবলৈ ছেটিংছ > অধিসূচনাসমূহ আৰু স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা > মেজিক কেপচুললৈ যাওক।
কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত অধিসূচনা পেনেলৰ লেআউট, গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱ আৰু চিহ্ন প্ৰদৰ্শনৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰা হয়।
দ্ৰুতভাৱে অনুমতিৰ ছেটিংছলৈ যাবলৈ এটা এপ্প্‌ৰ চিহ্নত দীঘলীয়াকৈ দবাওক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। আপুনি কেৱল চাৰ্জ কৰকৰ পৰিৱৰ্তে ফটোসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক বা ফাইলসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক/Android Auto বাছনি কৰাৰ সময়ত এটা প্ৰমাণীকৰণ বা নিৰাপত্তাৰ সংকেত দেখা পায়, যিয়ে নিৰাপদ ডাটা স্থানান্তৰ নিশ্চিত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>আপুনি এতিয়া হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাব পাৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > নিৰাপত্তা আৰু গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইচ আৰু ডাটা সুৰক্ষা > হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ পৰা এপ্প্‌সমূহ লুকুৱাওক।
ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (অক্টোবৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə Şəxsi məlumatları tutqunlaşdırın xüsusiyyətini təqdim edir. Bundan əlavə, əsas ekran nişanları gizlədilə bilər. Bölünmüş ekran rejimində proqram kombinasiyaları yadda saxlanıla bilər. USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Bu buraxılış həm də təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir. Yeniləmək tövsiyə olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Şəxsi məlumatları tutqunlaşdırın">
<feature>Şəkil seçin və Paylaşın -> Şəxsi məlumatları tutqunlaşdırın üstünə toxunun. Şəkildəki profil şəkli, ləqəb, telefon nömrəsi və digər həssas verilənlər avtomatik olaraq tutqunlaşdırılacaq. Bu, məxfiliyinizi qorumaq üçündür.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İki Pəncərəli">
<feature>Artıq bölünmüş ekran rejimində proqram kombinasiyaları yadda saxlanıla bilər. Bölünmüş ekran rejimində kombinasiyanı əsas ekranda nişan kimi yadda saxlamaq üçün bölücünün ortasındakı düyməyə toxunun. Nişana toxunmaq kombinasiyaya sürətli daxil olmaq imkanı verir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Əsas ekran">
<feature>Sehrli Kapsul bəzi sistem xidmətlərində yandırıla və ya söndürülə bilər. Bunu sınamaq üçün Parametrlər > Bildirişlər və status paneli > Sehrli Kapsul bölməsinə keçin.
Bildiriş panelinin tərtibatı, hərəkət effekti və nişan displeyi effekti bəzi hallarda optimallaşdırılıb.
İcazə parametrlərinə cəld keçmək üçün proqram nişanına basıb saxlayın.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Verilənlərin təhlükəsiz ötürülməsini təmin etmək üçün Yalnız doldurma əvəzinə Fotoları ötürün və ya Faylları ötürün/Android Auto seçdiyiniz zaman yoxlama və ya təhlükəsizlik sorğusu görünür.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>İndi əsas ekran nişanlarını gizlədə bilərsiniz. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Təhlükəsizlik və məxfilik > Cihaz və verilənlərin mühafizəsi > Proqramları Əsas ekrandan gizlədin.
Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Oktyabr 2024) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 veb-saytımıza daxil olun.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki nglebokake fitur Blawurake Info Pribadi. Saliyane iku, ikon layar ngarep bisa didhelikake. Kombinasi apl ing mode layar misah bisa disimpen. Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB. Rilis iki uga nggabungake patch keamanan. Sampeyan disaranake supaya nganyarake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blawurake Info Pribadi">
<feature>Pilih gambar lan tutul Bage -> Blawurake Info Pribadi. Gambar profil, celukan, nomer ponsel, lan data sensitif liyane ing gambar bakal otomatis diblawurake. Tujuane fitur iki yaiku kanggo nglindhungi privasi sampeyan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Kombinasi apl ing mode layar misah saiki bisa disimpen. Ing mode layar misah, tutul tombol ing tengahe pamisah kanggo nyimpen kombinasi minangka ikon ing layar ngarep. Nutul ikon kasebut bakal ngaktifake akses cepet menyang kombinasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Layar ngarep">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib bisa diuripake utawa dipateni ing sawetara layanan sistem. Bukak Setelan > Notifikasi lan garis status > Kapsul Ajaib kanggo nyoba fitur iki.
Tatanan, efek obahan, lan efek tampilan ikon ing panel notifikasi dioptimalake ing sawetara skenario.
Penet suwe ikon apl kanggo mbukak setelan idin kanthi cepet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB. Prentah verifikasi utawa keamanan bakal muncul nalika sampeyan milih opsi Transfer foto utawa Transfer file/Android Auto, tinimbang Mung ngisi daya, saengga njamin transfer data sing luwih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Sampeyan saiki bisa ndhelikake ikon layar ngarep. Coba fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Keamanan lan privasi > Proteksi data lan piranti > Dhelikake apl saka Layar ngarep.
Patch Keamanan Android (Oktober 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uvodi funkciju „Zamagli privatne podatke“. Pored toga ikone početnog ekrana mogu da se sakriju. Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana mogu da se sačuvaju. Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da nadogradite.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zamagli privatne podatke">
<feature>Izaberite sliku i dodirnite Deli -> Zamagli privatne podatke. Zatim se slika profila, nadimak, broj telefona i drugi osetljivi podaci na slici automatski zamagljuju da bi se zaštitila vaša privatnost.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Početni ekran">
<feature>Magična kapsula može da se uključi ili isključi u nekim sistemskim uslugama. Da biste isprobali ovu funkciju, idite u Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula.
Izgled, efekat kretanja i efekat prikaza ikona na tabli sa obaveštenjima su optimizovani u nekim scenarijima.
Duže držite pritisnutom ikonu aplikacije da biste brzo prešli u podešavanja dozvola.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka / Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Pokušajte tako što idete na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
Android bezbednosna zakrpa (okt. 2024) je integrisana za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim nadogradnjama HONOR, posetite našu web stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uvodi funkciju „Zamagli privatne podatke“. Pored toga ikone početnog ekrana mogu da se sakriju. Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana mogu da se sačuvaju. Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da nadogradite.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zamagli privatne podatke">
<feature>Izaberite sliku i dodirnite Deli -> Zamagli privatne podatke. Zatim se slika profila, nadimak, broj telefona i drugi osetljivi podaci na slici automatski zamagljuju da bi se zaštitila vaša privatnost.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Početni ekran">
<feature>Magična kapsula može da se uključi ili isključi u nekim sistemskim uslugama. Da biste isprobali ovu funkciju, idite u Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula.
Izgled, efekat kretanja i efekat prikaza ikona na tabli sa obaveštenjima su optimizovani u nekim scenarijima.
Duže držite pritisnutom ikonu aplikacije da biste brzo prešli u podešavanja dozvola.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka / Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Pokušajte tako što idete na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
Android bezbednosna zakrpa (okt. 2024) je integrisana za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim nadogradnjama HONOR, posetite našu web stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uvodi funkciju „Zamagli privatne podatke“. Pored toga ikone početnog ekrana mogu da se sakriju. Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana mogu da se sačuvaju. Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom. Ovo izdanje takođe uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da nadogradite.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zamagli privatne podatke">
<feature>Izaberite sliku i dodirnite Deli -> Zamagli privatne podatke. Zatim se slika profila, nadimak, broj telefona i drugi osetljivi podaci na slici automatski zamagljuju da bi se zaštitila vaša privatnost.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Početni ekran">
<feature>Magična kapsula može da se uključi ili isključi u nekim sistemskim uslugama. Da biste isprobali ovu funkciju, idite u Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula.
Izgled, efekat kretanja i efekat prikaza ikona na tabli sa obaveštenjima su optimizovani u nekim scenarijima.
Duže držite pritisnutom ikonu aplikacije da biste brzo prešli u podešavanja dozvola.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka / Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Pokušajte tako što idete na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
Android bezbednosna zakrpa (okt. 2024) je integrisana za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim nadogradnjama HONOR, posetite našu web stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ўводзіць функцыю «Размываць прыватную інфармацыю». Таксама цяпер можна схаваць значкі на галоўным экране. Гэта абнаўленне дазваляе захаваць камбінацыі праграм у рэжыме раздзельнага экрана. Пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB цяпер патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Акрамя таго, гэты выпуск уключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Рэкамендуецца ўстанавіць гэта абнаўленне.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Размываць прыватную інфармацыю">
<feature>Выберыце выяву і краніце «Падзяліцца -> Размываць прыватную інфармацыю». Пасля гэтага выява профілю, псеўданім, нумар тэлефона і іншыя канфідэнцыяльныя даныя на выяве аўтаматычна размыюцца. Гэта неабходна, каб абараніць вашу прыватнасць.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Многааконнасць">
<feature>Цяпер можна захоўваць камбінацыі праграм у рэжыме раздзельнага экрана. У рэжыме раздзельнага экрана націсніце на кнопку ў сярэдзіне раздзяляльніка, захаваць камбінацыю ў выглядзе значка на галоўным экране. Націснуўшы на значок, вы зможаце хутка аднавіць камбінацыю.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галоўны экран">
<feature>У некаторых сістэмных сэрвісах можна ўключыць або выключыць Чароўную капсулу. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Панэль апавяшчэнняў і стану > Чароўная капсула».
Кампаноўка, эфект руху і эфект адлюстравання значкоў панэлі апавяшчэнняў аптымізаваны ў некаторых сцэнарыях.
Доўгім націскам на значок праграмы можна хутка перайсці да налад дазволаў.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Калі вы выбераце функцыю «Перадача фота» або «Перадача файлаў / Android Auto» замест функцыі «Зарадкі», з’явіцца падказка наконт праверкі або бяспекі, каб гарантаваць бяспечную перадачу даных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Цяпер вы можаце хаваць значкі галоўнага экрана. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Бяспека і прыватнасць > Абарона прылады і даных > Схаваць праграмы з галоўнага экрана».
Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (кастрычнік 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, с тази актуализация се въвежда функцията „Замъгляване на лична информация“. Освен това иконите на началния екран могат да бъдат скрити. Комбинациите от приложения в режим на разделен екран могат да бъдат запаметени. Изисква се удостоверяване на потребителя при превключване на целите на USB връзката. Тази версия включва и корекция за сигурност. Препоръчва се да актуализирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Замъгляване на лична информация">
<feature>Изберете изображение и докоснете „Споделяне -> Замъгляване на лична информация“. Профилната снимка, псевдонимът, телефонният номер и други чувствителни данни в изображението ще бъдат автоматично замъглени. Целта е да се защити поверителността ви.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Няколко прозореца">
<feature>Комбинациите от приложения в режим на разделен екран вече могат да се запазват. В режим на разделен екран докоснете бутона в средата на разделителя, за да запазите комбинацията като икона на началния екран. Докосването на иконата позволява бърз достъп до комбинацията.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Начален екран">
<feature>„Магическа капсула“ може да бъде включена или изключена в някои системни услуги. Отидете в „Настройки > Известия и лента за състоянието > Магическа капсула“, за да я изпробвате.
Оформлението, ефектът на движение и ефектът на показване на иконите на панела за известия са оптимизирани в някои ситуации.
Натиснете продължително икона на приложение, за да отидете бързо в настройките за разрешение.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При превключване на целите на USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Когато изберете „Прехвърляне на снимки“ или „Прехвърляне на файлове/Android Auto“, вместо „Само зареждане“, се появява подкана за проверка или за сигурност, което гарантира по-безопасен трансфер на данни.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Защита">
<feature>Вече можете да скриете иконите на началния екран. Изпробвайте го, като отидете в: „Настройки > Сигурност и поверителност > Устройство и защита на данни > Скриване на приложения от началния екран“.
За сигурността на системата е включен пач за сигурност на Android (октомври 2024 г.). За повече информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR, моля, посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি ব্যক্তিগত তথ্য ঝাপসা করুন বৈশিষ্ট্যটি চালু করে। এছাড়াও হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলি লুকানো যেতে পারে। অ্যাপের সংমিশ্রণগুলি স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে সংরক্ষণ করা যেতে পারে। USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুইচ করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। এই রিলিজে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচও অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। এটা আপডেট করার সুপারিশ করা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ব্যক্তিগত তথ্য ঝাপসা করুন">
<feature>একটি ছবি নির্বাচন করুন এবং শেয়ার করুন -> ব্যক্তিগত তথ্য ঝাপসা করুন ট্যাপ করুন। প্রোফাইল ছবি, ডাকনাম, ফোন নম্বর এবং ছবির অন্যান্য সংবেদনশীল ডেটা স্বয়ংক্রিয়ভাবে ঝাপসা হয়ে যাবে। এটি আপনার গোপনীয়তা রক্ষা করার জন্য।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি উইন্ডো">
<feature>স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে অ্যাপের সংমিশ্রণগুলি এখন সংরক্ষণ করা যেতে পারে। স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে, সংমিশ্রণটিকে হোম স্ক্রিনে একটি আইকন হিসাবে সংরক্ষণ করতে বিভাজকের মাঝখানের বাটনটি ট্যাপ করুন। আইকনটি ট্যাপ করলে সংমিশ্রণটিতে কুইক অ্যাক্সেস সক্রিয় করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্রিন">
<feature>কিছু সিস্টেম পরিষেবায় ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল চালু বা বন্ধ করা যেতে পারে। এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখতে সেটিংস > বিজ্ঞপ্তি ও স্ট্যাটাস বার > ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল-এ যান।
বিজ্ঞপ্তি প্যানেলের ফরম্যাট, মোশন ইফেক্ট এবং আইকন ডিসপ্লে ইফেক্টকে কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে অপটিমাইজ করা হয়।
দ্রুত অনুমতি সেটিংসে যেতে দীর্ঘক্ষণ একটি অ্যাপের আইকন চাপুন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুইচ করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। আপনি যখন শুধুমাত্র চার্জ-এর পরিবর্তে ফটোগুলি ট্রান্সফার করুন বা ফাইলগুলি স্থানান্তর করুন / Android অটো নির্বাচন করেন তখন একটি যাচাইকরণ বা নিরাপত্তা প্রম্পট দেখতে পাওয়া যায়, যা নিরাপদ ডেটা স্থানান্তর নিশ্চিত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>আপনি এখন হোম স্ক্রিন আইকন লুকাতে পারেন। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > নিরাপত্তা ও গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইস এবং ডেটা সুরক্ষা > হোম স্ক্রিন থেকে অ্যাপগুলি লুকান।
সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (অক্টোবর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་དུ་སྒེར་གསང་བཀག་རིས་དང་ཡོལ་བགོ་ཉར་ཚགས། ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཡིབ་སྐུང་བྱེད་པ་བཅས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་ཅོག་ངོས་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【སྒེར་གསང་བཀག་རིས།】">
<feature>བཀག་རིས་བྱེད་དགོས་པའི་པར་རིས་བདམས་རྗེས་མཉམ་སྤྱོད་ནས་སྒེར་གསང་བཀག་རིས་ལ་བརྡབས་ན། རང་འགུལ་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་པར་རིས་ཁྲོད་ཀྱི་མགོ་པར་དང་གཅེས་མིང་། ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་ཨང་གྲངས་སོགས་ཀྱི་གནད་འགག་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ་རང་འགུལ་གྱིས་མཐེབ་གཅིག་གིས་བཀག་རིས་བརྒྱབ་ནས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྒེར་གསང་བདེ་འཇགས་ལ་སྲུང་སྐྱོབ་བྱ་སྲིད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རིག་ལྡན་སྒྲོམ་མང་།】">
<feature>ཡོལ་བགོ་ཉར་ཚགས་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡོལ་བགོའི་རྣམ་པའི་འོག་ཏུ་ཡོལ་བགོའི་ཐིག་གི་བར་གྱི་མཐེབ་ལ་བརྡབས་ན། ཡོལ་བགོའི་ཚོགས་སྒྲིག་རིས་རྟགས་རྣམ་པས་ཅོག་ངོས་སུ་ཉར་ཚགས་བྱ་ཆོག རྗེས་སུ་རིས་རྟགས་འདི་རྡེབ་པ་བརྒྱུད་ནས་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་ཡོལ་བགོ་ཚོགས་སྒྲིག་འདི་ཁ་ཕྱེ་ཆོག</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཅོག་ངོས།】">
<feature>ཁག་ཅིག་གི་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུས་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ་གྱི་བསད་སྤར་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱས་ནས། སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱིས་རང་བདག་གིས་སྒྲིག་འགོད་བྱས་པའི་དགོས་མཁོ་སྐོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི་སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བརྡ་ཐོ་དང་རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་། དེ་ནས་འགུལ་རྣམ་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ།
བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་བརྡ་ཐོའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་ལྟ་བཀོད་དང་འགུལ་ནུས། དེ་བཞིན་རིས་རྟགས་མངོན་སྟོན་ཁྱད་ནུས་བཅས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད།
ཉེར་སྤྱོད་རིས་རྟགས་ཡུན་རིང་གནོན་ན་མྱུར་བདེའི་ངང་དབང་ཚད་སྒྲིག་འགོད་ཀྱི་མཚམས་ངོས་སུ་འཛུལ་ཐུབ།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། གློག་གསོག་པ་ཁོ་ན་ནས་འདྲ་པར་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ཡང་ན་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ / Android Auto རྣམ་པར་བརྗེ་སྐབས། ར་སྤྲོད་མཚམས་ངོས་ཡང་ན་བདེ་འཇགས་དྲན་སྐུལ་འཕར། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་བརྒྱུད་སྐུར་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས་ཡིན་པར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བདེ་འཇགས་དང་སྒེར་གསང་། དེ་ནས་སྒྲིག་ཆས་དང་གཞི་གྲངས་སྲུང་སྐྱོབ། དེ་ནས་སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།
ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 10 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se uvodi funkcija Zamućivanje privatnih podataka. Osim toga, ikone na početnom ekranu se mogu sakriti. Kombinacije aplikacija na podijeljenom ekranu se mogu sačuvati. Provjera autentičnosti korisnika je obavezna prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze. Ovo izdanje također uključuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zamućivanje privatnih podataka">
<feature>Odaberite sliku i dodirnite opciju Dijeli -> Zamućivanje privatnih podataka. Zatim će se slika profila, nadimak, broj telefona i drugi osjetljivi podaci na slici automatski zamutiti. Cilj je zaštita vaše privatnosti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Višeprozorno">
<feature>Sada se mogu pohranjivati kombinacije aplikacija u načinu rada s podijeljenim ekranom. Dok ste u načinu rada s podijeljenim ekranom dodirnite dugme na sredini razdjelnika da sačuvate kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirom na ikonu možete brzo pristupiti sačuvanoj kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Početni ekran">
<feature>Magična kapsula se može uključiti ili isključiti u određenim sistemskim uslugama. Idite u Postavke > Obavještenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula da isprobate tu opciju.
Raspored, efekat kretanja i efekat prikaza ikona na panelu za obavještenja su optimizirani u određenim scenarijima.
Dugo pritisnite ikonu aplikacije da brzo odete u postavke dozvola.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Obavezna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze. Kada odaberete opciju Prenošenje fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android automatski umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, prikazuje se upit za potvrdu ili sigurnosni upit, čime se omogućava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Sada možete sakriti ikone početnog ekrana. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrivanje aplikacija s početnog ekrana.
Sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (oktobar 2024.) je ugrađena radi sigurnosti sistema. Za više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima, posjetite našu web lokaciju https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització introdueix la funció Desenfocar la informació privada. A més, les icones de la pantalla inicial es poden amagar. Es poden desar combinacions d'aplicacions en mode de pantalla dividida. Cal que els usuaris s'autentiquin quan vulguin canviar a la connexió USB. Aquesta versió també incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Us recomanem que l'actualitzeu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desenfocar la informació privada">
<feature>Seleccioneu una imatge i toqueu Compartir -> Desenfocar la informació privada. A continuació, la foto de perfil, el sobrenom, el número de telèfon i altres dades confidencials de la imatge es desenfocaran automàticament per tal de protegir la vostra privacitat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Diverses finestres">
<feature>Ara, les combinacions en el mode de pantalla dividida es poden desar. En el mode de pantalla dividida, toqueu el botó situat al centre del separador per desar la combinació com una icona a la pantalla inicial. Toqueu la icona per habilitar l'accés ràpid a la combinació.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pantalla inicial">
<feature>Càpsula màgica es pot activar o desactivar en alguns serveis del sistema. Aneu a Configuració > Notificacions i barra d'estat > Càpsula màgica per provar-ho.
El disseny, l'efecte de moviment i l'efecte de visualització d'icones del tauler de notificacions estan optimitzats en determinades situacions.
Deixeu premuda la icona d'una aplicació per anar ràpidament a la configuració dels permisos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan es canvia la connexió USB. Apareix una indicació de verificació o de seguretat quan seleccioneu Transferir fotos o Transferir fitxers/Android Auto, en lloc de Només carregar, per tal que la transferència de dades sigui més segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>Ara podeu amagar les icones de la pantalla inicial. Proveu-ho des de: Configuració > Seguretat i privacitat > Protecció del dispositiu i de les dades > Amagar aplicacions de la Pantalla inicial.
S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (octubre del 2024) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, visiteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace zavádí funkci Rozmazat soukromé údaje. Ikony domovské obrazovky lze navíc skrýt. Kombinace aplikací v režimu rozdělené obrazovky lze uložit. Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Toto vydání obsahuje také opravu zabezpečení. Doporučujeme aktualizovat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rozmazat soukromé údaje">
<feature>Vyberte obrázek a klepněte na Sdílet -> Rozmazat soukromé údaje. Profilový obrázek, přezdívka, telefonní číslo a další citlivá data na obrázku budou automaticky rozmazány. Cílem je ochrana vašeho soukromí.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Více oken">
<feature>Kombinace aplikací v režimu rozdělené obrazovky lze nyní uložit. V režimu rozdělené obrazovky klepnutím na tlačítko uprostřed oddělovače uložte kombinaci jako ikonu na domovské obrazovce. Klepnutím na ikonu zapnete rychlý přístup ke kombinaci.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Domovská obrazovka">
<feature>Magickou kapsli lze zapnout nebo vypnout v některých systémových službách. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Oznámení a stavový řádek > Magická kapsle.
Rozložení, efekt pohybu a efekt zobrazení ikon panelu oznámení jsou v některých scénářích optimalizovány.
Dlouhým stisknutím ikony aplikace rychle přejdete do nastavení oprávnění.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Když vyberete možnost Přenos fotografií nebo Přenos souborů / Android Auto namísto možnosti Nabíjení, zobrazí se výzva k ověření nebo výzva zabezpečení, což zajistí bezpečnější přenos dat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Nyní můžete skrýt ikony domovské obrazovky. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Zabezpečení a soukromí > Ochrana zařízení a dat > Skrýt aplikace na domovské obrazovce.
Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (říjen 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne opdatering introducerer funktionen Slør private oplysninger. Desuden kan startskærmsikoner skjules. Appkombinationer i tilstanden med opdelt skærm kan gemmes. Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål. Denne udgave integrerer også en sikkerhedsrettelse. Opdatering anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Slør private oplysninger">
<feature>Vælg et billede, og tryk på Del -> Slør private oplysninger. Så vil profilbilledet, kaldenavnet, telefonnummeret og andre følsomme data på billedet automatisk blive sløret. Dette er for at beskytte dine personlige oplysninger.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-vindue">
<feature>Appkombinationer i tilstanden Opdelt skærm kan nu gemmes. I tilstanden Opdelt skærm skal du trykke på knappen midt på deleren for at gemme kombinationerne som et ikon på startskærmen. Ved at trykke på ikonet aktiverer du hurtig adgang til kombinationen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startskærm">
<feature>Magisk kapsel kan slås til og fra i nogle systemtjenester. Gå til Indstillinger > Notifikationer og statuslinje > Magisk kapsel for at prøve det.
Meddelelsespanelets layout, bevægelseseffekt og ikonvisningseffekt er blevet optimeret i nogle scenarier.
Et langt tryk på et appikon for hurtigt at gå til tilladelsesindstillingerne.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål. En bekræftelses- eller sikkerhedsprompt bliver vist, når du vælger Overfør fotos eller Overfør filer / Android Auto i stedet for Oplad kun, hvilket garanterer sikrere dataoverførsel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Nu kan du skjule startskærmsikoner. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Sikkerhed og personlige oplysninger > Enhed og databeskyttelse > Skjul apps på Startskærmen.
Android sikkerhedsrettelse (okt 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung führt die Funktion „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“ ein. Darüber hinaus können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden. App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können gespeichert werden. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Dieses Version enthält auch einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen">
<feature>Wählen Sie ein Bild aus und tippen Sie auf „Teilen“ -> „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“. Das Profilbild, der Spitzname, die Telefonnummer und andere vertrauliche Daten im Bild werden automatisch unscharf gemacht. Dies dient dem Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm">
<feature>Magic Capsule kann in einigen System-Services ein- oder ausgeschaltet werden. Gehen Sie zu Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen und Statusleiste > Magic Capsule, um es auszuprobieren.
Das Layout, der Bewegungseffekt und der Symbolanzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds werden in einigen Szenarien optimiert.
Drücken Sie lange auf ein App-Symbol, um schnell zu den Berechtigungseinstellungen zu gelangen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung führt die Funktion „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“ ein. Darüber hinaus können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden. App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können gespeichert werden. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Dieses Version enthält auch einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen">
<feature>Wählen Sie ein Bild aus und tippen Sie auf „Teilen“ -> „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“. Das Profilbild, der Spitzname, die Telefonnummer und andere vertrauliche Daten im Bild werden automatisch unscharf gemacht. Dies dient dem Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm">
<feature>Magic Capsule kann in einigen System-Services ein- oder ausgeschaltet werden. Gehen Sie zu Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen und Statusleiste > Magic Capsule, um es auszuprobieren.
Das Layout, der Bewegungseffekt und der Symbolanzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds werden in einigen Szenarien optimiert.
Drücken Sie lange auf ein App-Symbol, um schnell zu den Berechtigungseinstellungen zu gelangen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung führt die Funktion „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“ ein. Darüber hinaus können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden. App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können gespeichert werden. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Dieses Version enthält auch einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen">
<feature>Wählen Sie ein Bild aus und tippen Sie auf „Teilen“ -> „Persönliche Informationen unscharf machen“. Das Profilbild, der Spitzname, die Telefonnummer und andere vertrauliche Daten im Bild werden automatisch unscharf gemacht. Dies dient dem Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm">
<feature>Magic Capsule kann in einigen System-Services ein- oder ausgeschaltet werden. Gehen Sie zu Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen und Statusleiste > Magic Capsule, um es auszuprobieren.
Das Layout, der Bewegungseffekt und der Symbolanzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds werden in einigen Szenarien optimiert.
Drücken Sie lange auf ein App-Symbol, um schnell zu den Berechtigungseinstellungen zu gelangen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση εισάγει τη δυνατότητα «Θάμπωμα ιδιωτικών πληροφοριών». Επιπλέον, είναι δυνατή η απόκρυψη των εικονιδίων της αρχικής οθόνης. Οι συνδυασμοί εφαρμογών σε λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης μπορούν να αποθηκευτούν. Απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB. Αυτή η έκδοση ενσωματώνει επίσης μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Συνιστάται η ενημέρωση.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Θάμπωμα ιδιωτικών πληροφοριών">
<feature>Επιλέξτε μια εικόνα και πατήστε Κοινή χρήση -> Θάμπωμα ιδιωτικών πληροφοριών. Η εικόνα προφίλ, το ψευδώνυμο, ο αριθμός τηλεφώνου και άλλα ευαίσθητα δεδομένα στην εικόνα θα θαμπώσουν αυτόματα. Αυτό γίνεται για την προστασία του απορρήτου σας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Πολλαπλά παράθυρα">
<feature>Οι συνδυασμοί εφαρμογών σε λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης μπορούν πλέον να αποθηκευτούν. Στη λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης, πατήστε το κουμπί στη μέση του διαχωριστικού για να αποθηκεύσετε τον συνδυασμό ως εικονίδιο στην αρχική οθόνη. Πατήστε το εικονίδιο για γρήγορη πρόσβαση στον συνδυασμό.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Αρχική οθόνη">
<feature>Η Μαγική κάψουλα μπορεί να ενεργοποιηθεί ή να απενεργοποιηθεί σε ορισμένες υπηρεσίες συστήματος. Μεταβείτε στις Ρυθμίσεις > Ειδοποιήσεις και γραμμή κατάστασης > Μαγική κάψουλα για να δοκιμάσετε τη λειτουργία.
Η διάταξη, το εφέ κίνησης και το εφέ εμφάνισης εικονιδίων του πίνακα ειδοποιήσεων βελτιστοποιήθηκαν σε ορισμένα σενάρια.
Πατήστε παρατεταμένα ένα εικονίδιο εφαρμογής για να μεταβείτε γρήγορα στις ρυθμίσεις αδειών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB. Ένα μήνυμα επαλήθευσης ή ασφάλειας εμφανίζεται όταν επιλέγετε «Μεταφορά φωτογραφιών» ή «Μεταφορά αρχείων/Android Auto», αντί για «Μόνο φόρτιση», εξασφαλίζοντας πιο ασφαλή μεταφορά δεδομένων.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Πλέον μπορείτε να αποκρύψετε τα εικονίδια της αρχικής οθόνης. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Ασφάλεια και απόρρητο > Προστασία συσκευής και δεδομένων > Απόκρυψη εφαρμογών από την Αρχική οθόνη.
Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Οκτώβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update introduces Blur Private Info feature. Additionally, home screen icons can be hidden. App combinations in split-screen mode can be saved. User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. This release also incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blur Private Info">
<feature>Select an image and tap Share -> Blur Private Info. The profile picture, nickname, phone number and other sensitive data in the image will be automatically blurred. This is to protect your privacy.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App combinations in split-screen mode can now be saved. In split-screen mode, tap the button in the middle of the divider to save the combination as an icon on the home screen. Tap the icon enables quick access to the combination.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen">
<feature>Magic Capsule can be switched on or turned off in some system services. Go to Settings > Notifications and status bar > Magic Capsule to try it out.
The layout, motion effect and icon display effect of the notification panel are optimised in some scenarios.
Long press an app icon to quickly go to permission settings.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>You can now hide home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen.
Android Security Patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización presenta la funcionalidad Desenfocar información privada. Además, se pueden ocultar los iconos de la pantalla principal. Se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Esta versión también incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desenfocar información privada">
<feature>Seleccione una imagen y toque Compartir -> Desenfocar información privada. La foto de perfil, el apodo, el número de teléfono y otros datos confidenciales en la imagen se difuminarán automáticamente. Se usa para proteger su privacidad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Ahora se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. En el modo de pantalla dividida, toque el botón en el medio del divisor para guardar la combinación como un icono en la pantalla principal. Al pulsar el icono se habilita el acceso rápido a la combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pantalla principal">
<feature>Magic Capsule se puede activar o desactivar en algunos servicios del sistema. Vaya a Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Magic Capsule para probarlo.
Se han optimizado el diseño, el efecto de movimiento y el efecto de visualización de iconos del panel de notificaciones en algunos escenarios.
Mantenga pulsado el icono de una aplicación para ir rápidamente a los ajustes de permisos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Ahora puede ocultar los iconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección de dispositivos y datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal.
Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización implementa la funcionalidad Desenfocar la información privada. Además, se pueden ocultar los íconos de la pantalla principal. Se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Esta versión también incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desenfocar la información privada">
<feature>Seleccione una imagen y toque Compartir -> Desenfocar la información privada. La foto de perfil, el apodo, el número de teléfono y otros datos confidenciales en la imagen se difuminarán automáticamente. Se usa para proteger su privacidad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Ahora se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. En el modo de pantalla dividida, presione el botón en el medio del divisor para guardar la combinación como un ícono en la pantalla principal. Al presionar el ícono se habilita el acceso rápido a la combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pantalla principal">
<feature>Magic Capsule puede activarse o desactivarse en algunos servicios del sistema. Vaya a Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Magic Capsule para probarlo.
Se optimizaron el diseño, el efecto de movimiento y el efecto de visualización de íconos del panel de notificaciones en algunos escenarios.
Mantenga presionado el ícono de una aplicación para ir rápidamente a los ajustes de permisos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Ahora puede ocultar los íconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección de dispositivos y datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal.
Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus lisab Privaatse teabe hägustamise funktsiooni. Lisaks saab peidab avakuva ikoonid. Jagatud ekraani režiimis saab rakenduste kombinatsioone salvestada. Ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. See värskendus sisaldab ka turvapaika. Soovitatav on värskendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Privaatse teabe hägustamine">
<feature>Valige pilt ja puudutage Jaga -> Privaatse teabe hägustamine. Profiilipilt, hüüdnimi, telefoninumber ja muud pildil olevad tundlikud andmed hägustatakse automaatselt. Selle eesmärk on kaitsta teie privaatsust.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mitu akent">
<feature>Jagatud ekraani režiimis saab nüüd rakenduste kombinatsioone salvestada. Puudutage jagatud ekraani režiimis eraldusjoone keskel olevat nuppu, et kombinatsioon ikoonina avakuvale salvestada. Ikooni puudutamisel avaneb kohe sama kombinatsioon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Avakuva">
<feature>Maagilise kapsli saab teatud süsteemiteenustes sisse või välja lülitada. Proovimiseks avage Sätted > Teavitused ja olekuriba > Maagiline kapsel.
Teatud olukordades optimeeritakse teavituspaneeli paigutust, liikumisefekti ja ikoonide kuvaefekti.
Rakenduse ikooni pikalt puudutades avate lubade sätted.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>Ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. Kui valite funktsiooni Ainult laadimine asemel Fotode edastamine või Failide edastamine / Android Auto, kuvatakse kinnitus- või turvaviip, mis tagab turvalisema andmeedastuse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>Nüüd saate avakuva ikoonid ära peita. Proovige seda, minnes menüüsse Sätted > Turve ja privaatsus > Seadme- ja andmekaitse > Peida avakuval olevad rakendused.
Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (oktoober 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, eguneratze honetan Lausotu informazio pribatua funtzioa gehitu da. Gainera, hasierako pantailaren ikonoak ezkutatu egin daitezke. Aplikazio-konbinazioak zatitutako pantailaren moduan gorde daitezke. Erabiltzailea autentifikatu behar da USB konexioa aldatzean. Bertsio honetan segurtasun-adabaki bat ere gehitu da. Eguneratzea gomendatzen da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lausotu informazio pribatua">
<feature>Aukeratu irudi bat eta sakatu Partekatu -> Lausotu informazio pribatua. Profilaren argazkia, ezizena, telefono-zenbakia eta irudiaren isilpeko beste datu batzuk automatikoki lausotuko dira, pribatutasuna babesteko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leiho anitz">
<feature>Orain, aplikazioen konbinazioak zatitutako pantaila moduan gorde daitezke. Zatitutako pantaila moduan, zatitzailearen erdian dagoen botoia ukitu, hasierako pantailan konbinazioa ikono gisa gordetzeko. Ikonoa ukitzeak konbinaziorako sarbide azkarra izateko aukera ematen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hasierako pantaila">
<feature>Kapsula magikoa beste zerbitzu batzuetan aktiba edo desaktiba daiteke. Probatzeko, joan Ezarpenak > Jakinarazpenak eta egoera-barra > Kapsula magikoa atalera.
Jakinarazpen-panelaren diseinua, mugimendu-efektua eta ikonoa bistaratzeko efektua optimizatu egin dira egoera batzuetan.
Sakatu luze aplikazioaren ikono bat baimenen ezarpenetara joateko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa beharrezkoa da USB bidezko konexiora aldatzen duzunean. Egiaztapen- edo segurtasun-gonbita bat bistaratuko da Transferitu argazkiak edo Transferitu fitxategiak / Android Auto aukera hautatzen duzunean, Kargatu bakarrik aukeratu beharrean; horri esker datuok segurtasunez transferituko dira.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Orain hasierako pantailaren ikonoak ezkuta ditzakezu. Proba ezazu hona joanda: Ezarpenak > Segurtasuna eta pribatutasuna > Gailuen eta datuen babesa > Ezkutatu hasierako pantailako aplikazioak.
Sistemaren segurtasunerako, Androiden segurtasun-adabakia gehitu da (Oct 2024). HONOR segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, bisitatu gure webgunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی، قابلیت جدید «تار کردن اطلاعات خصوصی» را معرفی می‌کند. علاوه بر این، آیکون‌های صفحۀ اصلی را می‌توان پنهان کرد. ترکیب‌ برنامه‌ها در حالت تقسیم صفحه را می‌توان ذخیره کرد. هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر الزامی است. این نسخه همچنین حاوی یک وصله امنیتی است. توصیه می‌شود این به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تار کردن اطلاعات خصوصی">
<feature>تصویری را انتخاب کنید و روی «اشتراک‌گذاری > تار کردن اطلاعات خصوصی» ضربه بزنید. پس از انجام این کار، عکس نمایه، نام خودمانی، شماره تلفن و سایر داده‌های حساس موجود در تصویر به‌طور خودکار تار می‌شوند. این کار برای محافظت از حریم خصوصی شما انجام می‌شود.</feature>
</features>
<features module="پنجره‌ها">
<feature>اکنون ترکیب برنامه‌ها در حالت تقسیم صفحه را می‌توان ذخیره کرد. در حالت تقسیم صفحه، روی دکمه وسط تقسیم‌کننده ضربه بزنید تا آن ترکیب به‌صورت آیکونی در صفحۀ اصلی ذخیره شود. با ضربه زدن روی آیکون، امکان دسترسی سریع به ترکیب فراهم می‌شود.</feature>
</features>
<features module="صفحۀ اصلی">
<feature>‏«‏کپسول جادویی» را می‌توان در برخی از سرویس‌های سیستم روشن یا خاموش کرد. برای امتحان کردن آن، به «تنظیمات > اعلان‌ها و نوار وضعیت > کپسول جادویی» بروید.
چیدمان، جلوه حرکت و جلوه نمایش آیکون پانل اعلانات در برخی شرایط بهینه شده است.
برای رفتن سریع به تنظیمات مجوز، آیکون برنامه را فشار دهید و نگه دارید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر نیاز است. هنگامی‌که «انتقال تصاویر» یا «انتقال فایل‌ها / Android Auto» را به‌جای «فقط شارژ» انتخاب می‌کنید، یک پیام‌واره تأیید یا امنیتی ظاهر می‌شود تا داده‌های خود را با امنیت بیشتری انتقال دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>اکنون می توانید آیکون‌های صفحۀ اصلی را پنهان کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: تنظیمات > امنیت و حریم خصوصی > محافظت از دستگاه و داده‌ها > پنهان کردن برنامه‌ها از «صفحۀ اصلی».
وصله امنیتی Android (اکتبر ۲۰۲۴) برای امنیت سیستم گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر درباره به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به نشانی https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 مراجعه کنید</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys lisää Sumenna yksityiset tiedot -ominaisuuden. Lisäksi aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet voidaan piilottaa. Jaetun näytön tilassa käytetyt sovellusyhdistelmät voidaan tallentaa. Käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitännän tarkoitusta vaihdetaan. Tämä päivitys sisältää myös turvallisuuskorjauksen. Päivittämistä suositellaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sumenna yksityiset tiedot">
<feature>Valitse kuva ja napauta kohtaa Jaa -> Sumenna yksityiset tiedot. Profiilikuva, lempinimi, puhelinnumero ja muut kuvan arkaluontoiset tiedot sumennetaan automaattisesti. Tämä tehdään tietosuojasi turvaamiseksi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Moni-ikkuna">
<feature>Jaetun näytön tilassa käytetyt sovellusyhdistelmät voidaan nyt tallentaa. Tallenna yhdistelmä kuvakkeena aloitusnäytölle napauttamalla jakajan keskellä olevaa painiketta. Kuvaketta napauttamalla voit käyttää yhdistelmää nopeasti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aloitusnäyttö">
<feature>Magic-kapseli voidaan kytkeä päälle tai pois päältä joissakin järjestelmäpalveluissa. Kokeile sitä menemällä kohtaan Asetukset > Ilmoitukset ja tilapalkki > Magic-kapseli.
Ilmoituspaneelin asettelu, liiketehoste ja kuvakkeiden näyttötehoste on optimoitu joissakin tilanteissa.
Voit siirtyä lupa-asetuksiin nopeasti painamalla sovelluskuvaketta pitkään.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitännän tarkoitusta vaihdetaan. Kun valitset Siirrä valokuvia tai Siirrä tiedostoja / Android Auto sen sijaan, että valitsisit Vain lataus -vaihtoehdon, tarkastus- tai turvallisuuskehote avautuu, mikä varmistaa turvallisemman tiedonsiirron.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Voit nyt piilottaa aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet. Kokeile sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Turvallisuus ja tietosuoja > Laitteen ja tietojen suojaus > Piilota sovellukset aloitusnäytöltä.
Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (lokakuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour présente la fonctionnalité Flouter les informations privées. De plus, les icônes de l'écran d'accueil peuvent être masquées. Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent être enregistrées. L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Cette version intègre également un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flouter les informations privées">
<feature>Sélectionnez une image et appuyez sur Partager -> Flouter les informations privées. La photo de profil, le surnom, le numéro de téléphone et d'autres données sensibles de l'image seront automatiquement floutés. Cette mesure est destinée à protéger votre vie privée.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent désormais être enregistrées. En mode partition d'écran, appuyez sur le bouton au milieu du séparateur pour enregistrer la combinaison sous forme d'icône sur l'écran d'accueil. Appuyez sur l'icône pour accéder rapidement à la combinaison.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Écran d'accueil">
<feature>Magic Capsule peut être activée ou désactivée dans certains services système. Accédez à Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Magic Capsule pour l'essayer.
La disposition, l'effet de mouvement et l'effet d'affichage des icônes du panneau de notifications sont optimisés dans certains scénarios.
Appuyez longuement sur l'icône d'une application pour accéder rapidement aux paramètres d'autorisation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour présente la fonctionnalité Flouter les informations privées. De plus, les icônes de l'écran d'accueil peuvent être masquées. Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent être enregistrées. L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Cette version intègre également un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flouter les informations privées">
<feature>Sélectionnez une image et appuyez sur Partager -> Flouter les informations privées. La photo de profil, le surnom, le numéro de téléphone et d'autres données sensibles de l'image seront automatiquement floutés. Cette mesure est destinée à protéger votre vie privée.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent désormais être enregistrées. En mode partition d'écran, appuyez sur le bouton au milieu du séparateur pour enregistrer la combinaison sous forme d'icône sur l'écran d'accueil. Appuyez sur l'icône pour accéder rapidement à la combinaison.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Écran d'accueil">
<feature>Magic Capsule peut être activée ou désactivée dans certains services système. Accédez à Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Magic Capsule pour l'essayer.
La disposition, l'effet de mouvement et l'effet d'affichage des icônes du panneau de notifications sont optimisés dans certains scénarios.
Appuyez longuement sur l'icône d'une application pour accéder rapidement aux paramètres d'autorisation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización introduce a funcionalidade Desenfocar a información privada. Ademais, as iconas da Pantalla de inicio poden ocultarse. As combinacións de aplicacións no modo pantalla dividida poden gardarse. A autenticación de usuarios é precisa cando se cambia o propósito da conexión USB. Esta versión tamén incorpora un parche de seguranza. Recoméndase instalar a actualización.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desenfocar a información privada">
<feature>Seleccione a imaxe e toque Compartir -> Desenfocar a información privada. A imaxe de perfil, o alcume, o número de teléfono e outros datos confidenciais da imaxe desenfocaranse automaticamente para protexer a súa privacidade.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Múltiples ventás">
<feature>As combinacións de aplicacións no modo pantalla dividida agora poden gardarse. No modo pantalla dividida, toque o botón no medio do divisor para gardar a combinación como unha icona na Pantalla de inicio. Ao tocar a icona terase acceso rápido á combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pantalla de inicio">
<feature>Cápsula máxica pode activarse ou desactivarse nalgúns servizos do sistema. Para probalo, vaia a Configuración > Notificacións e barra de estado > Cápsula máxica.
O deseño, o efecto de movemento e o efecto de visualización de iconas do panel de notificacións optimizáronse nalgunhas situacións.
Manteña pulsada a icona dunha aplicación para ir rapidamente á configuración de permisos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Requírese a autenticación do usuario ao cambiar de conexión USB. Aparece unha mensaxe de verificación ou seguranza ao seleccionar Transferir fotos ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, en lugar de Só carga, o que garante unha transferencia de datos máis segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Agora pode ocultar as iconas da Pantalla de inicio. Pode probalo indo a: Configuración > Seguranza e privacidade > Dispositivo e protección de datos > Ocultar aplicacións de Pantalla de inicio.
Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (outubro 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ ખાનગી માહિતીને અસ્પષ્ટ કરો સુવિધા રજૂ કરે છે. વધુમાં, હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નો છુપાવી શકાય છે. વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં એપ્લિકેશન સંયોજનો સાચવી શકાય છે. USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. આ પ્રકાશનમાં સુરક્ષા પેચ પણ સામેલ છે. અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ખાનગી માહિતીને અસ્પષ્ટ કરો">
<feature>એક છબી પસંદ કરો અને શેર કરો -> ખાનગી માહિતીને અસ્પષ્ટ કરો પર ટૅપ​કરો. પ્રોફાઇલ ચિત્ર, ઉપનામ, ફોન નંબર અને છબીમાંનો અન્ય સંવેદનશીલ ડેટા આપમેળે અસ્પષ્ટ થઈ જાશે. આ તમારી ગોપનીયતાને સુરક્ષિત રાખવા માટે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="મલ્ટિ-વિન્ડો">
<feature>વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં એપ્લિકેશન સંયોજનો હવે સાચવી શકાય છે. વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં, હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર સંયોજનને ચિહ્ન તરીકે સાચવવા માટે વિભાજકની મધ્યમાં આવેલ બટનને ટૅપ કરો. ચિહ્ન પર ટૅપ કરવાથી સંયોજનનો ઝડપી ઍક્સેસ સક્ષમ બને છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીન">
<feature>મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલને કેટલીક સિસ્ટમ સેવાઓમાં ચાલુ અથવા બંધ કરી શકાય છે. તેને અજમાવવા માટે સેટિંગ્સ > સૂચનાઓ અને સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી > મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ પર જાઓ.
સૂચના પૅનલનું લેઆઉટ, ગતિ પ્રભાવ અને ચિહ્ન ડિસ્પ્લે પ્રભાવ કેટલીક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરવામાં આવે છે.
પરવાનગી સેટિંગ્સ પર ઝડપથી જવા માટે એપ્લિકેશન ચિહ્નને લાંબા સમય સુધી દબાવી રાખો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. જ્યારે તમે સુરક્ષિત ડેટા ટ્રાન્સફરને સુનિશ્ચિત કરવા માટે માત્ર ચાર્જ કરોને બદલે, ફોટા ટ્રાન્સફર કરો અથવા ફાઇલો ટ્રાન્સફર કરો/ Android Auto પસંદ કરો ત્યારે ચકાસણી અથવા સુરક્ષા પ્રોમ્પ્ટ દેખાય છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>તમે હવે હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન છુપાવી શકો છો. આના પર જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > સુરક્ષા અને ગોપનીયતા > ઉપકરણ અને ડેટા સુરક્ષા > હોમ સ્ક્રીન પરથી એપ્લિકેશન્સ છુપાવો.
સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે એન્ડ્રોઇડ Android પેચ (ઓક્ટો 2024) સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से निजी जानकारी को धुँधला करें पेश किया जाता है। इसके अलावा, होम स्क्रीन आइकन छिपाए जा सकते हैं। स्क्रीन-विभाजक मोड में ऐप संयोजन सहेजे जा सकते हैं। USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। इस रिलीज़ से सुरक्षा पैच भी शामिल किया जाता है। इसे अद्यतित करने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="निजी जानकारी को धुँधला करें">
<feature>छवि चुनें और साझा करें -> निजी जानकारी को धुँधला करें पर टैप करें, उसके बाद छवि में मौजूद प्रोफ़ाइल चित्र, उपनाम, फ़ोन नंबर और अन्य संवेदनशील डेटा स्वचालित रूप से धुँधले हो जाएँगे। यह आपकी गोपनीयता की सुरक्षा के लिए है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>स्क्रीन-विभाजक मोड में ऐप संयोजन अब सहेजे जा सकते हैं। स्क्रीन-विभाजक मोड में, संयोजन को होम स्क्रीन पर आइकन के रूप में सहेजने के लिए विभाजक के बीच में बटन पर टैप करें। आइकन पर टैप करने से संयोजन तक त्वरित पहुँच सक्षम हो जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन">
<feature>कुछ सिस्टम सेवाओं में मैजिक कैप्सूल को चालू या बंद किया जा सकता है। इसे आज़माने के लिए, सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचनाएँ और स्थिति बार > मैजिक कैप्सूल पर जाएँ।
कुछ परिदृश्यों में अधिसूचना पैनल के लेआउट, गति प्रभाव और आइकन डिस्प्ले प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया गया है।
अनुमति सेटिंग्स पर तुरंत जाने के लिए ऐप के ​आइकन को देर तक दबाएँ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। जब आप सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करने के लिए केवल चार्ज के बजाय फ़ोटो स्थानांतरित करें या फ़ाइल स्थानांतरित करें/Android Auto को चुनते हैं, तो एक सत्यापन या सुरक्षा संकेत दिखाई देता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>अब आप होम स्क्रीन के आइकन छिपा सकते हैं। इसे आज़माने के लिए यहाँ जाएँ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा और गोपनीयता > डिवाइस और डेटा सुरक्षा > ऐप्स को होम स्क्रीन से छिपाएँ।
सिस्टम सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा के अद्यतन के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uvodi značajka Zamućenje privatnih informacija. Osim toga, sada je moguće sakriti ikone s početnog zaslona. Kombinacije aplikacija u načinu podijeljenog zaslona mogu se spremiti. Potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a. Ovo izdanje uključuje i sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zamućenje privatnih informacija">
<feature>Odaberite sliku i dodirnite Podijeli -> Zamućenje privatnih informacija. Profilna slika, nadimak, telefonski broj i drugi osjetljivi podaci na slici automatski će se zamutiti. To je u svrhu zaštite privatnosti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prikaz u više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u načinu podijeljenog zaslona sada se mogu spremiti. U načinu podijeljenog zaslona dodirnite gumb na sredini razdjelnika kako biste kombinaciju spremili kao ikonu na početnom zaslonu. Dodirnite ikonu za brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Početni zaslon">
<feature>Sada možete uključiti ili isključiti Magičnu kapsulu u nekim uslugama sustava. Idite na Postavke > Obavijesti i statusna traka > Magična kapsula kako biste je isprobali.
Izgled, efekt pokreta i efekt prikaza ikona ploče za obavijesti optimizirani su u nekim scenarijima.
Dugo pritisnite ikonu aplikacije za brzi pristup postavkama dozvole.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka / Android Auto, umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, pojavljuje se upit za provjeru ili sigurnost, čime se osigurava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Sada možete sakriti ikone s početnog zaslona. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrij aplikacije s Početnog zaslona.
Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (listopad 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés bevezeti a Privát adatok elhomályosítása funkciót. Ezenfelül mostantól elrejthetők a főképernyő ikonjai. Emellett lehetővé teszi az alkalmazáskombinációk mentését osztott képernyős módban. Mostantól felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges, ha módosítani szeretné az USB-kapcsolat típusát. Ez a verzió egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Privát adatok elhomályosítása">
<feature>Válasszon ki egy képet, majd koppintson a Megosztás -> Privát adatok elhomályosítása lehetőségre. A rendszer ekkor elhomályosítja a képen szereplő profilképet, becenevet, telefonszámot és más érzékeny adatokat. Ez az Ön magánéletének a védelmét szolgálja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Többablakos">
<feature>Mostantól mentheti az alkalmazáskombinációkat osztott képernyős módban. Osztott képernyős módban koppintson az elválasztó közepén található gombra, így a főképernyőn elhelyezett ikon formájában mentheti az adott kombinációt. Ha az ikonra koppint, gyorsan megnyithatja az adott kombinációt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Főképernyő">
<feature>A Mágikus kapszula egyes rendszerszolgáltatások be- és kikapcsolható. Próbálja ki: lépjen a Beállítások > Értesítések és állapotsáv > Mágikus kapszula menüpontba.
Bizonyos körülmények között az értesítési sáv elrendezése, mozgáseffektusa és ikonmegjelenési hatása optimalizált.
Tartsa nyomva a kívánt alkalmazás ikonját, ha szeretne gyorsan a jogosultságbeállításokra ugrani.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Az USB-kapcsolat váltásakor felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ha a Csak töltés opció helyett a Fotók átvitele vagy Fájlok átvitele/Android Auto opciót választja, megjelenik egy hitelesítési vagy biztonsági üzenet, amelynek célja, hogy az adatátvitel garantáltan biztonságos legyen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Mostantól elrejtheti a főképernyő ikonjait. Próbálja ki az alábbi útvonalon: Beállítások > Biztonság és titkosítás > Készülék és adatvédelem > Alkalmazások elrejtése a főképernyőről.
A rendszerbiztonság egy Android biztonsági frissítést (2024 október) is tartalmaz. A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memperkenalkan fitur Buramkan Info Pribadi. Selain itu, ikon layar beranda dapat disembunyikan. Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi dapat disimpan. Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Rilis ini menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Buramkan Info Pribadi">
<feature>Pilih gambar dan ketuk Berbagi -> Buramkan Info Pribadi. Gambar profil, nama panggilan, nomor telepon, dan data sensitif lainnya akan otomatis diburamkan. Fitur ini untuk melindungi privasi Anda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi kini dapat disimpan. Di mode layar terbagi, ketuk tombol di tengah pembagi untuk menyimpan kombinasi sebagai ikon di layar beranda. Ketuk ikon untuk mengaktifkan akses cepat ke kombinasi tersebut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Layar beranda">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib dapat diaktifkan atau dinonaktifkan di beberapa layanan sistem. Buka Pengaturan > Notifikasi dan bilah status > Kapsul Ajaib untuk mencobanya.
Tata letak, efek gerak, dan efek tampilan ikon panel notifikasi dioptimalkan di beberapa skenario.
Tekan lama ikon aplikasi untuk membuka pengaturan izin dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat mengganti tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Kini, Anda dapat menyembunyikan ikon layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
Penambal Keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memperkenalkan fitur Buramkan Info Pribadi. Selain itu, ikon layar beranda dapat disembunyikan. Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi dapat disimpan. Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Rilis ini menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Buramkan Info Pribadi">
<feature>Pilih gambar dan ketuk Berbagi -> Buramkan Info Pribadi. Gambar profil, nama panggilan, nomor telepon, dan data sensitif lainnya akan otomatis diburamkan. Fitur ini untuk melindungi privasi Anda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi kini dapat disimpan. Di mode layar terbagi, ketuk tombol di tengah pembagi untuk menyimpan kombinasi sebagai ikon di layar beranda. Ketuk ikon untuk mengaktifkan akses cepat ke kombinasi tersebut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Layar beranda">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib dapat diaktifkan atau dinonaktifkan di beberapa layanan sistem. Buka Pengaturan > Notifikasi dan bilah status > Kapsul Ajaib untuk mencobanya.
Tata letak, efek gerak, dan efek tampilan ikon panel notifikasi dioptimalkan di beberapa skenario.
Tekan lama ikon aplikasi untuk membuka pengaturan izin dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat mengganti tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Kini, Anda dapat menyembunyikan ikon layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
Penambal Keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento introduce la funzione Sfoca informazioni private. Inoltre, consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home. È possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB. Questa versione incorpora anche una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sfoca informazioni private">
<feature>Seleziona un'immagine e tocca Condividi -> Sfoca informazioni private. L'immagine del profilo, il nickname, il numero di telefono e altri dati sensibili presenti nell'immagine verranno automaticamente sfocati. Lo scopo di questa funzione è proteggere la tua privacy.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>È ora possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. In modalità schermo diviso, tocca il pulsante al centro del divisore per salvare la combinazione come icona nella schermata Home. Toccando l'icona accedi rapidamente alla combinazione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Schermata Home">
<feature>È possibile attivare o disattivare Magic Capsule in alcuni servizi di sistema. Per provare la funzione, vai in Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Magic Capsule.
Il layout, l'effetto di movimento e l'effetto di visualizzazione delle icone nell'area notifiche sono ottimizzati in alcuni scenari.
Premi a lungo l'icona di un'app per accedere rapidamente alle impostazioni delle autorizzazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferire file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento introduce la funzione Sfoca informazioni private. Inoltre, consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home. È possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB. Questa versione incorpora anche una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sfoca informazioni private">
<feature>Seleziona un'immagine e tocca Condividi -> Sfoca informazioni private. L'immagine del profilo, il nickname, il numero di telefono e altri dati sensibili presenti nell'immagine verranno automaticamente sfocati. Lo scopo di questa funzione è proteggere la tua privacy.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>È ora possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. In modalità schermo diviso, tocca il pulsante al centro del divisore per salvare la combinazione come icona nella schermata Home. Toccando l'icona accedi rapidamente alla combinazione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Schermata Home">
<feature>È possibile attivare o disattivare Magic Capsule in alcuni servizi di sistema. Per provare la funzione, vai in Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Magic Capsule.
Il layout, l'effetto di movimento e l'effetto di visualizzazione delle icone nell'area notifiche sono ottimizzati in alcuni scenari.
Premi a lungo l'icona di un'app per accedere rapidamente alle impostazioni delle autorizzazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferire file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מוסיף לראשונה את התכונה 'טשטוש פרטים אישיים'. בנוסף, ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית, וכן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה משלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="טשטוש פרטים אישיים">
<feature>בחר תמונה והקש על 'שיתוף' -> 'טשטוש פרטים אישיים'. תמונת הפרופיל, הכינוי, מספר הטלפון ונתונים רגישים אחרים בתמונה יטושטשו באופן אוטומטי, זאת כדי להגן על פרטיותך.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>כעת ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. במצב מסך מפוצל, הקש על הלחצן באמצע המחלק כדי לשמור את השילוב כסמל במסך הבית. הקשה על הסמל מאפשרת גישה מהירה לשילוב.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להפעיל או לכבות את 'קפסולת קסם' בחלק משירותי המערכת. עבור אל 'הגדרות' > 'התראות ושורת המצב' > 'קפסולת קסם' כדי לנסות זאת.
הפריסה, אפקט התנועה ואפקט תצוגת הסמלים של לוח התראות ממוטבים בתרחישים מסוימים.
לחץ לחיצה ארוכה על סמל יישום כדי לעבור במהירות להגדרות ההרשאה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על התקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מוסיף לראשונה את התכונה 'טשטוש פרטים אישיים'. בנוסף, ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית, וכן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה משלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="טשטוש פרטים אישיים">
<feature>בחר תמונה והקש על 'שיתוף' -> 'טשטוש פרטים אישיים'. תמונת הפרופיל, הכינוי, מספר הטלפון ונתונים רגישים אחרים בתמונה יטושטשו באופן אוטומטי, זאת כדי להגן על פרטיותך.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>כעת ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. במצב מסך מפוצל, הקש על הלחצן באמצע המחלק כדי לשמור את השילוב כסמל במסך הבית. הקשה על הסמל מאפשרת גישה מהירה לשילוב.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להפעיל או לכבות את 'קפסולת קסם' בחלק משירותי המערכת. עבור אל 'הגדרות' > 'התראות ושורת המצב' > 'קפסולת קסם' כדי לנסות זאת.
הפריסה, אפקט התנועה ואפקט תצוגת הסמלים של לוח התראות ממוטבים בתרחישים מסוימים.
לחץ לחיצה ארוכה על סמל יישום כדי לעבור במהירות להגדרות ההרשאה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על התקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の更新では、個人情報をぼかす機能が導入されます。さらに、ホーム画面のアイコンを非表示にできるようになります。画面分割モードでのアプリの組み合わせを保存できるようになります。USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。また、今回のリリースでは、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。更新することをおすすめします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="個人情報をぼかす">
<feature>画像を選択して、[共有] -> [個人情報をぼかす]をタップします。画像内のプロフィール写真、ニックネーム、電話番号、その他の取扱に注意を要するデータが自動的にぼかされます。これでユーザーのプライバシーが保護されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="マルチウィンドウ">
<feature>画面分割モードでアプリの組み合わせを保存できるようになりました。画面分割モードで分割線の中央にあるボタンをタップすると、組み合わせをホーム画面のアイコンとして保存できます。アイコンをタップすると、その組み合わせにすばやくアクセスできます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ホーム画面">
<feature>マジックカプセルは、一部のシステムサービスでオンに切り替える、またはオフにすることができます。これを試すには、[設定] > [通知]に移動し、ステータスバー > [マジックカプセル]に移動してください。
通知パネルのレイアウト、モーション効果、アイコン表示効果は、一部の状況で最適化されます。
アプリアイコンを長押しすると、権限設定に素早く移動できます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。[充電のみ]ではなく、[写真の転送]または[ファイルの転送/Android Auto]を選択すると、認証またはセキュリティプロンプトが表示され、より安全なデータ転送が保証されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>ホーム画面のアイコンを非表示にできるようになりました。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [セキュリティとプライバシー] > [デバイスとデータ保護] > [ホーム画面でアプリを非表示]に移動してください。
システムセキュリティのために、Androidセキュリティパッチ（2024年10月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება წარმოგიდგენთ პირადი ინფორმაციის გაბუნდოვანების ფუნქციას. გარდა ამისა, შესაძლებელია საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების დამალვა. შესაძლებელია გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში აპების კომბინაციების შენახვაც. USB კავშირის მიზნის შეცვლისას საჭიროა მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. მოცემულ გამოშვებას შემოაქვს უსაფრთხოების შესწორებაც. განახლება რეკომენდებულია.</feature>
</features>
<features module="პირადი ინფორმაციის გაბუნდოვანება">
<feature>აირჩიეთ სურათი და შეეხეთ: გაზიარება -> პირადი ინფორმაციის გაბუნდოვანება. პროფილის სურათი, მეტსახელი, ტელეფონის ნომერი და სხვა სენსიტიური მონაცემები სურათზე ავტომატურად გაბუნდოვანდება. ამის მიზანია თქვენი კონფიდენციალურობის დაცვა.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მულტიფანჯარა">
<feature>ახლა შესაძლებელია აპების კომბინაციების შენახვა გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში. გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში შეეხეთ ღილაკს გამყოფის შუაში, რომ კომბინაცია საწყის ეკრანზე პიქტოგრამად შეინახოთ. პიქტოგრამაზე შეხება გაძლევთ კომბინაციაზე სწრაფ წვდომას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="საწყისი ეკრანი">
<feature>შესაძლებელია ჯადოსნური კაფსულის ჩართვა ან გამორთვა ზოგიერთ სისტემურ სერვისში. იმისათვის, რომ გამოსცადოთ, გახსენით პარამეტრები > შეტყობინებები და სტატუსის ზოლი > ჯადოსნური კაფსულა.
გარკვეულ სცენარებში ოპტიმიზდა შეტყობინებათა პანელის განლაგება, მოძრაობის ეფექტი და პიქტოგრამის ჩვენების ეფექტი.
ნებართვების პარამეტრებში სწრაფად გადასასვლელად ხანგრძლივად დააჭირეთ აპის პიქტოგრამას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>USB კავშირის გადართვის დროს აუცილებელია მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. შემოწმების ან უსაფრთხოების მოთხოვნა გამოჩნდება, როცა აირჩევთ ფოტოების გადაცემას ან ფაილების გადაცემას / Android Auto-ს, მხოლოდ დამუხტვის ნაცვლად, რაც უზრუნველყოფს მონაცემთა უსაფრთხო გადაცემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>ახლა შეგიძლიათ დამალოთ საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამები. ეს შეგიძლიათ სცადოთ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > უსაფრთხოება და კონფიდენციალურობა > მოწყობილობა და მონაცემთა დაცვა > აპების დამალვა საწყისი ეკრანიდან.
სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩართულია Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ოქტომბერი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту «Жеке ақпаратты бұлыңғырлату» мүмкіндігін ұсынады. Сондай-ақ негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыруға болады. Бөлінген экран режиміндегі қолданба тіркесімдерін сақтауға болады. USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жаңарту ұсынылады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жеке ақпаратты бұлыңғырлату">
<feature>Кескінді таңдап, «Бөлісу» -> «Жеке ақпаратты бұлыңғырлату» тармағын түртіңіз. Профиль суреті, бүркеншік ат, телефон нөмірі және кескіндегі басқа құпия деректер автоматты түрде бұлыңғырланады. Бұл құпиялығыңызды қорғау үшін қажет.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бірнеше терезе">
<feature>Енді бөлінген экран режиміндегі қолданба тіркесімдерін сақтауға болады. Бөлінген экран режимінде тіркесімді негізгі экранда белгіше ретінде сақтау үшін бөлгіштің ортасындағы түймені түртіңіз. Белгішені түртсеңіз, тіркесімге жылдам қатынасуға мүмкіндік беріледі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Басты экран">
<feature>Кейбір жүйелік қызметтерде «Сиқырлы капсула» мүмкіндігін қосуға немесе өшіруге болады. Оны пайдаланып көру үшін «Параметрлер» > «Хабарландырулар мен күй жолағы» > «Сиқырлы капсула» тармағына өтіңіз.
Кейбір сценарийлерде хабарландырулар тақтасының орналасуы, қозғалыс әсері және белгішені көрсету әсері оңтайландырылған.
Рұқсат параметрлеріне жылдам өту үшін қолданба белгішесін ұзақ басып тұрыңыз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Деректерді қауіпсіз тасымалдауды қамтамасыз ететін «Тек зарядтау» орнына «Фотосуреттерді тасымалдау» немесе «Файлдарды тасымалдау/Android Auto» параметрін таңдаған кезде растау немесе қауіпсіздік сұрауы пайда болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Енді негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыра аласыз. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Қауіпсіздік және құпиялық» > «Құрылғыны және деректерді қорғау» > «Негізгі экрандағы қолданбаларды жасыру».
Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қазан, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះណែនាំមុខងារធ្វើឱ្យ​ព័ត៌មានឯកជនព្រាល។ លើសពីនេះ រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមអាចត្រូវបានលាក់។ បន្សំុំកម្មវិធីនៅក្នុងម៉ូដអេក្រង់បំបែកអាចត្រូវបានរក្សាទុក។ តម្រូវឱ្យធ្វើការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើ នៅពេលប្ដូរគោលបំណងនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB។ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះក៏រួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខផងដែរ។ សូមណែនាំឱ្យធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ធ្វើឱ្យ​ព័ត៌មានឯកជនព្រាល">
<feature>ជ្រើសរើសរូបភាព និងប៉ះ ចែករំលែក -> ធ្វើឱ្យ​ព័ត៌មានឯកជនព្រាល។ រូបភាពប្រវត្តិរូប ឈ្មោះហៅក្រៅ លេខទូរស័ព្ទ និងទិន្នន័យដែលមានលក្ខណៈរសើបផ្សេងទៀតនៅក្នុងរូបភាពនឹងត្រូវបានធ្វើឱ្យព្រាលដោយស្វ័យប្រវត្តិ។ ការធ្វើបែបនេះគឺដើម្បីការពារឯកជនភាពរបស់អ្នក។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ពហុវិនដូ">
<feature>ឥឡូវ បន្សំកម្មវិធីក្នុងម៉ូដអេក្រង់បំបែកអាចត្រូវបានរក្សាទុក។ ក្នុងម៉ូដអេក្រង់បំបែក ប៉ះប៊ូតុងនៅផ្នែកកណ្ដាលនៃបន្ទាត់ខណ្ឌចែក ដើម្បីរក្សាទុកបន្សំជារូបតំណាងនៅលើអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។ ប៉ះរូបតំណាង បើកការចូលប្រើរហ័សទៅកាន់បន្សំ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
<feature>ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្តអាចត្រូវបានបើក ឬបិទក្នុងសេវាកម្មប្រព័ន្ធមួយចំនួន។ ចូលទៅកាន់ការកំណត់ > ការជូនដំណឹង និងរបារស្ថានភាព > ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត ដើម្បីសាកល្បងវា។
ប្លង់ បែបផែនចលនា និងបែបផែនបង្ហាញរូបតំណាងនៃផ្ទាំងជូនដំណឹងត្រូវបានធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។
សង្កត់ឱ្យយូរលើរូបតំណាងកម្មវិធី ដើម្បីចូលទៅការកំណត់ការអនុញ្ញាតបានរហ័ស។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>ការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ត្រូវបានទាមទារនៅក្នុងគោលបំណងផ្លាស់ប្តូរនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB។ ការបញ្ជាក់ ឬសារសុវត្ថិភាពបង្ហាញនៅពេលអ្នកជ្រើសរើសផ្ទេររូបថត ឬផ្ទេរឯកសារ/Android Auto ជំនួសឱ្យការសាកថ្មតែប៉ុណ្ណោះ ដែលធានាបាននូវការផ្ទេរទិន្នន័យដែលមានសុវត្ថិភាពជាងមុន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>ឥឡូវនេះ អ្នកអាចលាក់រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមបានហើយ។ សាកល្បងវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > សន្តិសុខ និងឯកជនភាព > ការការពារឧបករណ៍ និងទិន្នន័យ > លាក់កម្មវិធីពីអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។
បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (តុលា 2024) ត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូលសម្រាប់សន្តិសុខប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់ព័ត៌មានបន្ថែមអំពីបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពសន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅកាន់គេហទំព័ររបស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಖಾಸಗಿ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಮಸುಕುಗೊಳಿಸಿ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವನ್ನು ಪರಿಚಯಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗಳನ್ನು ಉಳಿಸಬಹುದು. USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಹ ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ನವೀಕರಿಸಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಖಾಸಗಿ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಮಸುಕುಗೊಳಿಸಿ">
<feature>ಚಿತ್ರವನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆಮಾಡಿ ಮತ್ತು ಹಂಚಿಕೊಳ್ಳಿ -> ಖಾಸಗಿ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಮಸುಕುಗೊಳಿಸಿ ಎಂಬುದನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ. ಪ್ರೊಫೈಲ್ ಚಿತ್ರ, ಅಡ್ಡಹೆಸರು, ಫೋನ್ ಸಂಖ್ಯೆ ಮತ್ತು ಚಿತ್ರದಲ್ಲಿರುವ ಇತರ ಸೂಕ್ಷ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಸ್ವಯಂಚಾಲಿತವಾಗಿ ಮಸುಕುಗೊಳಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ. ನಿಮ್ಮ ಗೌಪ್ಯತೆಯನ್ನು ಕಾಪಾಡಲು ಹೀಗೆ ಮಾಡಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮಲ್ಟಿ-ವಿಂಡೋ">
<feature>ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗಳನ್ನು ಈಗ ಉಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ, ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಯನ್ನು ಐಕಾನ್ ಆಗಿ ಉಳಿಸಲು ವಿಭಾಜಕದ ಮಧ್ಯದಲ್ಲಿರುವ ಬಟನ್ ಮೇಲೆ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ. ಐಕಾನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡುವುದರಿಂದ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗೆ ತ್ವರಿತ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಹೋಮ್‌ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌">
<feature>ಕೆಲವು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸೇವೆಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆನ್ ಅಥವಾ ಆಫ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಲು, ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ > ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್ ಎಂಬಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗಿ.
ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆ ಪ್ಯಾನಲ್‌ನ ಲೇಔಟ್, ಮೋಷನ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಮತ್ತು ಐಕಾನ್ ಡಿಸ್‌ಪ್ಲೇ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ.
ಅನುಮತಿಯ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳಿಗೆ ತ್ವರಿತವಾಗಿ ಹೋಗಲು ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಐಕಾನ್ ಅನ್ನು ದೀರ್ಘವಾಗಿ ಒತ್ತಿರಿ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ನೀವು ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಮಾತ್ರ ಎಂಬುದರ ಬದಲಿಗೆ ಫೋಟೊಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ ಅಥವಾ ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ / Android Auto ವನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಿದಾಗ ಪರಿಶೀಲನೆ ಅಥವಾ ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ರಾಂಪ್ಟ್ ಕಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಡೇಟಾ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸುರಕ್ಷತೆ">
<feature>ನೀವು ಈಗ ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಭದ್ರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಗೌಪ್ಯತೆ > ಸಾಧನ ಮತ್ತು ಡೇಟಾ ರಕ್ಷಣೆ > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌‍ನಿಂದ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಿ.
Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಅಕ್ಟೋಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트에서는 비공개 정보 흐리게 기능이 도입됩니다. 또한 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨길 수도 있습니다. 화면 분할 모드에서 앱 조합을 저장할 수 있습니다. USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 이번 릴리스에는 보안 패치도 포함되어 있습니다. 업데이트하는 것이 좋습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="비공개 정보 흐리게">
<feature>이미지를 선택하고 공유 -> 비공개 정보 흐리게를 탭합니다. 이미지의 프로필 사진, 닉네임, 전화번호 및 기타 민감한 데이터는 자동으로 흐리게 처리됩니다. 이는 개인 정보를 보호하기 위한 것입니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="멀티 윈도우">
<feature>이제 화면 분할 모드에서 앱 조합을 저장할 수 있습니다. 화면 분할 모드에서 분할기 가운데에 있는 버튼을 탭하여 조합을 홈 화면에 아이콘으로 저장합니다. 아이콘을 탭하면 조합에 빠르게 액세스할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="홈 화면">
<feature>일부 시스템 서비스에서 매직 캡슐을 켜거나 끌 수 있습니다. 설정 > 알림 및 상태 표시줄 > 매직 캡슐로 이동하여 사용해 보세요.
알림 패널의 레이아웃, 모션 효과 및 아이콘 디스플레이 효과는 일부 시나리오에서 최적화되어 있습니다.
앱 아이콘을 길게 누르면 권한 설정으로 빠르게 이동합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 충전 전용 대신 사진 전송 또는 파일 전송/Android Auto를 선택하면 인증 또는 보안 메시지가 표시되어 더욱 안전하게 데이터를 전송할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>이제 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨길 수 있습니다. 설정 > 보안 및 개인 정보 보호 > 장치 및 데이터 보호 > 홈 화면에서 앱 숨기기로 이동하여 사용해 보십시오.
시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 10월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ແນະ​ນຳ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດມົວຂໍ້​​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ. ນອກ​ຈາກ​ນີ້, ຍັງ​ສາ​ມາດ​ເຊື່ອງໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກໄດ້. ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກການ​ລວມ​ແອັບ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ​ໄ​ດ້. ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ນອກນັ້ນ​ ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວນີ້​ຍັງ​ລວມ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນນຳ. ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ອັບ​ເດດ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ມົວຂໍ້​​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ">
<feature>ເລືອກ​ຮູບ​ພາບ ແລະ ແຕະ ແຊ​ຣ໌ -> ມົວຂໍ້​​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ. ຮູບ​ໂປ​ຣ​ໄຟ​ລ໌, ຊື່ຫຼິ້ນ, ເບີ​ໂທ​ລະ​ສັບ ແລະ ຂໍ້ມູນທີ່ລະ​ອຽດອ່ອນ​ອື່ນໆ​ໃນ​ຮູ​ບ​ພາບ​ຈະ​ຖືກ​ມົວ​ໂດຍ​ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ. ສິ່ງ​ນີ້​ແມ່ນ​ເພື່ອ​ປົກ​ປ້ອງ​ຄວາມ​ເປັນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຫຼາຍ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກການ​ລວມ​ແອັບ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ​ໄ​ດ້​ແລ້ວ. ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ, ແຕະ​ປຸ່ມ​ຢູ່​ກາງ​ຕົວ​ແບ່ງ ເພື່ອ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ການ​ລວມ​ເປັນ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ. ແຕະ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານການ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ດ່ວນຫາ​ການ​ລວມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ">
<feature>ສາ​ມາດ​ເປີດ ຫຼື ປິດແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກໃນ​ບາງ​ການ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການລະ​ບົບ​ໄດ້. ໄປ​ທີ່ ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ ແລະ ແຖບ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ > ແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກ ເພື່ອ​​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ເບິ່ງ.
ແຜ​ນ​ຜັງ, ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ ແລະ ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ສ​ະ​ແດງ​ຜົນ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ຂອງ​ແຜງ​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ຖືກ​ປັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ.
ກົດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ແອັບ​ຄ້າງ​ໄວ້​ເພື່ອ​ໄປ​ທີ່​ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ​ການ​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ຢ່າງ​ໄວ​ວາ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ການກວດ​ສອບ ຫຼື ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ປະ​ກົດຂຶ້ນ​ເມື່ອ​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ ໂອນ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ ຫຼື ໂອນ​ໄຟ​ລ໌ / Android ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ, ແທນ​ການ​ສາກ​ເທົ່າ​ນັ້ນ, ເຊິ່ງ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ການ​ໂອນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ທີ່​ປອດ​ໄພ​ກວ່າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ເຊື່ອງ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ແລະ ຄວາມ​ເປັນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ > ການ​ປົກ​ປ້ອງ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ ແລະ ຂໍ້​ມູນ > ເຊື່ອງ​ແອັບຈາກໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​.
ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ຕຸ​ລາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo naujiniu pristatoma privačios informacijos suliejimo funkcija. Be to, galima paslėpti pradžios ekrano piktogramas. Padalintojo ekrano režimu galima įrašyti programėlių derinius. Keičiant USB jungties paskirtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Į šią versiją taip pat įtraukta saugumo pataisa. Rekomenduojama atnaujinti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Privačios informacijos suliejimas">
<feature>Pasirinkite vaizdą ir palieskite „Bendrinti -> Sulieti privačią informaciją”. Tada profilio nuotrauka, slapyvardis, telefono numeris ir kiti vaizde esantys neskelbtini duomenys bus automatiškai sulieti. Taip siekiama saugoti jūsų privatumą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Daugialangis">
<feature>Nuo šiol galima įrašyti padalintojo ekrano režimu sukurtus programėlių derinius. Įjungę padalintojo ekrano režimą, palieskite skyriklio viduryje esantį mygtuką ir galėsite įrašyti derinį kaip piktogramą pradžios ekrane. Palietę piktogramą, galėsite greitai pasiekti derinį.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pradžios ekranas">
<feature>Stebuklingąją kapsulę galima įjungti arba išjungti kai kuriose sisteminėse paslaugose. Norėdami tai išbandyti, eikite į „Nuostatos > Pranešimai ir būsenos juosta > Stebuklingoji kapsulė“.
Kai kuriais atvejais optimizuojamas pranešimų skydelio išdėstymas, judesio efektas ir piktogramų rodymo efektas.
Norėdami greitai pereiti į leidimų nuostatas, paspauskite ir palaikykite programėlės piktogramą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Keičiant USB jungties paskirtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Pasirinkus „Persiųsti nuotraukas“ arba „Persiųsti failus („Android Auto“)“, o ne „Tik įkrauti“, pateikiamas patvirtinimo arba saugumo raginimas, užtikrinantis saugesnį duomenų persiuntimą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Nuo šiol galėsite paslėpti pradžios ekrano piktogramas. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos > Saugumas ir privatumas > Įrenginio ir duomenų apsauga > Slėpti programėles iš pradžios ekrano“.
Sistemos saugumui užtikrinti buvo įdiegta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. spalio mėn.). Daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius rasite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu tiek ieviesta funkcija Aizmiglot privāto informāciju. Turklāt sākuma ekrāna ikonas var paslēpt. Lietotņu kombinācijas dalītā ekrāna režīmā var saglabāt. Pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Šajā laidienā ir iekļauts arī drošības ielāps. Ieteicams atjaunināt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aizmiglot privāto informāciju">
<feature>Atlasiet attēlu un pieskarieties Kopīgot -> Aizmiglot privāto informāciju. Profila attēls, segvārds, tālruņa numurs un citi sensitīvie dati attēlā tiks automātiski aizmigloti. Tas ir paredzēts jūsu konfidencialitātes aizsardzībai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vairāki logi">
<feature>Lietotņu kombinācijas dalītā ekrāna režīmā var tagad saglabāt. Dalītā ekrāna režīmā pieskarieties pogai sadalītāja vidū, lai saglabātu kombināciju kā ikonu sākuma ekrānā. Pieskarieties ikonai, lai ātri piekļūtu kombinācijai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sākuma ekrāns">
<feature>Maģijas kapsula varat ieslēgt vai izslēgt dažos sistēmas pakalpojumos. Atveriet Iestatījumi > Paziņojumi un statusa josla > Maģijas kapsula, lai to izmēģinātu.
Dažos gadījumos paziņojumu paneļa izkārtojums, kustības efekts un ikonu parādīšanas efekts ir optimizēts.
Turiet nospiestu lietotnes ikonu, lai ātri pārietu uz atļauju iestatījumiem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Izvēloties Pārsūtīt fotoattēlus vai Pārsūtīt failus/Android Auto, nevis Tikai uzlāde, tiek parādīta verifikācijas vai drošības uzvedne, garantējot drošāku datu pārsūtīšanu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Tagad varat paslēpt sākuma ekrāna ikonas. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Drošība un konfidencialitāte > Ierīces un datu aizsardzība > Slēpt lietotnes sākuma ekrānā.
Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada oktobris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट निजी जानकारी केँ ब्लर करू प्रस्तुत करैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, होम स्क्रीन आइकन केँ नुकाओल जा सकैत अछि। विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे एप संयोजन सभ केँ संरक्षित कयल जा सकैत अछि। USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। ई रिलीज एकटा सुरक्षा पैच सेहो समाविष्ट करैत अछि। अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="निजी जानकारी केँ ब्लर करू">
<feature>एकटा इमेजक चयन करू आ साझा करू -> निजी जानकारी केँ ब्लर करू पर टैप करू। इमेज मे प्रोफाइल चित्र, उपनाम, फोन नंबर आ अन्य संवेदनशील डेटा स्वचालित रूप सँ ब्लर भए जायत। ई अहाँक गोपनीयताक सुरक्षाक लेल अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे आब एप संयोजन संरक्षित कयल जा सकैत अछि। विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे, संयोजन केँ होम स्क्रीन पर आइकनक रूप मे संरक्षित करबाक लेल विभाजक केर बीच मे बटन टैप करू। आइकन टैप कयला सँ संयोजन धरि त्वरित एक्सेस सक्षम भए जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन">
<feature>मैजिक कैप्सूल किछु सिस्टम सेवा सभ मे चालू वा बंद कयल जा सकैत अछि। एकरा अजमेबाक लेल सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचना आ स्थिति बार > मैजिक कैप्सूल मे जाउ।
किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे अधिसूचना पैनल केर लेआउट, गति प्रभाव आ आइकन प्रदर्शन प्रभाव अनुकूलित कयल गेल अछि।
अनुमति सेटिंग्स पर जेबाक लेल कोनो एप आइकन केँ कनेक काल धरि दबाकए राखू।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। जखन अहाँ मात्र चार्ज करबाक बजाय फोटो सभ केँ स्थानांतरित करू वा फाइल सभ ट्रांसफर करू/Android ऑटो चुनैत छी, तखन एकटा सत्यापन वा सुरक्षा संकेत देखाय पड़ैत अछि, जाहि सँ सुरक्षित डेटा ट्रांसफर सुनिश्चित होइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>आब अहाँ होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ नुका सकैत छी। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा आ गोपनीयता > डिवाइस आ डेटा संरक्षण > होम स्क्रीन सँ एप सभ नुकाउ।
सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टू 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka whakatakoto e tēnei whakahōu te āhuahira Rehu ngā mōhiohio tūmataiti. Tērā anō, ka taea te huna i ngā ata mata kāinga. Ka taea te tiaki i ngā pahekotanga taupānga i te aratau mata-wehe. E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take tūhononga USB. Kei te komokomo hoki tēnei putanga i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. E tūtohutia ana kia whakahōu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rehu ngā mōhiohio tūmataiti">
<feature>Tīpakohia tētahi atahanga ka pato Tuarihia -> Rehu ngā mōhiohio tūmataiti. Ka rehu aunoatia te pikitia kōtaha, ingoa kārangaranga, tau waea me tētahi atu raraunga tairongo i te atahanga. Ko tēnei hei pare i tō tūmataitinga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matapihi-Maha">
<feature>Ināianei ka taea te tiaki i ngā pahekotanga taupānga i te aratau mata-wehe. I roto i te aratau mata-wehe, patohia te pātene i waenganui o te whakawehe hei tiaki i te pahekotanga hei ata i te mata kāinga. Patohia te ata ka whakahohe te uru wawe ki te pahekotanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mata kāinga">
<feature>Pūmatua Tūmatarau ka taea te whakakā, te kua whakaweto rānei i ētahi ratonga pūnaha. Haere ki Ngā Tautuhinga > Ngā Whakamōhiotanga me te pae tūnga > Pūmatua Tūmatarau hei whakamātau.
Kua arotautia te tahora, te rākeitanga nekeneke me te pānga whakaatu ata o te paewhiri whakamōhiotanga ki ētahi tauari.
Pēhi roa i tētahi ata taupānga kia tere te haere ki ngā tautuhinga whakaaetanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take hononga USB. Ka puta mai tētahi manatokonga, tohuāki haumarutanga rānei ina tīpako koe i Whakawhiti whakaahua, Whakawhitia ngā kōnae / Android Auto rānei, kaua ko te Whakahiko anake, me whakarite kia haumaru ake te whakawhiti raraunga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Ka taea ināianei te huna i ngā ata mata kāinga. Whakamātauria mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga > Haumarutanga me te tūmataitinga > Te pūrere me te parenga raraunga > Huna ngā taupānga mai i te mata Kāinga.
Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Oketopa 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање ја воведува карактеристиката Замати приватни информации. Дополнително, може да се кријат иконите на почетниот екран. Може да се зачуваат комбинации на апликации во режим на поделен екран. Потребна е автентикација од корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB. Ова издание исто така вградува безбедносна крпеница. Се препорачува да ажурирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Замати приватни информации">
<feature>Изберете слика и допрете Сподели -> Замати приватни информации. Сликата на профилот, прекарот, телефонскиот број и другите чувствителни податоци во сликата автоматски ќе се заматат. Ова е со цел да се заштити вашата приватност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Повеќе прозорци">
<feature>Сега може да се зачувуваат комбинации на апликации во режим на поделен екран. Во режим на поделен екран, допрете го копчето во средината од разделникот за да ја зачувате комбинацијата како икона на почетниот екран. Допирањето на иконата овозможува брз пристап до комбинацијата.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Почетен екран">
<feature>Магична капсула може да се вклучи или исклучи во некои системски услуги. Одете до Нагодување > Известувања и статусна лента > Магична капсула за да ја испробате.
Распоредот, ефектот на движење и ефектот на прикажување на иконата на таблата за известувања се оптимизирани во некои сценарија.
Долго притиснете некоја икона за апликација за да одите брзо до поставките за дозволите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Потребна е автентикација на корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB. Се појавува барање за потврдување или безбедносно барање кога ќе изберете Пренесувајте фотографии или Пренос на датотеки / Android Auto наместо Само полнење, за да се осигури безбеден пренос на податоците.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Сега може да ги криете иконите на почетниот екран. Пробајте преку одење во: Нагодување > Безбедност и приватност > Заштита на уредот и податоците > Скриј апликации од почетниот екран.
Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (октомври 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за Ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја наша веб-локација: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или одете во сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് 'സ്വകാര്യ വിവരങ്ങൾ മങ്ങിപ്പിക്കുക' എന്ന സവിശേഷത അവതരിപ്പിക്കുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാവുന്നതുമാണ്. സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിലെ ആപ്പ് കോംബിനേഷനുകൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടത് ആവശ്യമാണ്. കൂടാതെ, ഈ റിലീസ് ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സ്വകാര്യ വിവരങ്ങൾ മങ്ങിപ്പിക്കുക">
<feature>ഒരു ഇമേജ് തിരഞ്ഞെടുത്ത് ഷെയർ ചെയ്യുക -> സ്വകാര്യ വിവരങ്ങൾ മങ്ങിപ്പിക്കുക എന്നതിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക. ഇമേജിലെ പ്രൊഫൈൽ ചിത്രവും വിളിപ്പേരും ഫോൺ നമ്പറും മറ്റ് സെൻസിറ്റീവ് ഡാറ്റയും സ്വയമേവ മങ്ങിപ്പിക്കും. നിങ്ങളുടെ സ്വകാര്യത പരിരക്ഷിക്കുന്നതിനാണിത്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മൾട്ടി-വിൻഡോ">
<feature>സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിലെ ആപ്പ് കോംബിനേഷനുകൾ ഇപ്പോൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിൽ, ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ ഒരു ഐക്കണായി കോംബിനേഷൻ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ ഡിവൈഡറിന്റെ മധ്യത്തിലെ ബട്ടണിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക. ഐക്കണിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുന്നത്, കോംബിനേഷനിലേക്കുള്ള ദ്രുത ആക്‌സസ് പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീന്‍">
<feature>ചില സിസ്റ്റം സേവനങ്ങളിൽ മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ സ്വിച്ച് ഓൺ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ ഓഫ് ചെയ്യാൻ കഴിയും. അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കാൻ, ക്രമീകരണം > നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷനുകളും സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാറും > മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ എന്നതിലേക്ക് പോകുക.
ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിൽ നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ പാനലിലെ ലേഔട്ടും ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റും ഐക്കൺ ഡിസ്പ്ലേ ഇഫക്റ്റും ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്‌തിരിക്കുന്നു.
അനുവാദ ക്രമീകരണത്തിലേക്ക് ദ്രുതഗതിയിൽ പോകാൻ ഒരു ആപ്പ് ഐക്കണിൽ ദീർഘനേരം അമർത്തിപ്പിടിക്കുക.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ ആവശ്യമാണ്. 'ചാർജ് ചെയ്യാൻ മാത്രം' എന്നതിന് പകരം, നിങ്ങൾ 'ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈമാറുക' അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 'ഫയലുകൾ കൈമാറുക / Android Auto' എന്നത് തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുമ്പോൾ ഒരു പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സുരക്ഷാ നിർദ്ദേശം ദൃശ്യമാകുന്നു, ഇത് സുരക്ഷിതമായ ഡാറ്റാ കൈമാറ്റം ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാവുന്നതാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി ഇത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > സുരക്ഷയും സ്വകാര്യതയും > ഉപകരണ, ഡാറ്റാ പരിരക്ഷ > ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ നിന്ന് ആപ്പുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കുക.
സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഒക്‌ടോബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр Хувийн мэдээлэл бүдгэрүүлэх онцлогийг нэвтрүүлж байна. Мөн үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой. Хуваасан дэлгэцийн горим дахь аппын хослолыг хадгалах боломжтой. USB холболтын зорилгыг солих үед хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардана. Энэхүү хувилбар нь хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг мөн багтаасан. Шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хувийн мэдээлэл бүдгэрүүлэх">
<feature>Зургийг сонгоод Хуваалцах -> Хувийн мэдээлэл бүдгэрүүлэх дээр товшино уу. Зураг дээрх профайл зураг, хоч, утасны дугаар, бусад нууцлалтай мэдээлэл автоматаар бүдгэрэх болно. Энэ нь таны нууцлалыг хамгаалах зорилготой юм.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Олон цонх">
<feature>Хуваасан дэлгэцийн горим дахь апликэйшний хослолыг одоо хадгалах боломжтой боллоо. Хуваасан дэлгэц горимд хуваагчийн голд байгаа товчлуур дээр товшиж хослолыг үндсэн дэлгэц дээр шигтгээ зураг болгон хадгална. Шигтгээ зураг дээр товшиж хослол руу шуурхай хандах боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Үндсэн дэлгэц">
<feature>Шидэт капсулыг зарим системийн үйлчилгээнд асааж, унтрааж болно. Үүнийг туршиж үзэхийн тулд Тохиргоо > Мэдэгдэл болон төлөвийн мөр > Шидэт капсул руу очно уу.
Мэдэгдлийн хэсгийн зохион байгуулалт, хөдөлгөөний нөлөө, шигтгээ зургийн харагдах нөлөөг зарим тохиолдолд оновчилсон.
Апликэйшний шигтгээ зургийг удаан дарж зөвшөөрлийн тохиргоо руу шуурхай очно уу.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>USB-г холбох зорилгоор сэлгэх үед хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардлагатай. Зөвхөн цэнэглэхийн оронд, Зургуудыг дамжуулах эсвэл Файл шилжүүлэх/Андройд автоматыг сонгох үед баталгаажуулах эсвэл хамгаалалтын сануулга гарч ирж, өгөгдөл дамжуулах аюулгүй байдлыг хангана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Одоо та үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой боллоо. Та Тохиргоо > Хамгаалалт ба нууцлал > Төхөөрөмж ба өгөгдөл хамгаалалт > Үндсэн дэлгэцээс апликэйшн нуух руу очиж үүнийг туршиж үзнэ үү.
Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны 10-р сар) системийн аюулгүй байдалд зориулж нэгтгэсэн. HONOR хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаарх дэлгэрэнгүй мэдээллийг авах бол манай https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 вэбсайтад зочилно уу</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन खाजगी माहिती अस्पष्ट करा वैशिट्य सादर करते. याव्यतिरिक्त, मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे लपवले जाऊ शकतात. विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमधील ॲप संयोजने जतन केले जाऊ शकतात. USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशाने स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. या प्रकाशनात सुरक्षितता पॅच देखील समाविष्ट आहे. अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="खाजगी माहिती अस्पष्ट करा">
<feature>एक प्रतिमा निवडा आणि सामायिक करा -> खाजगी माहिती अस्पष्ट करा वर टॅप करा. प्रतिमेमधील प्रोफाइल चित्र, टोपणनाव, फोन नंबर आणि अन्य संवेदनशील डेटा स्वयंचलितपणे अस्पष्ट होईल. हे आपल्या गोपनीयतेचे रक्षण करण्यासाठी आहे.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमधील ॲप संयोजने आता जतन केले जाऊ शकतात. विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमध्ये, मुख्य स्क्रीनवर संयोजन जतन करण्यासाठी विभाजक मध्ये असलेल्या बटणावर टॅप करा. चिन्हावर टॅप केल्याने संयोजनात जलद अ‍ॅक्‍सेस सक्षम करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन">
<feature>जादूई कॅप्सूल काही सिस्टम सेवांमध्ये चालू किंवा बंद केले जाऊ शकते. हे वापरून पाहण्यासाठी सेटिंग्ज > सूचना आणि स्टेटस बार > जादूई कॅप्सूल वर जा.
सूचना पॅनेलचे लेआउट, मोशन प्रभाव आणि चिन्‍ह डिस्प्ले प्रभाव काही परिस्थितींमध्ये ऑप्टिमाइझ केले जातात.
त्वरीत परवानगी सेटिंग्जवर जाण्यासाठी ॲप चिन्‍ह दाबून ठेवा.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशांनी स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. जेव्हा आपण फोटो स्‍थानांतरित करा किंवा फाइल्स/Android स्वयं स्‍थानांतरित करा निवडता तेव्हा एक सत्यापन किंवा सुरक्षितता सूचना दिसते, केवळ चार्ज करण्याऐवजी, सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>आपण आता मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे लपवू शकता. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुरक्षितता आणि गोपनीयता > उपकरण आणि डेटा संरक्षण > मुख्य स्क्रीनवरून ॲप्स लपवा.
सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षिता पॅच (ऑक्टो 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini memperkenalkan ciri Kaburkan Maklumat Peribadi. Selain itu, ikon skrin utama boleh disembunyikan. Gabungan aplikasi dalam mod skrin pisah boleh disimpan. Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB. Keluaran ini juga memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Anda disyorkan untuk mengemas kini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaburkan Maklumat Peribadi">
<feature>Pilih imej dan ketik Kongsi -> Kaburkan Maklumat Peribadi. Gambar profil, nama panggilan, nombor telefon dan data sensitif lain dalam imej akan dikaburkan secara automatik. Ini adalah untuk melindungi privasi anda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multitetingkap">
<feature>Gabungan aplikasi dalam mod skrin pisah kini boleh disimpan. Dalam mod skrin pisah, ketik butang di tengah pembahagi untuk menyimpan gabungan sebagai ikon pada skrin utama. Ketik ikon membolehkan akses pantas kepada gabungan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Skrin utama">
<feature>Kapsul Magic boleh dihidupkan atau dimatikan dalam sesetengah perkhidmatan sistem. Pergi ke Tetapan > Pemberitahuan dan bar status > Kapsul Magic untuk mencubanya.
Tataletak, kesan gerakan dan kesan paparan ikon panel pemberitahuan dioptimumkan dalam beberapa senario.
Tekan lama ikon aplikasi untuk pergi ke tetapan kebenaran dengan pantas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB. Pengesahan atau gesaan keselamatan muncul apabila anda memilih Pindahkan foto atau Pindahkan fail / Android Auto, bukannya Cas sahaja, demi memastikan pemindahan data yang lebih selamat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Anda kini boleh menyembunyikan ikon skrin utama. Cubalah dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Keselamatan dan privasi > Perlindungan peranti dan data > Sembunyikan aplikasi daripada Skrin utama.
Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Okt 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် ပုဂ္ဂိုလ်ရေး အချက်အလက်များကို မှုန်ဝါးပေးသည့် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်နှင့် မိတ်ဆက်ပေးထားသည်။ ထို့အပြင် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်သည်။ မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်ဖြင့် သုံးမည့် အက်ပ်အတွဲများကို သိမ်းဆည်းနိုင်သည်။ USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှု ရည်ရွယ်ချက်များ ပြောင်းသည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်တွင် လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကိုလည်း ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုဂ္ဂိုလ်ရေး အချက်အလက်များကို မှုန်ဝါးရန်">
<feature>ရုပ်ပုံကို ရွေးချယ်ပြီး မျှဝေရန် -> ပုဂ္ဂိုလ်ရေး အချက်အလက်များကို မှုန်ဝါးရန်ကို နှိပ်ပါ။ ရုပ်ပုံထဲရှိ ပရိုဖိုင်းပုံ၊ အမည်ပြောင်၊ ဖုန်းနံပါတ်နှင့် အခြား ထိခိုက်လွယ်သောဒေတာတို့ကို အလိုအလျောက် မှုန်ဝါးပေးပါမည်။ သင့်ကိုယ်ပိုင် အချက်အလက်ကို ကာကွယ်ရန်အတွက် ထိုသို့ပြုလုပ်ခြင်းဖြစ်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>ယခုအခါ မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်ဖြင့် သုံးမည့် အက်ပ်အတွဲများကို သိမ်းဆည်းနိုင်ပါပြီ။ မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်တွင် အက်ပ်အတွဲကို ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ပေါ်တွင် အိုင်ကွန်အဖြစ် သိမ်းဆည်းရန် ပိုင်းခြားမျဉ်း၏အလယ်ရှိ ခလုတ်ကို နှိပ်ပါ။ အိုင်ကွန်ကို နှိပ်ခြင်းဖြင့် အက်ပ်အတွဲကို အမြန် ရယူသုံးစွဲခွင့်ရစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်">
<feature>အချို့ စနစ်ဝန်ဆောင်မှုများတွင် Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်ကို ဖွင့် သို့မဟုတ် ပိတ်နိုင်သည်။ ၎င်းကိုစမ်းကြည့်ရန် ဆက်တင် > အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများနှင့် အခြေအနေပြဘား > Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်သို့ သွားပါ။
အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် အသိပေးချက် မျက်နှာပြင်၏ ပုံစံ၊ လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်နှင့် အိုင်ကွန် ပြသမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိထားသည်။
ခွင့်ပြုချက် ဆက်တင်သို့ အမြန်သွားရန် အက်ပ်အိုင်ကွန်ကို ကြာကြာနှိပ်ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှု အပြောင်းအလဲလုပ်သည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ "အားသွင်းရန်သာ" အစား ပုံများ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် သို့မဟုတ် ဖိုင်များ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် / Android Auto ကို ရွေးချယ်သည့်အခါ အတည်ပြုမှု သို့မဟုတ် လုံခြုံရေး ညွှန်ကြားချက် ပေါ်လာပြီး ဒေတာ လွှဲပြောင်းမှုကို ပို၍လုံခြုံစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်ပါပြီ။ ဖော်ပြပါသို့သွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > လုံခြုံရေးနှင့် ကိုယ်ပိုင် အချက်အလက် > စက်နှင့် ဒေတာ ကာကွယ်ရေး > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်မှ အက်ပ်များကို ဝှက်ရန်။
စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (အောက်တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း အချက်အလက်များ ပိုမိုသိရှိလိုပါက ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ် https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ ပုဂၢိဳလ္ေရး အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို မႈန္ဝါးေပးသည့္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ႏွင့္ မိတ္ဆက္ေပးထားသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္သည္။ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္ျဖင့္ သုံးမည့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲမ်ားကို သိမ္းဆည္းႏိုင္သည္။ USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ ရည္႐ြယ္ခ်က္မ်ား ေျပာင္းသည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကိုလည္း ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုဂၢိဳလ္ေရး အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို မႈန္ဝါးရန္">
<feature>႐ုပ္ပုံကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္ၿပီး မွ်ေဝရန္ -> ပုဂၢိဳလ္ေရး အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို မႈန္ဝါးရန္ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ။ ႐ုပ္ပုံထဲရွိ ပ႐ိုဖိုင္းပုံ၊ အမည္ေျပာင္၊ ဖုန္းနံပါတ္ႏွင့္ အျခား ထိခိုက္လြယ္ေသာေဒတာတို႔ကို အလိုအေလ်ာက္ မႈန္ဝါးေပးပါမည္။ သင့္ကိုယ္ပိုင္ အခ်က္အလက္ကို ကာကြယ္ရန္အတြက္ ထိုသို႔ျပဳလုပ္ျခင္းျဖစ္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>ယခုအခါ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္ျဖင့္ သုံးမည့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲမ်ားကို သိမ္းဆည္းႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္တြင္ အက္ပ္အတြဲကို ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ေပၚတြင္ အိုင္ကြန္အျဖစ္ သိမ္းဆည္းရန္ ပိုင္းျခားမ်ဥ္း၏အလယ္ရွိ ခလုတ္ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ။ အိုင္ကြန္ကို ႏွိပ္ျခင္းျဖင့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲကို အျမန္ ရယူသုံးစြဲခြင့္ရေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
<feature>အခ်ိဳ႕ စနစ္ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈမ်ားတြင္ Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္ကို ဖြင့္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ပိတ္ႏိုင္သည္။ ၎ကိုစမ္းၾကည့္ရန္ ဆက္တင္ > အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားႏွင့္ အေျခအေနျပဘား > Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္သို႔ သြားပါ။
အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ အသိေပးခ်က္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္၏ ပုံစံ၊ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ႏွင့္ အိုင္ကြန္ ျပသမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိထားသည္။
ခြင့္ျပဳခ်က္ ဆက္တင္သို႔ အျမန္သြားရန္ အက္ပ္အိုင္ကြန္ကို ၾကာၾကာႏွိပ္ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ အေျပာင္းအလဲလုပ္သည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ "အားသြင္းရန္သာ" အစား ပုံမ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ဖိုင္မ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ / Android Auto ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္သည့္အခါ အတည္ျပဳမႈ သို႔မဟုတ္ လုံျခံဳေရး ၫႊန္ၾကားခ်က္ ေပၚလာၿပီး ေဒတာ လႊဲေျပာင္းမႈကို ပို၍လုံၿခဳံေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔သြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > လုံျခံဳေရးႏွင့္ ကိုယ္ပိုင္ အခ်က္အလက္ > စက္ႏွင့္ ေဒတာ ကာကြယ္ေရး > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္မွ အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ရန္။
စနစ္လုံျခံဳေရးအတြက္ Android လုံျခံဳေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ေအာက္တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ HONOR လုံျခံဳေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း အခ်က္အလက္မ်ား ပိုမိုသိရွိလိုပါက ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne oppdateringen introduserer Tilslør personlig info-funksjonen. I tillegg kan du skjule startskjermikonene. App-kombinasjoner i delt-skjerm-modus kan lagres. Brukerautentisering kreves ved bytte av USB-tilkoblingsformål. Denne utgivelsen innlemmer også en sikkerhetsoppdatering. Det anbefales å oppdatere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tilslør personlig info">
<feature>Velg et bilde og trykk på Del -> Tilslør personlig info. Profilbildet, kallenavnet, telefonnummeret og andre sensitive opplysninger på bildet blir automatisk tilslørt. Dette er for å beskytte personvernet ditt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flere vinduer">
<feature>App-kombinasjoner i delt-skjerm-modus kan nå lagres. I delt-skjerm-modus trykk på knappen i midten av deleren for å lagre kombinasjonen som et ikon på startskjermen. Trykk på ikonet gjør det mulig med hurtigtilgang til kombinasjonen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startside">
<feature>Magisk kapsel kan slås på eller av i noen systemtjenester. Gå til Innstillinger > Varslinger og Statuslinje > Magisk kapsel for å prøve dette.
Layout, bevegelseseffekt og ikonvisningseffekt på varslingspanelet er optimalisert i noen scenarier.
Trykk lenge på et app-ikon for å hurtig gå til Innstillinger for tillatelser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brukerbekreftelse kreves ved bytting av USB-tilkoblingsformål. En bekreftelse eller sikkerhetsmelding dukker opp når du velger Overfør bilder eller Overfør filer / Android Auto istedenfor bare Bare opplading, og sikrer dermed tryggere dataoverføring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Du kan nå skjule startskjermikonene. Prøv dette ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Sikkerhet og personvern > Enhets- og personvern > Skjul apper på startskjermen.
Android sikkerhetsoppdatering (okt. 2024) har blitt integrert for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om HONOR Sikkerhet-oppdateringer, se vårt nettsted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले निजी जानकारी धमिलो पार्ने सुविधा ल्याएको छ । साथै गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन मिल्छ । स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा एपको संयोजन बचत गर्न सकिन्छ । USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । यो रिलिजमा सुरक्षा प्याच पनि समावेश गरिएको छ । अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="निजी जानकारी धमिलो पार्नुहोस्">
<feature>कुनै फोटो चयन गर्नुहोस् र साझा गर्नुहोस् -> निजी जानकारी धमिलो पार्नुहोस् मा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् । प्रोफाइल तस्विर, उपनाम, फोन नम्बर र फोटोमा भएका अन्य संवेदनशील जानकारी स्वतः धमिलो पारिने छ । तपाईंको गोपनीयता सुरक्षित राख्नका लागि यसो गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="बहु-विन्डो">
<feature>अब स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा एपको संयोजन बचत गर्न सकिन्छ । एपको संयोजनलाई गृह स्क्रिनको आइकनका रूपमा बचत गर्न स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा डिभाइडरको मध्य भागमा भएको बटनमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् । आइकनहरूमा ट्याप गर्नाले तपाईं एपको संयोजनलाई द्रुत पहुँच गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गृह स्क्रिन">
<feature>प्रणालीका केही सेवाहरूमा म्याजिक क्याप्सुल अन वा अफ गर्न मिल्छ । सेटिङहरू > सूचनाहरू र स्थिति पट्टी > म्याजिक क्याप्सुलमा जानुहोस् र यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस् ।
केही परिदृश्यहरूमा सूचना प्यानलको लेआउट, मोसनको प्रभाव र आइकनको डिस्प्ले प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गरिएका छन् ।
अनुमतिसम्बन्धी सेटिङहरूमा जान एप आइकनमा केही बेरसम्म थिच्नुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । तपाईंले चार्ज मात्र गर्नुहोस् विकल्पको साटो फोटोहरू स्थानान्तरण गर्नुहोस् वा फाइल स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् / Android Auto चयन गर्नुभयो भने प्रमाणीकरण वा सुरक्षा प्रम्प्ट देखिने छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>तपाईं अब गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सुरक्षा तथा गोपनीयता > यन्त्र तथा डाटाको सुरक्षा > गृह स्क्रिनबाट एपहरू लुकाउनुहोस् ।
एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अक्टोबर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update introduceert de functie Privé-info wazig maken. Bovendien kunnen startschermpictogrammen worden verborgen. App-combinaties in de modus gesplitst-scherm kunnen worden opgeslagen. Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden. Deze release bevat ook een beveiligingspatch. Het wordt aanbevolen om bij te werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Privé-info wazig maken">
<feature>Selecteer een afbeelding en tik op Delen -> Privé-info wazig maken. De profielfoto, de bijnaam, het telefoonnummer en andere gevoelige gegevens in de afbeelding worden automatisch vervaagd om uw privacy te beschermen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multivenster">
<feature>App-combinaties in de modus gesplitst-scherm kunnen nu worden opgeslagen. Tik in de modus gesplitst-scherm op de knop in het midden van de verdeler om de combinatie op te slaan als een pictogram op het startscherm. Tik op het pictogram om snel toegang te krijgen tot de combinatie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startscherm">
<feature>Magische capsule kan in sommige systeemservices worden in- of uitgeschakeld. Ga naar Instellingen > Meldingen en statusbalk > Magische capsule om het uit te proberen.
De lay-out, het bewegingseffect en het pictogramweergave-effect van het meldingenpaneel zijn in sommige scenario's geoptimaliseerd.
Druk lang op een app-pictogram om snel naar toestemmingsinstellingen te gaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden. Er verschijnt een verificatie- of beveiligingsprompt wanneer u Foto's overdragen of Bestanden overdragen / Android Auto selecteert, in plaats van Alleen opladen, wat zorgt voor een veiligere gegevensoverdracht.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>U kunt nu startschermpictogrammen verbergen. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Beveiliging en privacy > Apparaat- en gegevensbescherming > Apps verbergen van Startscherm.
Android-beveiligingspatch (oktober 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ସୂଚନାକୁ ଝାପସା କରନ୍ତୁ ବିଶେଷତାକୁ ଯୋଡ଼ାଯାଇଛି। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଲୁଚାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ ସମସ୍ତ ମିଶ୍ରଣ ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ ମଧ୍ୟ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ସୂଚନାକୁ ଝାପସା କରନ୍ତୁ">
<feature>ଏକ ପ୍ରତିଛବି ଚୟନ କରନ୍ତୁ ଏବଂ ଅଂଶୀଦାର କରନ୍ତୁ -> ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ସୂଚନାକୁ ଝାପସା କରନ୍ତୁରେ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ। ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ଥିବା ପ୍ରୋଫାଇଲ୍‌ ଫଟୋ, ଶ୍ରଦ୍ଧାନାମ, ଫୋନ୍ ନମ୍ଵର୍ ଏବଂ ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ସମ୍ବେଦନଶୀଳ ଡାଟା ସ୍ୱତଃସ୍ପୃତ ଭାବେ ଝାପସା କରାଯିବ। ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଗୋପନୀୟତାକୁ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଦେବାକୁ ଏହା କରାଯାଇଥାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମଲ୍ଟି-ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ">
<feature>ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ ସମସ୍ତ ମିଶ୍ରଣ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ, ମିଶ୍ରଣକୁ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ରେ ଏକ ଆଇକନ୍ ପରି ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରିବାକୁ ଡିଭାଇଡର୍‌ର ମଧ୍ୟରେ ଥିବା ବଟନ୍‌ରେ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ। ଆଇକନ୍‌ ଉପରେ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ମିଶ୍ରଣର ଦ୍ରୁତ ଆକସେସ୍ ସକ୍ଷମ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌">
<feature>କିଛି ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସେବାରେ ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ ଅନ୍ କିମ୍ବା ଅଫ୍ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ଏହାକୁ ପରଖିବାକୁ ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଏବଂ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍ > ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍‌କୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।
ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତି ପ୍ୟାନେଲ୍‌ର ଲେଆଉଟ୍, ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବ ଏବଂ ଆଇକନ୍ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶନ ପ୍ରଭାବ କିଛି କ୍ଷେତ୍ରରେ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରାଯାଇଛି।
ଅନୁମତି ସେଟିଂସ୍‌କୁ ତୁରନ୍ତ ଯିବାକୁ ଏକ ଆପ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ରେ ଲମ୍ବା ସମୟ ଦବାନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଆପଣ ଫଟୋଗୁଡିକ ସ୍ଥାନାନ୍ତର କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ/Android Auto ଚୟନ କରିବା ବେଳେ, କେବଳ ଚାର୍ଜ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ ବଦଳରେ ସୁରକ୍ଷିତ ଡାଟା ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି ଏହା ଯାଞ୍ଚ କିମ୍ବା ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ରମ୍ପଟ୍‌ ଦେଖାଯଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ଆପଣ ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ ଲୁଚାଇ ପାରିବେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଓ ଗୋପନୀୟତା > ଡିଭାଇସ୍ ଓ ଡାଟା ସୁରକ୍ଷା > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ରୁ ଆପସ୍ ଲୁଚାନ୍ତୁ।
ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅକ୍ଟୋବର 2024) ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਧੁੰਦਲਾ ਕਰੋ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਗਈ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾਏ ਜਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ। ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪ ਸੁਮੇਲਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਵੀ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨਿੱਜੀ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਧੁੰਦਲਾ ਕਰੋ">
<feature>ਇੱਕ ਚਿੱਤਰ ਚੁਣੋ ਅਤੇ ਸਾਂਝਾ ਕਰੋ -> ਨਿੱਜੀ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਧੁੰਦਲਾ ਕਰੋ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ। ਚਿੱਤਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਪ੍ਰੋਫਾਈਲ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ, ਉਪ ਨਾਮ, ਫ਼ੋਨ ਨੰਬਰ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਸੰਵੇਦਨਸ਼ੀਲ ਡੇਟਾ ਆਪਣੇ-ਆਪ ਧੁੰਦਲਾ ਹੋ ਜਾਵੇਗਾ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਡੀ ਪਰਦੇਦਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਰੱਖਿਆ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮਲਟੀ-ਵਿੰਡੋ">
<feature>ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪ ਸੁਮੇਲਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹੁਣ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ, ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਵਜੋਂ ਸੁਮੇਲ ਨੂੰ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਡਿਵਾਈਡਰ ਦੇ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਬਟਨ ਨੂੰ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ। ਆਈਕੋਨ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰਨਾ ਸੁਮੇਲ ਤੱਕ ਤੇਜ਼ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ">
<feature>ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ ਨੂੰ ਕੁਝ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੇਵਾਵਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਚਾਲੂ ਜਾਂ ਬੰਦ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ > ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।
ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੂਚਨਾ ਪੈਨਲ ਦੇ ਲੇਆਉਟ, ਗਤੀ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਅਤੇ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ 'ਤੇ ਤੇਜ਼ੀ ਨਾਲ ਜਾਣ ਲਈ ਐਪ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਨੂੰ ਲੰਬੇ ਸਮੇਂ ਤੱਕ ਦਬਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਡੇਟਾ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ, ਸਿਰਫ਼ ਚਾਰਜ ਕਰੋ ਦੀ ਬਜਾਏ, ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ/Android Auto ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਨੂੰ ਚੁਣਦੇ ਹੋ ਤਾਂ ਤਸਦੀਕ ਜਾਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪ੍ਰੌਂਪਟ ਦਿਖਾਈ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਹੁਣ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅਤੇ ਪਰਦੇਦਾਰੀ > ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਅਤੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਤੋਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਲੁਕਾਓ।
ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਕਤੂਬਰ 2024) ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਵਾਸਤੇ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja wprowadza funkcję Rozmyj informacje poufne. Ponadto można ukrywać ikony na ekranie głównym. Kombinacje aplikacji w trybie podzielonego ekranu można zapisywać. Podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB jest wymagane uwierzytelnianie użytkownika. Ta wersja zawiera również poprawkę zabezpieczeń. Zaleca się zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rozmyj informacje poufne">
<feature>Wybierz obraz, a następnie dotknij Udostępnij -> Rozmyj informacje poufne. Zdjęcie profilowe, pseudonim, numer telefonu i inne poufne dane na obrazie zostaną automatycznie rozmyte w celu ochrony prywatności.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Wiele okien">
<feature>Można już zapisywać kombinacje aplikacji w trybie podzielonego ekranu. W trybie podzielonego ekranu dotknij przycisku pośrodku separatora, aby zapisać kombinację jako ikonę na ekranie głównym. Dotknięcie ikony umożliwia szybki dostęp do kombinacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ekran główny">
<feature>Magiczną kapsułę można włączyć lub wyłączyć w niektórych usługach systemowych. Wybierz Ustawienia > Powiadomienia i pasek stanu > Magiczna kapsuła, aby wypróbować tę funkcję.
Układ, efekt ruchu i efekt wyświetlania ikon panelu powiadomień zostały zoptymalizowane w niektórych sytuacjach.
Naciśnij długo ikonę aplikacji, aby szybko przejść do ustawień uprawnień.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Wymagane jest uwierzytelnienie użytkownika podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB. Monit o weryfikację lub monit dotyczący bezpieczeństwa pojawia się po wybraniu opcji Transferowanie zdjęć lub Transferowanie plików / Android Auto zamiast opcji Tylko ładowanie, zapewniając bezpieczniejszy transfer danych.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Można już ukrywać ikony ekranu głównego. Aby wypróbować tę funkcję, wybierz Ustawienia > Bezpieczeństwo i prywatność > Ochrona danych i urządzenia > Ukryj aplikacje na Ekranie głównym.
Poprawka zabezpieczeń systemu Android (październik 2024) została dodana w celu zapewnienia bezpieczeństwa systemu. Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń HONOR można uzyskać na stronie internetowej https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, esta atualização apresenta o recurso Desfocar informações privadas. Além disso, os ícones da tela inicial podem ser ocultados. Combinações de aplicativos no modo tela dividida podem ser salvas. A autenticação de usuário é necessária ao alternar os propósitos de conexão USB. Esta versão também incorpora um patch de segurança. É recomendado atualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desfocar informações privadas">
<feature>Selecione uma imagem e toque em Compartilhar -> Desfocar informações privadas. A imagem do perfil, apelido, número de telefone e outros dados sensíveis na imagem serão automaticamente desfocados para proteger sua privacidade.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Várias janelas">
<feature>As combinações de aplicativos no modo de tela dividida agora podem ser salvas. No modo de tela dividida, toque no botão no meio do divisor para salvar a combinação como um ícone na tela inicial. Tocar no ícone permite o acesso rápido à combinação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tela inicial">
<feature>A Cápsula mágica pode ser ativada ou desativada em alguns serviços do sistema. Acesse Configurações > Notificações e barra de status > Cápsula mágica para experimentar.
O layout, o efeito de movimento e o efeito de exibição de ícones do painel de notificação são otimizados em alguns cenários.
Pressione e segure um ícone de aplicativo para acessar rapidamente as configurações de permissão.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>A autenticação de usuário é necessária ao mudar o propósito da conexão USB. Uma mensagem de verificação ou segurança aparece quando você seleciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir arquivos/Android Auto, em vez de Carregar apenas, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Agora você pode ocultar ícones da tela inicial. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Segurança e privacidade > Proteção de dispositivos e dados > Ocultar aplicativos da Tela inicial.
O patch de segurança do Android (Outubro de 2024) foi incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização apresenta a funcionalidade Desfocar informações privadas. Além disso, os ícones do ecrã inicial podem ser ocultados. As combinações de aplicações no modo de ecrã dividido podem ser guardadas. A autenticação do utilizador é necessária quando se mudam as finalidades da ligação USB. Esta versão também inclui uma correção de segurança. A atualização é recomendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desfocar informações privadas">
<feature>Selecione uma imagem e toque em Partilhar -> Desfocar informações privadas. A imagem do perfil, o pseudónimo, o número de telefone e outros dados sensíveis na imagem serão automaticamente desfocados. O objetivo é proteger a sua privacidade.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijanela">
<feature>As combinações de aplicações no modo de ecrã dividido podem agora ser guardadas. No modo de ecrã dividido, toque no botão no meio da divisória para guardar a combinação como um ícone no ecrã inicial. Tocar no ícone permite um acesso rápido à combinação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ecrã Inicial">
<feature>A Cápsula mágica pode ser ativada ou desativada em alguns serviços do sistema. Aceda a Definições > Notificações e barra de estado > Cápsula mágica para experimentar.
A disposição, o efeito de movimento e o efeito de visualização dos ícones do painel de notificações são otimizados em alguns cenários.
Exerça uma longa pressão no ícone de uma aplicação para rapidamente aceder às definições de permissão.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>É necessária a autenticação do utilizador ao mudar para a ligação USB. É apresentado um comando de verificação ou segurança ao selecionar Transferir fotografias ou Transferir ficheiros / Android Auto em vez de Apenas carregar, garantindo a transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Pode agora ocultar ícones do ecrã inicial. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Segurança e privacidade > Proteção do dispositivo e dos dados > Ocultar aplicações do Ecrã inicial.
Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (outubro de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre atualizações de Segurança HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare introduce funcția Blurare informații confidențiale. În plus, pictogramele de pe ecranul de pornire pot fi ascunse. Combinațiile de aplicații din modul ecran divizat pot fi salvate. Autentificarea utilizatorului este necesară la comutarea scopului conexiunii USB. Această versiune include, de asemenea, un patch de securitate. Se recomandă actualizarea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blurare informații confidențiale">
<feature>Selectați o imagine și atingeți Partajare -> Blurare informații confidențiale. Imaginea de profil, pseudonimul, numărul de telefon și alte date sensibile din imagine vor fi estompate automat. Acest lucru vă va proteja confidențialitatea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ferestre multiple">
<feature>Combinațiile de aplicații în modul Ecran divizat pot fi acum salvate. În modul Ecran divizat, atingeți butonul din mijlocul separatorului pentru a salva combinația ca pictogramă pe ecranul de pornire. Atingerea pictogramei permite accesul rapid la combinație.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ecran de pornire">
<feature>Funcția Capsulă magică poate fi activată sau dezactivată în anumite servicii de sistem. Accesați Setări > Notificări și bară de stare > Capsulă magică pentru a o încerca.
Aspectul, efectul de mișcare și efectul de afișare a pictogramelor din panoul de notificare sunt optimizate în anumite scenarii.
Apăsați lung pe pictograma unei aplicații pentru a accesa rapid setările pentru permisiuni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentificarea utilizatorului este necesară când schimbați scopul conexiunii prin USB. Un mesaj de verificare sau de securitate apare atunci când selectați Transfer de fotografii sau Transferare fișiere/Android Auto, în loc de Doar încărcare, asigurând un transfer de date mai sigur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Acum puteți ascunde pictogramele ecranului de pornire. Încercați-o accesând la: Setări > Securitate și confidențialitate > Protecția dispozitivului și a datelor > Ascundere aplicații din Ecranul de pornire.
Corecția de securitate Android (octombrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de Securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы представить функцию «Размытие конфиденциальной информации», добавить возможность скрытия значков на рабочем экране и сохранения пар приложений в режиме нескольких окон, добавить аутентификацию пользователя при переключении целей USB-подключения, а также внедрить исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Размытие конфиденциальной информации">
<feature>Выберите изображение и нажмите «Отправить > Размытие конфиденциальной информации», после чего фото профиля, никнейм, номер телефона и другая конфиденциальная информация на изображении будет автоматически размыта для защиты вашей конфиденциальности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Мультиоконный режим">
<feature>Теперь можно сохранять комбинации приложений в режиме нескольких окон. В режиме нескольких окон нажмите кнопку в середине разделителя, чтобы сохранить комбинацию в виде значка на рабочем экране. Нажатие на значок предоставит быстрый доступ к комбинации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Рабочий экран">
<feature>В некоторых системных службах можно включить или выключить функцию Magic Capsule. Чтобы попробовать эту функцию, перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Уведомления и строка состояния > Magic Capsule».
Вид, эффект движения и эффект отображения значков на панели уведомлений оптимизированы в некоторых сценариях.
Нажмите и удерживайте значок приложения, чтобы быстро перейти к настройкам прав доступа.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При переключении USB-соединения требуется аутентификация пользователя. При выборе режима «Передача фото», «Передача файлов/Android Auto» вместо режима «Только зарядка» появляется запрос проверки или безопасности, что обеспечивает более безопасную передачу данных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>Теперь вы можете скрывать некоторые значки на рабочем экране. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Безопасность и конфиденциальность > Защита устройства и данных > Скрыть значки приложений на рабочем экране».
В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (октябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලය පුද්ගලික තතු බොඳ කරන්න විශේෂාංගය හඳුන්වා දෙයි. අමතරව, මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවිය හැකිවනු ඇත. බෙදුම් තිර ප්‍රකාරයේ යෙදුම් ඒකාබද්ධ සුරැකීමට හැකිවනු ඇත. USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. මෙම නිකුතුවේ ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ද ඇතුළත් වේ. යාවත්කාල කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පුද්ගලික තතු බොඳ කරන්න">
<feature>රූපයක් තෝරා ගෙන බෙදාගන්න -> පුද්ගලික තතු බොඳ කරන්න තට්ටු කරන්න. රූපයේ ඇති පැතිකඩ පින්තූරය, පටබැඳි නම, දුරකථන අංකය සහ වෙනත් සංවේදී දත්ත ස්වයංක්‍රීයව බොඳ කෙරෙනු ඇත. මෙය ඔබගේ රහස්‍යතාව ආරක්ෂා කිරීමට ය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බහු කවුළුව">
<feature>බෙදුම් තිර ප්‍රකාරයේ යෙදුම් ඒකාබද්ධ දැන් සුරැකිය හැකිවනු ඇත. බෙදුම් තිරය ප්‍රකාරයේ දී, ඒකාබද්ධය මුල් තිරයේ අයිකනයක් ලෙස සුරැකීමට බෙදනයේ මැද ඇති බොත්තම තට්ටු කරන්න. අයිකනය තට්ටු කිරීම ඒකාබද්ධයට ඉක්මන් පිවිසීම සක්‍රිය කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුල් තිරය">
<feature>සමහර පද්ධති සේවා තුළ මැජික් කැප්සියුලය සක්‍රිය කිරීමට හෝ අක්‍රිය කිරීමට හැකිවනු ඇත. එය උත්සාහ කිරීමට සැකසුම් > දැනුම්දීම් සහ තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ > මැජික් කැප්සියුලය වෙත යන්න.
දැනුම්දීම් පැනලයේ පිරිසැලසුම, චලන ප්‍රයෝගය සහ අයිකන සංදර්ශක ප්‍රයෝගය සමහර අවස්ථාවලදී ප්‍රශස්ත කෙරේ.
ඉක්මනින් අවසර සැකසුම් වෙත යාමට යෙදුම් අයිකනයක් දීර්ඝව ඔබන්න.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. ඔබ ආරෝපණය පමණි වෙනුවට ඡායාරූප මාරු කරන්න හෝ ගොනු හුවමාරු කරන්න / Android Auto තෝරාගත් විට, වඩා ආරක්ෂිත දත්ත මාරුව තහවුරු කරමින් සත්‍යාපන හෝ ආරක්ෂක ප්‍රේරණයක් දිස්වේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>ඔබට දැන් මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවිය හැකිවේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ආරක්ෂාව සහ රහස්‍යතාව > උපාංග සහ දත්ත ආරක්ෂාව > මුල් තිරයෙන් යෙදුම් සඟවන්න.
පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ඔක්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia zavádza funkciu Rozmazať súkromné informácie. Okrem toho môžete skryť ikony na domovskej obrazovke. Kombinácie aplikácií v režime rozdelenej obrazovky možno uložiť. Pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Toto vydanie obsahuje aj bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizácia sa odporúča.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rozmazať súkromné informácie">
<feature>Vyberte obrázok a ťuknite na položku Zdieľať -> Rozmazať súkromné informácie. Profilový obrázok, prezývka, telefónne číslo a ďalšie citlivé údaje na obrázku sa automaticky rozmažú. Slúži to na ochranu vášho súkromia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Viacero okien">
<feature>Kombinácie aplikácií v režime rozdelenej obrazovky možno teraz uložiť. V režime rozdelenej obrazovky ťuknite na tlačidlo v strede oddeľovača, čím kombináciu uložíte ako ikonu na domovskej obrazovke. Ťuknutím na ikonu získate rýchly prístup ku kombinácii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Domovská obrazovka">
<feature>V niektorých systémových službách je teraz možné zapnúť alebo vypnúť funkciu Magická kapsula. Prejdite do ponuky Nastavenia > Upozornenia a stavový riadok > Magická kapsula a vyskúšajte to.
Rozloženie, efekt pohybu a efekt zobrazenia ikon na paneli upozornení sú v niektorých prípadoch optimalizované.
Dlhým stlačením ikony aplikácie rýchlo prejdite na nastavenia povolení.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Pri výbere možnosti Prenos fotografií alebo Prenos súborov/Android Auto sa namiesto možnosti Len nabíjanie zobrazí výzva na overenie alebo zabezpečenie, čím sa zaistí bezpečnejší prenos dát.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Teraz môžete skryť ikony domovskej obrazovky. Vyskúšajte to v ponuke Nastavenia > Zabezpečenie a súkromie > Zariadenie a ochrana údajov > Skryť aplikácie na domovskej obrazovke.
Obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu systému Android (okt. 2024) na zabezpečenie systému. Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev uvaja funkcijo zameglitve osebnih podatkov. Obenem lahko skrijete ikone na začetnem zaslonu in shranite kombinacije aplikacij v načinu razdeljenega zaslona. Pri preklopu povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ta izdaja vključuje tudi varnostni popravek. Priporočamo posodobitev.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zameglitev osebnih podatkov">
<feature>Izberite sliko in se dotaknite možnosti Skupna raba -> Zamegli osebne podatke. Slika profila, vzdevek, telefonska številka in drugi občutljivi podatki na sliki bodo samodejno zamegljeni. S tem se zaščiti vaša zasebnost.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Več oken">
<feature>Kombinacijo aplikacij v načinu razdeljenega zaslona je zdaj mogoče shraniti. V načinu razdeljenega zaslona se dotaknite gumba na sredini separatorja, da shranite kombinacijo kot ikono na začetnem zaslonu. Z dotikom ikone lahko hitro dostopate do kombinacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Začetni zaslon">
<feature>V nekaterih sistemskih storitvah lahko vklopite ali izklopite s Čarobno kapsulo. Izberite Nastavitve > Obvestila in vrstica stanja > Čarobna kapsula, da jo preizkusite.
V nekaterih situacijah so postavitev, učinek gibanja in učinek prikaza ikon v podoknu z obvestili optimizirani.
Z dolgim pritiskom ikone aplikacije hitro odprete nastavitve dovoljenj.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pri preklopu povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ko izberete možnost Prenos fotografij ali Prenos datotek/Android Auto, se namesto možnosti Samo polnjenje prikaže poziv za preverjanje ali varnostni poziv, s tem pa je zagotovljen varnejši prenos podatkov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Zdaj lahko skrijete ikone na začetnem zaslonu. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite v razdelku Nastavitve > Varnost in zasebnost > Zaščita naprave in podatkov > Skrij aplikacije na začetnem zaslonu.
Varnostni popravek za Android (oktober 2024) je vključen za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen introducerar funktionen Suddig privat information. Dessutom kan ikoner på startsidan döljas. Appkombinationer i delat skärmläge kan sparas. Användarautentisering krävs när du byter USB-anslutning. Den här utgåvan implementerar också en säkerhetskorrigering. Du rekommenderas att uppdatera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suddig privat information">
<feature>Välj en bild och tryck på Dela -> Suddig privat information. Profilbilden, smeknamnet, telefonnumret och annan känslig information i bilden blir automatiskt suddig. Det här görs för att skydda din sekretess.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flera fönster">
<feature>Appkombinationer i delat skärmläge kan nu sparas. Tryck på knappen i mitten av delaren i det delade skärmläget för att spara kombinationen som en ikon på startsidan. Ett tryck på ikonen ger snabbåtkomst till kombinationen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startsida">
<feature>Magisk kapsel kan slås på eller stängas av i vissa systemtjänster. Gå till Inställningar > Aviseringar och statusfält > Magisk kapsel om du vill prova.
Layouten, rörelseeffekten och ikonvisningseffekten för aviseringspanelen är optimerade i vissa scenarier.
Tryck länge på en appikon för att snabbt gå till behörighetsinställningar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Användarautentisering krävs när du byter USB-anslutning. En verifierings- eller säkerhetsuppmaning visas när du väljer Överföra foton eller Överföra filer/Android Auto i stället för Endast laddning, vilket ger en säkrare dataöverföring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Du kan nu dölja ikoner på startsidan. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Säkerhet och sekretess > Enhets- och dataskydd > Dölj appar från startsidan.
Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (oktober 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linaleta kipengele cha Tia Ukungu Maelezo ya Kibinafsi. Pia, aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo zinaweza kufichwa. Mikusanyiko ya programu katika hali ya ugawaji skrini inaweza kuhifadhiwa. Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB. Toleo hili pia linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama. Unapendekezwa usasishe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tia Ukungu Maelezo ya Kibinafsi">
<feature>Chagua picha kisha uguse Shiriki -> Tia Ukungu Maelezo ya Kibinafsi. Picha ya wasifu, jina la utani, nambari ya simu na data nyingine nyeti kwenye picha zitawekwa ukungu kiotomatiki. Hii ni ili kulinda faragha yako.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madirisha Kadhaa">
<feature>Mikusanyiko ya programu katika hali ya ugawaji skrini sasa inaweza kuhifadhiwa. Katika hali ya ugawaji skrini, gusa kitufe kilicho katikati ya kitenganishi ili kuhifadhi mkusanyiko kama aikoni kwenye skrini ya mwanzo. Kugusa aikoni huwezesha ufikiaji wa haraka wa mkusanyiko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Skrini ya mwanzo">
<feature>Kapsuli ya Miujiza inaweza kuwashwa au kuzimwa katika huduma fulani za mfumo. Nenda kwenye Mipangilio > Taarifa na upau wa hali > Kapsuli ya Miujiza ili uijaribu.
Ruwaza, athari ya mwendo na athari ya onyesho la aikoni ya paneli ya taarifa zinaboreshwa katika baadhi ya miktadha.
Bonyeza kwa muda mrefu aikoni ya programu ili uende kwenye mipangilio ya kibali kwa haraka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB. Kidokezo cha uthibitishaji au usalama hutokea unapochagua Hamisha picha au Hamisha faili / Android Auto, badala ya Chaji pekee, hivyo basi kuhakikisha uhamishaji salama wa data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Sasa unaweza kuficha aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwa: Mipangilio > Usalama na faragha > Ulinzi wa data na kifaa > Ficha programu kutoka kwenye Skrini ya mwanzo.
Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Okt 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு தனிப்பட்ட தகவலை மங்கலாக்கு அம்சத்தை அறிமுகப்படுத்துகிறது. கூடுதலாக, முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்கவும் முடியும். திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில் செயலிக் கலவைகளைச் சேமிக்கலாம். USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. இந்த வெளியீடு பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பையும் கொண்டுள்ளது. இது பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு ஆகும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="தனிப்பட்ட தகவலை மங்கலாக்கு">
<feature>ஒரு படத்தைத் தேர்ந்தெடுத்து, பகிர் -> தனிப்பட்ட தகவலை மங்கலாக்கு என்பதைத் தட்டவும். சுயவிவரப் படம், புனைப்பெயர், ஃபோன் எண் மற்றும் படத்தில் உள்ள பிற உணர்திறன் தரவு ஆகியவை தானாகவே மங்கலாக்கப்படும். இது உங்கள் தனியுரிமையைப் பாதுகாக்கும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பல சாளரம்">
<feature>திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில் செயலிக் கலவைகளை இப்போது சேமிக்கலாம். திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில், முகப்புத் திரையில் கலவையை ஓர் ஐகானாகச் சேமிக்க டிவைடரின் நடுப்பகுதியில் உள்ள பொத்தானைத் தட்டவும். ஐகானைத் தட்டுவது கலவைக்கான விரைவு அணுகலைச் செயல்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="முகப்புத் திரை">
<feature>சில சிஸ்டம் சேவைகளில் மேஜிக் கேப்சூலை இயக்கவும் அல்லது அணைக்கவும் முடியும். அதை முயன்று பார்க்க, அமைப்புகள் > அறிவிப்புகள் மற்றும் நிலைப் பட்டி > மேஜிக் கேப்சூல் என்பதற்குச் செல்லவும்.
சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் அறிவிப்பு பேனலின் தளவமைப்பு, இயக்க விளைவு மற்றும் ஐகான் காட்சி விளைவு போன்றவை உகந்ததாக்கப்பட்டுள்ளன.
அனுமதி அமைப்புகளுக்கு விரைவாகச் செல்ல, செயலி ஐகானை நீண்ட அழுத்தம் செய்யவும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. பாதுகாப்பான தரவுப் பரிமாற்றத்தை உறுதிசெய்யும் வகையில், சார்ஜ் மட்டும் என்பதற்குப் பதிலாக, புகைப்படங்களைப் பரிமாற்று அல்லது கோப்புகளைப் பரிமாற்று / Android Auto என்பதைத் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கும்போது சரிபார்ப்பு அல்லது பாதுகாப்புத் தூண்டுதல் தோன்றும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>நீங்கள் இப்போது முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்கலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > பாதுகாப்பு மற்றும் தனியுரிமை > சாதனம் மற்றும் தரவுப் பாதுகாப்பு > முகப்புத் திரையிலிருந்து செயலிகளை மறைக்கவும்.
சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (அக் 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ వ్యక్తిగత సమాచారాన్ని అస్పష్టం చేయి ఫీచర్‌ను పరిచయం చేస్తుంది. అదనంగా, హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచవచ్చు. స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో అప్లికేషన్ కలయికను సేవ్ చేయవచ్చు. USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చుతున్నప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రామాణీకరణ అవసరం. ఈ విడుదల భద్రతా ప్యాచ్‌ను కూడా చేర్చుతుంది. అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="వ్యక్తిగత సమాచారాన్ని అస్పష్టం చేయి">
<feature>చిత్రాన్ని ఎంచుకుని, భాగస్వామ్యం చేయి -> వ్యక్తిగత సమాచారాన్ని అస్పష్టం చేయి ఎంపికను ట్యాప్ చేయండి. ప్రొఫైల్ చిత్రం, మారుపేరు, ఫోన్ నంబర్ మరియు చిత్రంలోని ఇతర ముఖ్యమైన డేటా స్వయంచాలకంగా అస్పష్టం చేయబడతాయి. ఇది మీ గోప్యతను సంరక్షించడానికి చేసే చర్య.</feature>
</features>
<features module="బహుళ-విండో">
<feature>స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో అప్లికేషన్ కలయికలను ఇప్పుడు సేవ్ చేయవచ్చు. స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో, హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌పై కలయికను ఒక చిహ్నం వలె సేవ్ చేయడానికి డివైడర్ మధ్యలోని బటన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయండి. ఐకాన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయడం వలన కలయికకు త్వరిత యాక్సెస్ లభిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్">
<feature>మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్‌ను కొన్ని సిస్టమ్ సేవల్లో స్విచ్ ఆన్ చేయవచ్చు లేదా ఆఫ్ చేయవచ్చు. దీనిని ప్రయత్నించడానికి సెట్టింగ్‌లు > నోటిఫికేషన్‌లు మరియు స్థితి బార్ > మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్‌కు వెళ్లండి.
నోటిఫికేషన్ ప్యానెల్ యొక్క లేఅవుట్, మోషన్ ప్రభావం మరియు చిహ్నం ప్రదర్శన ప్రభావం కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేయబడ్డాయి.
అనుమతి సెట్టింగ్‌లకు వేగంగా వెళ్లడానికి అప్లికేషన్ చిహ్నాన్ని ఎక్కువ సేపు నొక్కి, పట్టుకోండి.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చేటప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రమాణీకరణ అవసరం. మీరు ఛార్జ్ మాత్రమే కాకుండా, సురక్షితమైన డేటా బదిలీని నిర్ధారిస్తూ ఫోటోలను బదిలీ చేయండి లేదా ఫైల్స్ బదిలీ చేయి / Android ఆటోను బదిలీ చేయడాన్ని ఎంచుకున్నప్పుడు ధృవీకరణ లేదా భద్రతా ప్రాంప్ట్ కనిపిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>మీరు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచవచ్చు. దీనిని ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > భద్రత మరియు గోప్యత > పరికరం మరియు డేటా రక్షణ > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ నుండి అప్లికేషన్‌లను దాచండి.
Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (అక్టో 2024) అనేది సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రతా అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตนี้แนะนำฟีเจอร์เบลอข้อมูลส่วนตัว นอกจากนี้ คุณสามารถซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก บันทึกชุดของแอปในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอได้ และจำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB อีกด้วย รีลีสนี้ยังรวมแพตช์ความปลอดภัย เราจึงแนะนำให้คุณอัปเดต</feature>
</features>
<features module="เบลอข้อมูลส่วนตัว">
<feature>เลือกรูปภาพแล้วแตะแบ่งปัน -> เบลอข้อมูลส่วนตัว รูปภาพโปรไฟล์ ชื่อเล่น หมายเลขโทรศัพท์ และข้อมูลที่ละเอียดอ่อนอื่น ๆ ในรูปภาพจะเบลอโดยอัตโนมัติ การทำเช่นนี้ช่วยปกป้องความเป็นส่วนตัวของคุณ</feature>
</features>
<features module="หลายหน้าต่าง">
<feature>บันทึกชุดของแอปในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอได้แล้วในตอนนี้ ในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอ แตะปุ่มที่ตรงกลางของตัวแบ่งเพื่อบันทึกชุดเป็นไอคอนบนหน้าจอหลัก แตะไอคอนเพื่อเปิดใช้งานการเข้าถึงด่วนถึงชุด</feature>
</features>
<features module="หน้าจอหลัก">
<feature>เปิดหรือปิดเมจิกแคปซูลได้ในบริการระบบบางอย่าง ไปที่การตั้งค่า > การแจ้งเตือนและแถบสถานะ > เมจิกแคปซูลเพื่อทดลองเลย
เพิ่มประสิทธิภาพเลย์เอาต์, เอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวและเอฟเฟ็กต์การแสดงผลไอคอนของแผงการแจ้งเตือนในบางสถานการณ์
กดแอปไอคอนค้างเพื่อไปที่การตั้งค่าการอนุญาตอย่างรวดเร็ว</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB การยืนยันหรือข้อความแจ้งเตือนความปลอดภัยจะปรากฏเมื่อคุณเลือกถ่ายโอนรูปภาพหรือถ่ายโอนไฟล์ / Android Auto แทนที่จะชาร์จเท่านั้นเพื่อให้แน่ใจถึงการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลที่ปลอดภัยขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>ในตอนนี้คุณสามารถซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลักได้ ทดลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ความปลอดภัยและความเป็นส่วนตัว > การปกป้องอุปกรณ์และข้อมูล > ซ่อนแอปจากหน้าจอหลัก
มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ต.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng update na ito ang feature na I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon. Bukod pa rito, puwedeng itago ang mga icon ng home screen. Puwedeng i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Isinasama rin ng release na ito ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon">
<feature>Pumili ng larawan at i-tap ang Ibahagi -> I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon. Awtomatikong ibu-blur ang larawan sa profile, palayaw, numero ng telepono at iba pang sensitibong data sa larawan. Ito ay para protektahan ang privacy mo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Puwede nang i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Sa split-screen mode, i-tap ang button sa gitna ng divider para i-save ang kumbinasyon bilang isang icon sa home screen. Nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa kumbinasyon kapag na-tap ang icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-on o i-off ang Magic Capsule sa ilang serbisyo ng system. Pumunta sa Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Magic Capsule para subukan ito.
Nao-optimize sa ilang sitwasyon ang layout, effect ng paggalaw at effect sa display ng icon ng notification panel.
Pindutin nang matagal ang isang icon ng app para mabilisang pumunta sa mga setting ng pahintulot.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang magtago ng mga icon ng home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng update na ito ang feature na I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon. Bukod pa rito, puwedeng itago ang mga icon ng home screen. Puwedeng i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Isinasama rin ng release na ito ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon">
<feature>Pumili ng larawan at i-tap ang Ibahagi -> I-blur ang Pribadong Impormasyon. Awtomatikong ibu-blur ang larawan sa profile, palayaw, numero ng telepono at iba pang sensitibong data sa larawan. Ito ay para protektahan ang privacy mo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Puwede nang i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Sa split-screen mode, i-tap ang button sa gitna ng divider para i-save ang kumbinasyon bilang isang icon sa home screen. Nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa kumbinasyon kapag na-tap ang icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-on o i-off ang Magic Capsule sa ilang serbisyo ng system. Pumunta sa Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Magic Capsule para subukan ito.
Nao-optimize sa ilang sitwasyon ang layout, effect ng paggalaw at effect sa display ng icon ng notification panel.
Pindutin nang matagal ang isang icon ng app para mabilisang pumunta sa mga setting ng pahintulot.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang magtago ng mga icon ng home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile Gizli Bilgileri Bulanıklaştır özelliği eklenmiştir. Ayrıca başlangıç ekranı simgelerini gizleme, bölünmüş ekran modundaki uygulama kombinasyonlarını kaydetme seçeneği eklenmiştir. USB bağlantı amaçları değiştirilirken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekliliği getirilmiştir. Bu sürüm ayrıca bir güvenlik yaması içermektedir. Güncellemeniz tavsiye edilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gizli Bilgileri Bulanıklaştır">
<feature>Görsel seçin ve Paylaş -> Gizli Bilgileri Bulanıklaştır seçeneğine dokunun. Görseldeki profil resmi, takma ad, telefon numarası ve diğer hassas veriler otomatik olarak bulanıklaştırılacaktır. Bu işlem gizliliğinizi korumak içindir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Çoklu Pencere">
<feature>Bölünmüş ekran modundaki uygulama kombinasyonları artık kaydedilebilir. Bölünmüş ekran modunda, kombinasyonu başlangıç ekranında bir simge olarak kaydetmek için ayırıcının ortasındaki düğmeye dokunun. Simgeye dokunarak kombinasyona hızlı erişim sağlayabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Başlangıç ekranı">
<feature>Sihirli Kapsül bazı sistem servislerinde açılabilir veya kapatılabilir. Denemek için Ayarlar > Bildirimler ve durum çubuğu > Sihirli Kapsül bölümüne gidin.
Bildirim panelinin düzeni, hareket efekti ve simge görüntüleme efekti bazı senaryolarda optimize edilmiştir.
Hızlı bir şekilde izin ayarlarına gitmek için bir uygulama simgesine basılı tutun.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı amacı değiştirilirken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekliliği eklenmiştir. Sadece şarj yerine Fotoğraf aktarımı veya Dosya aktarma/Android Auto'yu seçtiğinizde bir doğrulama ya da güvenlik istemi görünür ve bu da daha güvenli veri aktarımı sağlar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Artık başlangıç ekranı simgelerini gizleyebilirsiniz. Şuraya giderek deneyin: Ayarlar > Güvenlik ve gizlilik > Cihaz ve veri koruması > Uygulamaları Başlangıç Ekranından gizleyin.
Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yaması (Ekim 2024) dahil edilmiştir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/10 web sitemizi ziyaret edin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا مەخپىيەتلىكنى يوشۇرۇش، ئېكران بۆلۈشنى ساقلاش ۋە ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى ئۈستەليۈزى ئىقتىدارىنى ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئ‍ۆزگەرتكەن ۋاقىتتا ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«مەخپىيەتلىكنى يوشۇرۇش»">
<feature>مەخپىيەتلىكىنى يوشۇرىدىغان رەسىمنى تاللىغاندىن كېيىن، «ئورتاقلىشىش > مەخپىيەتلىكنى يوشۇرۇش» نى چەكسىڭىز، رەسىمدىكى باش سۈرەت، نام، يانفون نومۇرى قاتارلىق سەزگۈر ئۇچۇرلارنى بىر كۇنۇپكا بىلەنلا يوشۇرۇپ، مەخپىيەتلىكىڭىزنىڭ بىخەتەرلىكىنى قوغدايدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«كۆپ كۆزنەك»">
<feature>‏ئېكران بۆلۈشنى ساقلاش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئېكران بۆلۈش ھالىتىدە ئېكران بۆلۈش سىزىقىنىڭ ئوتتۇرىدىكى كۇنۇپكىنى چەكسىڭىز، ئېكران بۆلۈش بىرىكمىسى سىنبەلگە شەكلىدە ئۈستەليۈزىگە ساقلىنىدۇ، كېيىن بۇ سىنبەلگىنى چېكىش ئارقىلىق بۇ ئېكران بۆلۈش بىرىكمىسىنى تېزلىكتە ئاچسىڭىز بولىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ئۈستەليۈزى»">
<feature>‏بىر قىسىم سىستېما مۇلازىمىتى لەيلىگۈچ ئۈزچاتىنى قوللايدىغان بولدى، ئۇ ئىشلەتكۈچىنىڭ ئۆزى تەڭشەش ئېھتىياجىنى قاندۇرىدۇ، سىناش يولى: «تەڭشەك > ئۇقتۇرۇش ۋە ھالەت بالدىقى > چاققان لەيلىگۈچ».
بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى ئۇقتۇرۇش بالدىقىنىڭ ئورۇنلاشتۇرۇلۇشى، ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمى ۋە سىنبەلگە كۆرسىتىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.
ئەپ سىنبەلگىسىنى ئۇزۇن باسسىڭىز ئىجازەت تەڭشىكى ئارايۈزىگە قولاي ھالدا كىرەلەيسىز.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«سىستېما»">
<feature>‏‏USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئۆزگەرتكەندە ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، «پەقەت توكلاش» تىن «رەسىم يوللاش» ياكى «ھۆججەت يوللاش/Android Auto» ھالىتىگە ئالماشتۇرغاندا دەلىللەش كۆرۈنمە يۈزى ياكى بىخەتەرلىك ئەسكەرتمىسى پەيدا بولۇپ، مەلۇمات يوللىشىڭىزنى تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر قىلىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > بىخەتەرلىك ۋە مەخپىيەتلىك > ئۈسكۈنە ۋە مەلۇمات قوغداش > ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش.
ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىلى 10-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، سىستېمىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالى بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلانمىسىنىڭ مەزمۇنىغا ئائىت ئۇچۇرلارنى روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتى https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10 نى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення впроваджує функцію "Розмити особисті дані". Крім того, піктограми головного екрана можна приховувати. Комбінації додатків у режимі розділення екрана можна зберігати. У разі змінення цілей підключення через USB потрібна автентифікація користувача. У цьому випуску також реалізовано виправлення системи безпеки. Рекомендується встановити це оновлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Розмити особисті дані">
<feature>Виберіть зображення та торкніться кнопок "Поділитися" > "Розмити особисті дані". Після цього буде автоматично розмито зображення профілю, псевдонім, номер телефону та інші конфіденційні дані на зображенні, щоб захистити вашу конфіденційність.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Багатовіконний режим">
<feature>Тепер можна зберігати комбінації додатків у режимі розділення екрана. Щоб зберегти комбінацію як піктограму на головному екрані, у режимі розділеного екрана торкніться кнопки посередині роздільника. Щоб отримати швидкий доступ до комбінації, торкніться піктограми.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Головний екран">
<feature>У деяких системних службах можна ввімкнути або вимкнути Магічну капсулу. Виберіть "Налаштування" > "Сповіщення та рядок стану" > "Магічна капсула", щоб спробувати.
У деяких сценаріях оптимізовано макет, ефект руху та візуальний ефект піктограм на панелі сповіщень.
Натисніть і утримуйте піктограму додатка, щоб швидко перейти до налаштувань дозволів.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>У разі змінення цілей підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. Якщо замість цілі "Тільки заряджання" вибирано ціль "Передавання фото" або "Передавання файлів / Android Auto", з’являється підказка для проходження перевірки чи контролю безпеки, що зменшує ризик під час передавання даних.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Тепер ви можете приховати значки на головному екрані. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Налаштування" > "Безпека та конфіденційність" > "Захист пристрою та даних" > "Приховати додатки на головному екрані".
Для посилення безпеки системи впроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки Android від жовтня 2024 року. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ نجی معلومات کو دھندلا کریں کی خصوصیت متعارف کرواتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز چھپائے جا سکتے ہیں۔ منقسم سکرین موڈ میں ایپ کے امتزاجات کو محفوظ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو تبدیل کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ یہ ریلیز سکیورٹی پیچ بھی شامل کرتی ہے۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="نجی معلومات کو دھندلا کریں">
<feature>ایک تصویر منتخب کریں اور شیئر کریں -> نجی معلومات کو دھندلا کریں پر ٹیپ کریں۔ تصویر میں پروفائل کی تصویر، عرفی نام، فون نمبر اور دیگر حساس ڈیٹا خود کار طور پر دھندلا ہو جائے گا۔ یہ آپ کی رازداری کی حفاظت کے لیے ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ملٹی ونڈو">
<feature>منقسم اسکرین موڈ میں ایپ کے امتزاج کو اب محفوظ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ منقسم سکرین موڈ میں، ہوم اسکرین پر امتزاج کو بطور آئیکن محفوظ کرنے کے لیے ڈیوائیڈر کے وسط میں بٹن پر ٹیپ کریں۔ آئیکن پر ٹیپ کرنے سے امتزاج تک جلدی رسائی حاصل ہوتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ہوم اسکرین">
<feature>میجک کیپسول کو کچھ سسٹم سروسز میں آن یا آف کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ اسے آزمانے کے لیے ترتیبات > اطلاعات اور اسٹیٹس بار > میجک کیپسول پر جائیں۔
اطلاعی پینل کا لے آؤٹ، حرکت کا اثر اور آئیکن ڈسپلے کا اثر کچھ منظرناموں میں بہتر بنا دیے گئے ہیں۔
اجازت کی ترتیبات پر تیزی سے جانے کے لیے ایپ کے آئیکن کو دیر تک دبائیں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>‏‏USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو سوئچ کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ جب آپ ڈیٹا کی محفوظ منتقلی کو یقینی بناتے ہوئے، صرف چارج کریں کی بجائے، تصاویر منتقل کریں یا فائلز منتقل کریں / Android خود کار کو منتخب کرتے ہیں تو تصدیق یا سکیورٹی اشارہ ظاہر ہوتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>اب آپ ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کو پوشیدہ کر سکتے ہیں۔ اسے یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: ترتیبات > سکیورٹی اور رازداری > ڈیوائس اور ڈیٹا کی حفاظت > ہوم اسکرین سے ایپس پوشیدہ کریں۔
سسٹم سکیورٹی کے لیے Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اکتوبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ملاحظہ کریں</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanishda Shaxsiy axborotni xiralashtirish funksiyasi taqdim etildi. Bundan tashqari, bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitish mumkin. Ajratilgan ekran rejimida ilovalar kombinatsiyasi saqlanishi mumkin. USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. Bu nashrga xavfsizlik tuzatmasi ham kiritildi. Uni yangilash tavsiya etiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Shaxsiy axborotni xiralashtirish">
<feature>Rasmni tanlang va Ulashish -> Shaxsiy axborotni xiralashtirish bandini bosing. Rasmdagi profil rasmi, nik, telefon raqami va boshqa shaxsiy maʼlumotlar avtomatik xiralashtiriladi. Bu maxfiyligingizni himoya qilish uchun zarur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bir nechta oyna">
<feature>Ajratilgan ekran rejimida endi ilovalar kombinatsiyasi saqlanishi mumkin. Kombinatsiyani bosh ekranga belgi sifatida saqlash uchun Ajratilgan ekran rejimida ajratkich markazidagi tugmani bosing. Bu belgini bosish kombinatsiyaga tezkor kirish imkonini beradi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bosh ekran">
<feature>Ayrim tizim xizmatlarida Sehrli kapsulani yoqish yoki faolsizlantirish mumkin. Sinash uchun Sozlamalar > Bildirishnomalar va holat paneli > Sehrli kapsula rukniga kiring.
Bildirishnomalar panelining ayrim holatlardagi joylashuvi, harakat effekti va belgilarni koʻrsatish effekti optimallandi.
Ruxsat sozlamalariga tezkor kirish uchun ilova belgisini uzoq bosib turing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. “Faqat quvvatlash” oʻrniga “Suratlarni o‘tkazish” yoki “Fayllarni uzatish / Android Auto” tanlaganida, maʼlumotlarni xavfsiz uzatishni taʼminlash uchun tasdiqlash yoki xavfsizlik haqida ogohlantirish oynasi ochiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Endi bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitishingiz mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Xavfsizlik va maxfiylik > Qurilma va maʼlumotlar himoyasi > Bosh ekranda ilovalarni berkitish.
Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, oktabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này giới thiệu tính năng Làm mờ thông tin riêng tư. Ngoài ra, có thể ẩn các biểu tượng trên màn hình chính. Có thể lưu các kiểu kết hợp ứng dụng ở chế độ màn hình chia. Cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB. Bản phát hành này cũng tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Chúng tôi khuyến nghị bạn cập nhật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Làm mờ thông tin riêng tư">
<feature>Chọn một hình ảnh rồi chạm vào Chia sẻ -> Làm mờ thông tin riêng tư. Ảnh đại diện, biệt danh, số điện thoại và dữ liệu nhạy cảm khác trong hình ảnh sẽ tự động bị làm mờ. Việc này nhằm bảo vệ quyền riêng tư của bạn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Đa cửa sổ">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể lưu các kiểu kết hợp ứng dụng ở chế độ màn hình chia. Ở chế độ màn hình chia, hãy chạm vào nút ở giữa đường phân cách để lưu kiểu kết hợp đó làm biểu tượng trên màn hình chính. Chạm vào biểu tượng để bật quyền truy cập nhanh vào kiểu kết hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Màn hình chính">
<feature>Bạn có thể bật hoặc tắt Magic Capsule trong một số dịch vụ hệ thống. Hãy vào Cài đặt > Thanh thông báo và trạng thái > Magic Capsule để dùng thử.
Tối ưu hóa bố cục, hiệu ứng chuyển động và hiệu ứng hiển thị biểu tượng của bảng thông báo trong một số trường hợp.
Nhấn và giữ biểu tượng ứng dụng để chuyển nhanh đến mục cài đặt quyền.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB. Một thông báo nhắc xác minh hoặc bảo mật sẽ xuất hiện khi bạn chọn Truyền tải ảnh hoặc Truyền tệp tin/Android Auto, thay vì Chỉ sạc pin, giúp truyền dữ liệu an toàn hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể ẩn các biểu tượng trên màn hình chính. Hãy thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Bảo mật và quyền riêng tư > Bảo vệ thiết bị và dữ liệu > Ẩn ứng dụng khỏi Màn hình chính.
Bản cập nhật này tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 10 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增私隱打格、分割屏幕儲存，以及隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標功能，優化部分場景主屏幕使用體驗，更改了 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【私隱打格】">
<feature>選擇需要打格的圖片，然後輕觸「分享 -> 私隱打格」，將自動對您圖片中的頭像、暱稱和手機號碼等敏感資訊一鍵打格，以保護您的私隱安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智能多窗】">
<feature>新增分割屏幕儲存功能。在分割屏幕狀態下輕觸分割屏幕線中間按鈕，可將分割屏幕組合以圖標形式儲存在主屏幕，之後可透過輕觸該圖標即可快速開啟此分割屏幕組合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【主屏幕】">
<feature>部分系統服務支援膠囊開關，滿足用戶自主設定的需求。體驗路徑：「設定 > 通知和狀態欄 > 靈動膠囊」。
優化部分場景通知欄佈局、動畫效果，以及圖標顯示效果。
長按應用程式圖標即可快速進入權限設定介面。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>更改 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」模式時，彈出驗證介面或安全提示，讓您的數據傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全性和私隱 > 裝置和數據保護 > 隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標。
整合 Android 2024年10月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增隱私馬賽克處理、螢幕分割儲存以及隱藏應用程式桌面圖示功能，最佳化在部分場景下的桌面使用體驗，變更 USB 連接方式時增加使用者身分驗證，整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【隱私馬賽克處理】">
<feature>選取需要馬賽克處理的圖片，然後輕觸「分享 -> 隱私馬賽克處理」，將自動一鍵馬賽克處理圖片中的個人檔案圖片、暱稱、手機號碼等敏感資訊，保護您的隱私安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>新增螢幕分割儲存功能，螢幕分割狀態下輕觸螢幕分割線中間按鈕，可將螢幕分割組合，以圖示形式儲存在桌面，後續透過輕觸該圖示即可快捷開啟此螢幕分割組合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面】">
<feature>部分系統服務支援膠囊開關，滿足使用者自主設定的需求，體驗路徑：「設定 > 通知和狀態列 > 靈動膠囊」。
最佳化部分場景通知列版面配置、動畫以及圖示顯示效果。
長按應用程式圖示即可快速進入權限設定介面。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>變更 USB 連接方式時新增使用者身分驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸照片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」模式時，彈出驗證畫面或安全提示，讓您的資料傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隱藏應用程式桌面圖示功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全和隱私 > 裝置與資料保護 > 隱藏應用程式桌面圖示。
整合 Android 2024 年 10 月安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
