<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新优化户外场景人像模式拍照成像效果，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相机】">
<feature>优化户外场景人像模式拍照成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年10月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update enhances the shooting effect in portrait mode outdoors, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Enhances the shooting effect in portrait mode outdoors.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ ከቤት ውጭ ባለው የፖርትሬት ሁነታ ላይ ያለውን የማንሳት ተጽእኖ ያሳድጋል፣ እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ካሜራ">
<feature>ከቤት ውጭ በፖርትሬት ሁነታ ላይ የማንሳት ተጽእኖን ያሻሽላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኦክ 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የሚከተለውን የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ ይጎብኙ፦ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث الموصى به تأثير التصوير في وضع البورتريه في الأماكن الخارجية، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الكاميرا">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث تأثير التصوير في وضع البورتريه في الأماكن الخارجية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أكتوبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটে বাহিৰত প'ৰ্ট্ৰেইট মোডত শ্বুটিঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কেমেৰা">
<feature>বাহিৰত প'ৰ্ট্ৰেইট মোডত শ্বুটিঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (অক্টোবৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə açıq havada portret rejimində çəkiliş effektini yaxşılaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Kamera</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Oktyabr 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki ningkatake efek ngrekam ing mode potret njaba, lan nggabungake patch keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ningkatake efek ngrekam ing mode potret njaba.">
<feature/>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch Keamanan Android (Oktober 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, preporučeno ažuriranje poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portret i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portreta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, preporučeno ažuriranje poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portret i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portreta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, preporučeno ažuriranje poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portret i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Poboljšava efekat snimanja napolju u režimu portreta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне паляпшае эфект здымкі ў кніжнай арыентацыі, калі вы здымаеце на вуліцы, і ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Палепшаны эфект здымкі ў кніжнай арыентацыі, калі вы знаходзіцеся на вуліцы.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (кастрычнік 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, с тази препоръчителна актуализация се подобрява ефектът при заснемане в портретен режим на открито и се включва корекция за сигурност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Подобрява ефекта при заснемане в портретен режим на открито.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (октомври 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি আউটডোরে পোর্ট্রেট মোডে শুটিং এফেক্টকে উন্নত করে এবং এটিতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ক্যামেরা">
<feature>আউটডোরে পোর্ট্রেট মোডে শুটিং এফেক্টকে উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (অক্টোবর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁང་ཕྱིའི་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཀྱི་མི་གཟུགས་རྣམ་པའི་པར་ལེན་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་ཆས།】">
<feature>ཁང་ཕྱིའི་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཀྱི་མི་གཟུགས་རྣམ་པའི་པར་ལེན་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་ 10 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་བསྡེབས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་ཇེ་བཟང་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>

<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje poboljšava efekat snimanja u portretnom načinu rada na otvorenom i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Poboljšava efekat snimanja u portretnom načinu rada na otvorenom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada millora l'efecte de captura en el mode retrat a l'exterior, i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càmera">
<feature>Millora l'efecte de captura en el mode retrat a l'exterior.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (octubre del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato doporučená aktualizace vylepšuje fotografování venku v režimu portrétu a obsahuje bezpečnostní opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Vylepšuje fotografování venku v režimu portrétu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (říjen 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering forbedrer optagelseseffekten i nogle scenarier og integrerer en sikkerhedsrettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Forbedrer optagelseseffekten i portrættilstanden udendørs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (okt 2024) er blevet integreret for øget systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Verbessert den Aufnahmeeffekt im Porträtmodus im Freien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση βελτιώνει το αποτέλεσμα λήψης σε λειτουργία πορτρέτου σε εξωτερικούς χώρους και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κάμερα">
<feature>Βελτιώνει το αποτέλεσμα λήψης σε λειτουργία πορτρέτου σε εξωτερικούς χώρους.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Οκτώβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update enhances the shooting effect in portrait mode outdoors, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Enhances the shooting effect in portrait mode outdoors.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada mejora el efecto de disparo en modo retrato al aire libre e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Mejora el efecto de disparo en modo retrato al aire libre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada mejora el efecto de captura en modo Retrato al aire libre e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Mejora el efecto de captura en modo Retrato al aire libre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus suurendab pildistamisefekti õues portreerežiimis ja sisaldab turvapaika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaamera">
<feature>Parandab pildistamisefekti õues portreerežiimis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (oktoober 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, gomendatutako eguneratze honetan aire librean argazki bertikalak ateratzeko efektuak hobetu dira eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Aire librean argazki bertikalak ateratzeko efektuak hobetu dira.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko urr.) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی عملکرد عکس‌برداری در حالت پرتره در فضای باز را بهبود می‌بخشد و حاوی یک وصله امنیتی است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="دوربین">
<feature>عملکرد عکس‌برداری در حالت پرتره در فضای باز را بهبود می‌بخشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (اکتبر ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="نکات قابل‌توجه:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys parantaa kuvaustehostetta muotokuvatilassa ulkona ja sisällyttää turvallisuuskorjauksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Parantaa kuvaustehostetta muotokuvatilassa ulkona.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (lokakuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée améliore l'effet de prise de vue en mode portrait en extérieur et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Améliore l'effet de prise de vue en mode portrait en extérieur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée améliore l'effet de prise de vue en mode portrait en extérieur et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Améliore l'effet de prise de vue en mode portrait en extérieur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada mellora o efecto de captura no modo de retrato en exteriores e incorpora un parche de seguranza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Mellora o efecto de captura no modo de retrato en exteriores.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (outubro de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia a un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ બહાર પોર્ટ્રેટ મોડમાં શૂટિંગના પ્રભાવને વધારે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કૅમેરા">
<feature>બહાર પોર્ટ્રેટ મોડમાં શૂટિંગના પ્રભાવને વધારે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ઑક્ટોબર 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>

<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, यह अनुशंसित अद्यतन आउटडोर में लिए जाने वाले पोर्ट्रेट मोड के शूटिंग प्रभाव को बेहतर बनाता है और एक सुरक्षा पैच शामिल करता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>आउटडोर के लिए पोर्ट्रेट मोड में शूटिंग प्रभाव को बेहतर बनाया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem poboljšava efekt snimanja u portretnom načinu rada na otvorenom, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Poboljšava se efekt snimanja u portretnom načinu rada na otvorenom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (listopad 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Tisztelt felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés javítja a fényképezési hatást a szabadtéri portré módban, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Javítja a fényképezési hatást portré módban a szabadban.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. október). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini meningkatkan efek pengambilan gambar dalam mode potret di luar ruangan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Meningkatkan efek pengambilan gambar dalam mode potret di luar ruangan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini meningkatkan efek pengambilan gambar dalam mode potret di luar ruangan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Meningkatkan efek pengambilan gambar dalam mode potret di luar ruangan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato migliora l'effetto di scatto in modalità Ritratto all'aperto e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>Migliora l'effetto di scatto in modalità Ritratto all'aperto.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato migliora l'effetto di scatto in modalità Ritratto all'aperto e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>Migliora l'effetto di scatto in modalità Ritratto all'aperto.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה משפר את אפקט הצילום במצב דיוקן בחוץ, וכולל תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>משפר את אפקט הצילום במצב דיוקן בחוץ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה משפר את אפקט הצילום במצב דיוקן בחוץ, וכולל תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>משפר את אפקט הצילום במצב דיוקן בחוץ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の推奨更新では、屋外でのポートレートモードでの撮影効果が強化され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="カメラ">
<feature>屋外でのポートレートモードでの撮影効果が強化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年10月）が組み込まれます。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება აძლიერებს გარეთ გადაღების ეფექტს პორტრეტის რეჟიმში და შემოაქვს უსაფრთხოების შესწორება.</feature>
</features>
<features module="კამერა">
<feature>აძლიერებს გარეთ გადაღების ეფექტს პორტრეტის რეჟიმში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ოქტომბერი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту сыртта портрет режимінде түсіру әсерін жақсартады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Сыртта портрет режимінде түсіру әсерін жақсартады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қазан, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនថតក្នុងម៉ូដរូបភាពពាក់កណ្តាលខ្លួននៅខាងក្រៅអគារប្រសើរឡើង និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កាមេរ៉ា​">
<feature>ធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនថតក្នុងម៉ូដរូបភាពពាក់កណ្តាលខ្លួននៅខាងក្រៅអគារប្រសើរឡើង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (តុលា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಹೊರಾಂಗಣದಲ್ಲಿ ಪೋರ್ಟ್ರೇಟ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
<feature>ಹೊರಾಂಗಣದಲ್ಲಿ ಪೋರ್ಟ್ರೇಟ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಅಕ್ಟೋಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트는 야외에서 포트레이트 모드의 촬영 효과를 개선하고 보안 패치를 적용했습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="카메라">
<feature>야외에서 포트레이트 모드의 촬영 효과를 향상시킵니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 10월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະບາຍດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້​ປັບປຸງ​ເອັບ​ເຟັກການ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​ໃນສະພາບ​ກາງ​ແຈ້ງ​ໂໝດຮູບເຄິ່ງຕົວ​ ແລະ ລວມ​ເອົາ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
<feature>ປັບປຸງ​ເອັບ​ເຟັກ​ກາ​ນຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​​ກາງ​ແຈ້ງ​ໂໝດ​ຮູບເຄິ່ງຕົວ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ຕຸ​ລາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu pagerinamas fotografavimo portreto režimu lauke efektas ir įtraukiama saugumo pataisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Pagerinamas fotografavimo portreto režimu lauke efektas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. spalio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek uzlabots fotografēšanas efektu portreta režīmā ārā, un tajā ir iekļauts drošības ielāps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Uzlabo fotografēšanas efektu portreta režīmā ārā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada oktobris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट आउटडोर सभ मे पोर्ट्रेट मोड मे शूटिंग प्रभाव केँ वर्धित करैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>आउटडोर सभ मे पोर्ट्रेट मोड मे शूटिंग प्रभाव केँ वर्धित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, mā tēnei whakahōutanga tūtohutia e whakarei ake te pānga tākaro i roto i te aratau poutū i waho, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kāmera">
<feature>He whakarei ake i te pānga tākaro i roto i te aratau poutū i waho.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Oketopa 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање го подобрува ефектот на сликање во режим на портрет на отворено и вградува безбедносна крпеница.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Го подобрува ефектот на сликање во режим на портрет на отворено.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (октомври 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയപ്പെട്ട ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്ഡേറ്റ്, ഔട്ട്‌ഡോറുകളിൽ പോർട്രെയ്റ്റ് മോഡിലെ ഷൂട്ടിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ക്യാമറ">
<feature>ഔട്ട്‌ഡോറുകളിൽ പോർട്രെയ്റ്റ് മോഡിലെ ഷൂട്ടിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഒക്‌ടോബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр гадаа хөрөг зураг горимд зураг авах нөлөөг сайжруулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаав.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камер">
<feature>Гадаа хөрөг зураг горимд зураг авах эффектийг сайжруулна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны аравдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन घराबाहेर पोर्ट्रेट मोडमध्ये शूटिंग प्रभाव वाढवते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कॅमेरा">
<feature>घराबाहेर पोर्ट्रेट मोडमध्ये शूटिंग प्रभाव वाढवते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (ऑक्टोबर 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 वर जा</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini meningkatkan kesan penangkapan dalam mod potret di luar bangunan dan memasukkan tampalan keselamatan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Tingkatkan kesan penangkapan dalam mod potret di luar bangunan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Okt 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အပြင်ဘက် အလှပုံစနစ်တွင် ရိုက်ကူးမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင်မရာ">
<feature>အပြင်ဘက် အလှပုံစနစ်တွင် ရိုက်ကူးမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (အောက်တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အျပင္ဘက္ အလွပုံစနစ္တြင္ ႐ိုက္ကူးမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင္မရာ">
<feature>အျပင္ဘက္ အလွပုံစနစ္တြင္ ႐ိုက္ကူးမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ေအာက္တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen forbedrer opptakseffekten i portrettmodus utendørs og integrerer en sikkerhetsoppdatering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Forbedrer opptakseffekten i portrettmodus utendørs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (okt 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले पोर्ट्रेट मोडमा बाहिरी वातावरणमा हुँदा सुटिङको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="क्यामेरा">
<feature>पोर्ट्रेट मोडमा बाहिर हुँदा सुटिङको प्रभाव परिष्कार गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अक्टोबर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update verbetert het opname-effect in portretmodus buitenshuis en bevat een beveiligingspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Verbetert het opname-effect in portretmodus buiten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (oktober 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ପୋର୍ଟ୍ରେଟ୍‌ ମୋଡ୍ ଆଉଟଡୋର୍‌ରେ ଶୁଟିଂ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ବଢାଏ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
<feature>ପୋର୍ଟ୍ରେଟ୍‌ ମୋଡ୍ ଆଉଟଡୋର୍‌ରେ ଶୁଟିଂ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ବଢାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅକ୍ଟୋବର 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਆਉਟਡੋਰ ਪੋਰਟ੍ਰੇਟ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
<feature>ਆਉਟਡੋਰ ਪੋਰਟ੍ਰੇਟ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਕਤੂਬਰ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja poprawia efekt zdjęć robionych na zewnątrz w trybie portretowym i zawiera poprawkę zabezpieczeń.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aparat">
<feature>Ulepszono efekt robienia zdjęć w trybie portretowym na zewnątrz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (październik 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, esta atualização recomendada aprimora o efeito de captura no modo retrato em áreas externas e incorpora um patch de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmera">
<feature>Aprimora o efeito de captura no modo retrato em áreas externas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (outubro de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada melhora o efeito de disparo no modo retrato no exterior e incorpora uma correção de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmara">
<feature>Melhora o efeito de disparo no modo retrato no exterior.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma Correção de Segurança Android (Outubro de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată îmbunătățește efectul de fotografiere în modul portret pentru exterior și încorporează o corecție de securitate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cameră foto">
<feature>Îmbunătățește efectul de fotografiere în modul portret pentru exterior.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (octombrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea actualizării nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы улучшить эффект уличной съемки в портретном режиме и внедрить исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Улучшен эффект уличной съемки в портретном режиме.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (октябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය එළිමහනේ ආලේඛ්‍යය ප්‍රකාරයේ රූගත කිරීමේ ප්‍රයෝගය වැඩි දියුණු කරන අතර ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ඇතුළත් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කැමරාව">
<feature>එළිමහනේ ආලේඛ්‍යය ප්‍රකාරයේ රූගත කිරීමේ ප්‍රයෝගය උසස් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ඔක්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>

<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia zlepšuje efekt snímania v režime portrétu v exteriéri a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Zlepšuje efekt snímania v režime portrétu v exteriéri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z októbra 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljšuje učinek pri fotografiranju v pokončnem načinu na prostem in vključuje tudi varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Izboljša učinek pri fotografiranju v pokončnem načinu na prostem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravki za Android (oktober 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen förbättrar fotograferingseffekten i porträttläge utomhus och implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Förbättrar fotograferingseffekten i porträttläge utomhus.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (oktober 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mpendwa mtumiaji, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaboresha athari ya kupiga picha katika hali ya mkao wima nje ya chumba na inajumuisha rekebisho la usalama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Huboresha athari ya kupiga picha katika hali ya mkao wima nje ya chumba.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Okt 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு வெளிப்புறங்களில் போர்ட்ரெயிட் பயன்முறையில் ஷூட்டிங் விளைவை மேம்படுத்துகிறது, பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேமரா">
<feature>வெளிப்புறங்களில் போர்ட்ரெயிட் பயன்முறையில் ஷூட்டிங் விளைவை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (அக் 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ పోర్ట్రెయిట్ మోడ్ అవుట్‌డోర్స్‌లో షూటింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ చేర్చబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కెమెరా">
<feature>పోర్ట్రెయిట్ మోడ్ అవుట్‌డోర్స్‌లో షూటింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రత ప్యాచ్ (అక్టోబర్ 2024) పొందుపరచబడింది. HONOR భద్రత నవీకరణల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำนี้จะปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ในการถ่ายโหมดภาพถ่ายบุคคลกลางแจ้ง และรวมแพตช์รักษาความปลอดภัย</feature>
</features>
<features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
<feature>ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์การถ่ายโหมดภาพถ่ายบุคคลกลางแจ้ง</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ต.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, pinapahusay ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang effect sa pag-shoot sa mga portrait mode sa mga outdoor, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang effect sa pag-shoot sa portrait mode sa mga outdoor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, pinapahusay ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang effect sa pag-shoot sa mga portrait mode sa mga outdoor, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang effect sa pag-shoot sa portrait mode sa mga outdoor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sayın kullanıcı, önerilen güncelleme açık alanda portre modunda çekim efektini güçlendirir ve bir güvenlik yaması içerir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Açık alanda portre modunda çekim efektini güçlendirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yamasını (Ekim 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا دالا كۆرۈنۈشىدە پورترېت ھالىتىدە رەسىمگە تارتىش ۋە سىنغا ئېلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«كامېرا»">
<feature>دالا كۆرۈنۈشىدە پورترېت ھالىتىدە رەسىمگە تارتىش ۋە سىنغا ئېلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 10-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це рекомендоване оновлення покращує ефект зйомки в портретному режимі на відкритому повітрі й впроваджує виправлення системи безпеки.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Покращується ефект зйомки в портретному режимі на відкритому повітрі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від жовтня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ باہر پورٹریٹ موڈ میں شوٹنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور ایک سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کیمرہ">
<feature>باہر پورٹریٹ موڈ میں شوٹنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اکتوبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda tashqaridagi portret rejimida suratga olish effekti yaxshilandi va xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Tashqaridagi portret rejimida suratga olish effekti yaxshilandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, oktabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này sẽ cải thiện hiệu ứng chụp ảnh ở chế độ ảnh chân dung ngoài trời và tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Máy ảnh">
<feature>Tăng cường hiệu ứng chụp ảnh ở chế độ ảnh chân dung ngoài trời.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 10 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新優化戶外場景人像模式拍攝成像效果，整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>優化戶外場景人像模式拍攝成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024年10月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新最佳化在戶外場景下人像模式拍照的成像效果，整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>最佳化在戶外場景下人像模式拍照的成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 10 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features></language>

</root>