<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增隐藏应用桌面图标和USB连接用户身份认证功能，优化状态栏字体图标显示，提升系统稳定性，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【状态栏】">
<feature>优化状态栏字体图标显示，增大字体字号，加粗图标样式，提高信息识别度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>提升系统稳定性，让您的手机运行更稳定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隐藏应用桌面图标功能，体验路径：设置>安全和隐私>设备与数据保护>隐藏应用桌面图标。
新增USB连接用户身份认证功能，在选择“传输照片”或“传输文件 / Android Auto”时，需要进行身份认证，让您的数据传输更安全。
合入安卓2024年10月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, in this update, home screen icons can be hidden, and user authentication is required when using USB connection. This update also optimizes the display of text and icons in status bar. Additionally, this release improves the system stability, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Increases the text size, and bolds the icons to make the information easier to recognize.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>You can now hide home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen.
User authentication is required when using USB connection. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, ensuring safer data transfer.
Android security patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ በዚህ ዝማኔ ውስጥ የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች ሊደበቁ ይችላሉ እና የUSB ግንኙነት ሲጠቀሙ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። እንዲሁም ይህ ማሻሻያ በሁኔታ አሞሌ ውስጥ የጽሑፍ እና የአዶዎች ማሳያን ያተባል። በተጨማሪም፣ ይህ ልቀት የስርዓቱን መረጋጋት ያሻሽላል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን በውስጡ ያካትታል። እንዲያዘምኑ ይመከራል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ሁኔታ አሞሌ">
<feature>መረጃውን ለማወቅ ይበልጥ ቀላል ለማድረግ የጽሑፍ መጠኑን ይጨምራል፣ እና አዶዎቹን ይደፍራል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>መሳሪያዎ ን በበለጠ እርጋታ ለማሄድ ለማድረግ የስርዓት መረጋጋትን ያሻሽላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>አሁን የመነሻ ማያ አዶዎችን መደበቅ ይችላሉ። ወደ እነዚህ በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ደህንነት እና ግላዊነት > የመሳሪያ እና የውሂብ ጥበቃ > መተግበሪያዎችን ከመነሻ ገጽ ደብቅ።
የUSB ግንኙነት ሲጠቀሙ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ፎቶዎችን አስተላልፍ ወይም ፋይሎችን አስተላልፍ / አንድሮይድ አውቶ የሚለውን ሲመርጡ፣ ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ የውሂብ ማስተላለፍን ለማረጋግጥ የማረጋገጫ ወይም የደህንነት ጥያቄ ይመጣል።
አንድሮይድ ደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኦክቶበር 2024) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካትቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ማሻሻያዎች የበለጠ መረጃ ለማግኘት https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 የሚለውን ይጎብኙ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يمكن إخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية في هذا التحديث. ويجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند استخدام اتصال USB. يحسّن هذا التحديث أيضًا عرض النصوص والأيقونات في شريط الحالة. علاوةً على ذلك، يحسّن هذا الإصدار أيضًا استقرار النظام، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان. من المستحسن التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="شريط الحالة">
<feature>يزيد حجم النص ويطبق التنسيق الغامق على الأيقونات لتسهيل التعرف على المعلومات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يحسّن استقرار النظام لجعل جهازك يعمل بشكل أكثر استقرارًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>يمكنك الآن إخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الأمان والخصوصية > حماية الجهاز > إخفاء التطبيقات من الشاشة الرئيسية.
يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند استخدام اتصال USB. تظهر مطالبة التحقق أو الأمان عندما تحدد "نقل الصور" أو "نقل الملفات/أندرويد أوتو"، مما يضمن نقل البيانات بشكل أكثر أمانًا.
تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أكتوبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটত হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাব পাৰি আৰু USB সংযোগ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। এই আপডেটটোৱে স্থিতি দণ্ডিকাত পাঠ আৰু চিহ্নবোৰৰ প্ৰদৰ্শনো অনুকূলন কৰে। ইয়াৰ উপৰিও, এই মুক্তিয়ে ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। এইটো আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা">
<feature>তথ্য চিনাক্ত কৰিবলৈ সহজ বনাবলৈ পাঠৰ আকাৰ বঢ়ায় আৰু চিহ্নবোৰ ব'ল্ড কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>আপোনাৰ ডিভাইচ অধিক স্থিৰতাৰে চলাবলৈ ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>আপুনি এতিয়া হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাব পাৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > নিৰাপত্তা আৰু গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইচ আৰু ডাটা সুৰক্ষা > হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ পৰা এপ্প্‌সমূহ লুকুৱাওক।
USB সংযোগ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। আপুনি ফটোসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক বা ফাইলসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক / Android Auto বাছনি কৰাৰ সময়ত এটা প্ৰমাণীকৰণ বা নিৰাপত্তাৰ সংকেত দেখা পায়, যিয়ে নিৰাপদ ডাটা স্থানান্তৰ নিশ্চিত কৰে।
ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (অক্টোবৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmədə əsas ekran nişanları gizlədilə bilər və USB bağlantısından istifadə edərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Bu yeniləmə, həmçinin status panelində mətn və nişanların göstərilməsini optimallaşdırır. Bundan əlavə, bu buraxılış sistemin sabitliyini yaxşılaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir. Yeniləmək tövsiyə olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status paneli">
<feature>Məlumatın daha asan tanınması üçün mətn ölçüsünü artırır və nişanları qalınlaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Cihazınızın daha stabil işləməsi üçün sistem stabilliyini təkmilləşdirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>İndi əsas ekran nişanlarını gizlədə bilərsiniz. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Təhlükəsizlik və məxfilik > Cihaz və verilənlərin mühafizəsi > Proqramları əsas ekrandan gizlədin.
USB bağlantısından istifadə edərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Verilənlərin daha təhlükəsiz ötürülməsini təmin edərək Fotoları ötürün və ya Faylları ötürün / Android Auto seçdiyiniz zaman doğrulama və ya təhlükəsizlik sorğusu görünür.
Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (oktyabr 2024) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 veb-saytımıza daxil olun</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, ing panganyaran iki, ikon layar ngarep bisa didhelikake, lan otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika nggunakake sambungan USB. Panganyaran iki uga ngoptimalake tampilan teks lan ikon ing garis status. Saliyane iku, rilis iki ngapikake stabilitas sistem, lan nggabungake patch keamanan. Sampeyan disaranake supaya nganyarake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Garis status">
<feature>Nambah ukuran teks lan ngandeli ikon supaya informasi bisa luwih gampang dikenali.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ngapikake stabilitas sistem supaya piranti mlaku kanthi luwih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Sampeyan saiki bisa ndhelikake ikon layar ngarep. Coba fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Keamanan lan privasi > Piranti lan proteksi data > Dhelikake apl saka Layar ngarep.
Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika nggunakake sambungan USB. Prentah verifikasi utawa keamanan bakal muncul nalika sampeyan milih Transfer foto utawa Transfer file/Android Auto, saengga jamin transfer data sing luwih aman.
Patch keamanan Android (Okt 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju neke ikone početnog ekrana mogu da budu sakrivene i potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Ovo ažuriranje takođe optimizuje prikaz teksta i ikona na statusnoj traci. Pored toga, izdanje poboljšava stabilnost sistema i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrij aplikacije s početnog ekrana.
Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Verifikacija ili sigurnosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju neke ikone početnog ekrana mogu da budu sakrivene i potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Ovo ažuriranje takođe optimizuje prikaz teksta i ikona na statusnoj traci. Pored toga, izdanje poboljšava stabilnost sistema i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrij aplikacije s početnog ekrana.
Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Verifikacija ili sigurnosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju neke ikone početnog ekrana mogu da budu sakrivene i potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Ovo ažuriranje takođe optimizuje prikaz teksta i ikona na statusnoj traci. Pored toga, izdanje poboljšava stabilnost sistema i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećanje veličine teksta i podebljanje ikona radi boljeg pregleda informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrij aplikacije s početnog ekrana.
Potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se koristi veza putem USB-a. Verifikacija ili sigurnosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.
Bezbednosna zakrpa Android (okt 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima HONOR, posetite našu veb stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, у гэтым абнаўленні можна схаваць значкі галоўнага экрана, а пры выкарыстанні падключэння да USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Таксама гэта абнаўленне аптымізуе адлюстраванне тэксту і значкоў на панэлі стану. У гэтай версіі палепшана ўстойлівасць сістэмы, і яна ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Рэкамендуецца ўстанавіць абнаўленне.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панэль стану">
<feature>Павялічаны памер тэксту, а значкі сталі больш выразнымі, што спрашчае ўспрыманне інфармацыі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Устойлівасць сістэмы павышана, што робіць працу прылады больш стабільнай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Цяпер вы можаце хаваць значкі галоўнага экрана. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Бяспека і прыватнасць > Абарона прылады і даных > Схаваць праграмы з галоўнага экрана».
Пры выкарыстанні падключэння да USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Калі вы выбіраеце «Перадача фота» ці «Перадача файлаў / Android Auto», з’яўляецца запыт праверкі сапраўднасці або праверкі бяспекі, каб гарантаваць бяспечную перадачу даных.
Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (кастрычнік 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, в тази актуализация иконите на началния екран може да бъдат скрити, а при използване на USB връзка се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Тази актуализация също така оптимизира показването на текста и иконите в лентата за състоянието. Освен това тази версия подобрява стабилността на системата и включва корекция за сигурност. Препоръчва се да актуализирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Лента за състоянието">
<feature>Увеличава размера на текста и удебелява шрифта на иконите, за да направи информацията по-лесно разпознаваема.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Подобрява стабилността на системата, за да работи устройството ви по-стабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>Вече можете да скривате иконите на началния екран. Изпробвайте го, като отидете на: „Настройки > Сигурност и поверителност > Устройство и защита на данни > Скриване на приложения от началния екран“.
При използване на USB връзка се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Когато изберете „Прехвърляне на снимки“ или „Прехвърляне на файлове/Android Auto“, се появява подкана за проверка или подкана за сигурност, което осигурява по-безопасен трансфер на данните.
Включена е корекция на сигурността на Android (октомври 2024 г.) за системна сигурност. За повече информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR, моля, посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটে হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলি লুকানো যেতে পারে, এবং USB সংযোগ ব্যবহার করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। এই আপডেটটি স্ট্যাটাস বারে টেক্সট এবং আইকনগুলির ডিসপ্লেকেও অপটিমাইজ করে। এছাড়াও এই রিলিজটি সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতাকে উন্নত করে এবং এটিতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। আপডেট করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="স্ট্যাটাস বার">
<feature>পাঠ্যের আকার বাড়ায়, এবং তথ্য শনাক্ত করাকে আরো সহজ করতে আইকনগুলিকে বোল্ড করে দেয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>আপনার ডিভাইসকে আরো স্থিতিশীলভাবে চালানোর জন্য সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>আপনি এখন হোম স্ক্রিন আইকন লুকাতে পারেন। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > নিরাপত্তা ও গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইস এবং ডেটা সুরক্ষা > হোম স্ক্রিন থেকে অ্যাপগুলি লুকান।
USB সংযোগ ব্যবহার করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। আপনি যখন ফটো স্থানান্তর করুন বা ফাইল স্থানান্তর / Android Auto নির্বাচন করেন তখন একটি যাচাইকরণ বা নিরাপত্তা প্রম্পট দেখতে পাওয়া যায়, যা নিরাপদ ডেটা স্থানান্তর নিশ্চিত করে।
সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (অক্টোবর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་དང་ USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ར་སྤྲོད་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་པ་དང་། རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་ཡིག་གཟུགས་རིས་རྟགས་མངོན་སྟོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁ་ཤས་ཀྱི་འཕྲིན་གཏོང་གི་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ནས། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་།】">
<feature>རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་ཡིག་གཟུགས་མངོན་སྟོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡིག་གཟུགས་ཡིག་ཨང་ཇེ་ཆེར་བཏང་བ་དང་རིས་རྟགས་ཕྱི་ཚུལ་སྦོམ་བཟོ་བྱས་ནས། ཆ་འཕྲིན་ངོས་འཛིན་ཚད་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་སྟེ། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་གྱི་འཁོར་སྐྱོད་སྔར་ལས་བརྟན་པོ་ཡོང་བར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བདེ་འཇགས་དང་སྒེར་གསང་། དེ་ནས་སྒྲིག་ཆས་དང་གཞི་གྲངས་སྲུང་སྐྱོབ། དེ་ནས་སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།
USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ར་སྤྲོད་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས། འདྲ་པར་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ཡང་ན་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་། / Android Auto འདེམས་སྐབས། ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་བྱ་དགོས་ཏེ། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་བརྒྱུད་སྐུར་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས་བྱེད།
ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 10 བའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, u ovom ažuriranju se mogu sakriti ikone s početnog ekrana, a prilikom korištenja USB veze je obavezna provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Ovo izdanje također optimizira prikaz teksta i ikona na statusnoj traci. Osim toga, ovo izdanje poboljšava stabilnost sistema i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da izvršite ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećava veličinu teksta i podebljava ikone radi lakšeg prepoznavanja informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema kako bi se omogućio stabilniji rad uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Sada možete sakriti ikone s početnog ekrana. Isprobajte ovu funkciju odlaskom u: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrivanje aplikacija s početnog ekrana.
Prilikom korištenja USB veze je obavezna provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android Auto prikazuje se potvrda ili sigurnosni upit kako bi se osigurao sigurniji prijenos podataka.
Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (okt 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, en aquesta actualització les icones de la pantalla inicial es poden amagar i es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan s'utilitza una connexió USB. Aquesta actualització també optimitza la visualització del text i les icones a la barra d'estat. A més, aquesta versió millora l'estabilitat del sistema i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Es recomana actualitzar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra d'estat">
<feature>S'ha augmentat la mida del text i posat en negreta les icones perquè la informació sigui més fàcil de reconèixer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Millora l'estabilitat del sistema, la qual cosa permet que el funcionament del dispositiu sigui més estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>Ara podeu amagar les icones de la pantalla inicial. Proveu-ho des de: Configuració > Seguretat i privacitat > Protecció del dispositiu i de les dades > Amagar aplicacions de la Pantalla inicial.
Es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan s'utilitza una connexió USB. Apareix un missatge de verificació o seguretat quan seleccioneu Transferir fotos o Transferir fitxers/Android Auto, la qual cosa garanteix una transferència de dades més segura.
S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (octubre del 2024) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, visiteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, v této aktualizaci lze skrýt ikony domovské obrazovky a při použití připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Tato aktualizace také optimalizuje zobrazení textu a ikon ve stavovém řádku. Tato verze dále zlepšuje stabilitu systému a obsahuje bezpečnostní opravu. Doporučujeme aktualizovat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stavový řádek">
<feature>Zvětší velikost textu a zvýrazní ikony tučně, aby byly informace snáze rozpoznatelné.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Vylepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zařízení pracovalo stabilněji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Nyní můžete skrýt ikony domovské obrazovky. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Zabezpečení a soukromí > Ochrana zařízení a dat > Skrýt aplikace na domovské obrazovce.
Při používání připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Když vyberete možnost Přenos fotografií nebo Přenos souborů / Android Auto, zobrazí se výzva k ověření nebo výzva zabezpečení, což zajistí bezpečnější přenos dat.
Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (říjen 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, i denne opdatering kan startskærmens ikoner skjules, og brugergodkendelse er påkrævet ved brug af en USB-forbindelse. Denne opdatering optimerer også visningen af tekst og ikoner på statuslinjen. Desuden forbedrer denne udgave systemstabiliteten og integrerer en sikkerhedsrettelse. Opdatering anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statuslinje">
<feature>Øger tekststørrelsen og fremhæver ikonerne for at gøre oplysningerne nemmere at genkende.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Forbedrer systemstabiliteten, så din enhed kører mere stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Du kan nu skjule startskærmens ikoner. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Sikkerhed og personlige oplysninger > Enhed og databeskyttelse > Skjul apps på Startskærmen.
Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet ved brug af en USB-forbindelse. En bekræftelses- eller sikkerhedsprompt vises, når du vælger Overfør fotos eller Overfør filer/Android Auto, hvilket garanterer sikrere dataoverførsel.
Android sikkerhedsrettelse (okt 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden und bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Aktualisierung optimiert auch die Anzeige von Text und Symbolen in der Statusleiste. Darüber hinaus verbessert diese Version die Systemstabilität und enthält ein Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden und bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Aktualisierung optimiert auch die Anzeige von Text und Symbolen in der Statusleiste. Darüber hinaus verbessert diese Version die Systemstabilität und enthält ein Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung können Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausgeblendet werden und bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Aktualisierung optimiert auch die Anzeige von Text und Symbolen in der Statusleiste. Darüber hinaus verbessert diese Version die Systemstabilität und enthält ein Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusleiste">
<feature>Vergrößert die Schrift und stellt die Symbole fett dar, damit die Informationen leichter zu erkennen sind.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Probieren Sie es aus, indem Sie zu „Einstellungen“ > „Sicherheit und Datenschutz“ > „Geräte- und Datenschutz“ > „Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden“ gehen.
Bei Nutzung einer USB-Verbindung ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen/Android Auto“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.
Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, σε αυτή την ενημέρωση, τα εικονίδια της αρχικής οθόνης μπορούν να αποκρυφθούν και απαιτείται έλεγχος ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά τη χρήση σύνδεσης USB. Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί επίσης την εμφάνιση κειμένου και εικονιδίων στη γραμμή κατάστασης. Επιπλέον, αυτή η έκδοση βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Συνιστάται η ενημέρωση.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Γραμμή κατάστασης">
<feature>Αυξάνει το μέγεθος του κειμένου και κάνει πιο έντονα τα εικονίδια για να διευκολύνει την αναγνώριση των πληροφοριών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος για να λειτουργεί η συσκευή σας πιο σταθερά.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Πλέον μπορείτε να αποκρύψετε τα εικονίδια της αρχικής οθόνης. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Ασφάλεια και απόρρητο > Προστασία συσκευής και δεδομένων > Απόκρυψη εφαρμογών από την Αρχική οθόνη.
Απαιτείται έλεγχος ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά τη χρήση σύνδεσης USB. Ένα μήνυμα επαλήθευσης ή ασφάλειας εμφανίζεται όταν επιλέγετε «Μεταφορά φωτογραφιών» ή «Μεταφορά αρχείων/Android Auto», εξασφαλίζοντας πιο ασφαλή μεταφορά δεδομένων.
Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Οκτώβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, in this update, home screen icons can be hidden, and user authentication is required when using USB connection. This update also optimises the display of text and icons in status bar. Additionally, this release improves the system stability, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Increases the text size, and bolds the icons to make the information easier to recognise.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>You can now hide home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen.
User authentication is required when using USB connection. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, ensuring safer data transfer.
Android security patch (Oct 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, en esta actualización, los iconos de la pantalla principal se pueden ocultar y se requiere autenticación del usuario cuando se usa la conexión USB. Esta actualización también optimiza la visualización de texto e iconos en la barra de estado. Además, esta versión también mejora la estabilidad del sistema e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta el tamaño del texto y pone los iconos en negrita para que la información sea más fácil de reconocer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Ahora puede ocultar los iconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección de dispositivos y datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal.
Se requiere autenticación de usuario al usar la conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.
Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, en esta actualización, los íconos de la pantalla principal se pueden ocultar y se requiere autenticación del usuario cuando se usa la conexión USB. Esta actualización también optimiza la visualización de texto e íconos en la barra de estado. Además, esta versión mejora la estabilidad del sistema e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta el tamaño del texto y pone los íconos en negrita para que la información sea más fácil de reconocer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Ahora puede ocultar los íconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección del dispositivo y de los datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal.
Se requiere autenticación de usuario cuando se usa la conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.
Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! Selle värskendusega saab avakuva ikoone peita ja USB-ühenduse kasutamisel on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. See värskendus optimeerib ka teksti ja ikoonide kuvamist olekuribal. Lisaks muudab see värskendus süsteemi stabiilsemaks ning sisaldab turvapaika. Soovitatav on värskendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Olekuriba">
<feature>Suurendab teksti suurust ja kuvab ikoonid paksult, et teave oleks lihtsamini äratuntav.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>Parandab süsteemi stabiilsust, et teie seade töötaks ühtlasemalt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>Nüüd saate avakuva ikoonid ära peita. Proovige seda, minnes menüüsse Sätted > Turve ja privaatsus > Seadme- ja andmekaitse > Peida avakuval olevad rakendused.
USB-ühenduse kasutamise korral on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. Kui valite funktsiooni Edasta fotosid või Edasta faile / Android Auto, kuvatakse kinnitus- või turvaviip, mis tagab turvalisema andmeedastuse.
Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (oktoober 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, eguneratze honetan, hasierako pantailako ikonoak ezkuta daitezke, eta erabiltzailea autentifikatu behar da USB konexioa erabiltzea. Eguneratze honetan, egoera-barrako testuaren eta ikonoen bistaratzea ere optimizatu da. Gainera, bertsio honetan sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da eta segurtasun-adabaki bat du. Eguneratzea gomendatzen da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Egoera-barra">
<feature>Testuaren tamaina handitu da eta ikonoak letra lodiz ageri dira informazioa errazago ezagutzeko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetzen du, gailuak hobeto funtziona dezan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Orain hasierako pantailaren ikonoak ezkuta ditzakezu. Proba ezazu hona joanda: Ezarpenak > Segurtasuna eta pribatutasuna > Gailuaren eta datuen babesa > Ezkutatu hasierako pantailako aplikazioak.
Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa beharrezkoa da USB konexioa erabiltzean. Egiaztapen- edo segurtasun-gonbidapen bat bistaratuko da Transferitu argazkiak edo Transferitu fitxategiak / Android Auto hautatzen duzunean, datuen transferentzia seguruagoa ziurtatuz.
Sistemaren segurtasunerako, Android-en segurtasun-adabakia gehitu da (2024ko urr). HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، در این به‌روزرسانی، آیکون‌های صفحۀ اصلی را می‌توان پنهان کرد و هنگام استفاده از اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر الزامی است. این به‌روزرسانی همچنین نمایش متن و آیکون‌ها در نوار وضعیت را بهینه می‌کند. به‌علاوه، این نسخه پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد و حاوی یک وصله امنیتی است. توصیه می‌شود به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوار وضعیت">
<feature>اندازۀ متن را افزایش می‌دهد و آیکون‌ها را پررنگ می‌کند تا اطلاعات راحت‌تر تشخیص داده شوند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد تا دستگاه شما عملکرد پایدارتری داشته باشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>اکنون می توانید آیکون‌های صفحۀ اصلی را پنهان کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: تنظیمات > امنیت و حریم خصوصی > محافظت از دستگاه و داده‌ها > پنهان کردن برنامه‌ها از «صفحۀ اصلی».
هنگام استفاده از اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر لازم است. هنگامی‌که گزینه «انتقال تصاویر» یا «انتقال فایل‌ها / Android Auto» را انتخاب می‌کنید، یک پیام‌واره تأیید یا امنیتی ظاهر می‌شود تا انتقال ایمن‌تر داده‌ها تأمین شود.
وصله امنیتی Android (اکتبر ۲۰۲۴) برای امنیت سیستم گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر درباره به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به نشانی https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 مراجعه کنید</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämän päivityksen jälkeen aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet voidaan piilottaa ja käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitäntää käytetään. Tämä päivitys myös optimoi tekstin ja kuvakkeiden näyttämisen tilapalkissa. Lisäksi tämä päivitys parantaa järjestelmän vakautta ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen. Päivittämistä suositellaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tilapalkki">
<feature>Suurentaa tekstin kokoa ja lihavoi kuvakkeet, jotta tiedot on helpompi tunnistaa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Parantaa järjestelmän vakautta, jolloin laite toimii vakaammin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Voit nyt piilottaa aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet. Kokeile sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Turvallisuus ja tietosuoja > Laitteen ja tietojen turvallisuus > Piilota sovellukset aloitusnäytöltä.
Käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitäntää käytetään. Kun valitset Siirrä valokuvia tai Siirrä tiedostoja / Android Auto, tarkastus- tai turvallisuuskehote avautuu, mikä varmistaa turvallisemman tiedonsiirron.
Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (lokakuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, dans cette mise à jour, les icônes de l'écran d'accueil peuvent être masquées et l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors de l'utilisation d'une connexion USB. Cette mise à jour optimise également l'affichage du texte et des icônes dans la barre d'état. De plus, cette version améliore la stabilité du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barre d'état">
<feature>Augmente la taille du texte et met en gras les icônes pour rendre les informations plus faciles à reconnaître.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil.
L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors de l'utilisation d'une connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, dans cette mise à jour, les icônes de l'écran d'accueil peuvent être masquées et l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors de l'utilisation d'une connexion USB. Cette mise à jour optimise également l'affichage du texte et des icônes dans la barre d'état. De plus, cette version améliore la stabilité du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barre d'état">
<feature>Augmente la taille du texte et met en gras les icônes pour rendre les informations plus faciles à reconnaître.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil.
L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors de l'utilisation d'une connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.
Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, nesta actualización ocultáronse as iconas da Pantalla de inicio e converteuse en necesaria a autenticación do usuario para usar a conexión USB. Esta actualización tamén optimiza o texto da pantalla e as iconas na Barra de estado. Ademais, esta actualización mellora a estabilidade do sistema e incorpora un parche de seguranza. Recoméndase actualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta o tamaño do texto e destaca as iconas para que sexa máis fácil recoñecer a información.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mellora a estabilidade do sistema para que o dispositivo funcione dun xeito máis estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Agora pode ocultar as iconas da Pantalla de inicio. Pode probalo indo a: Configuración > Seguranza e privacidade > Dispositivo e protección de datos > Ocultar aplicacións de Pantalla de inicio.
A autenticación do usuario é necesaria cando se usa a conexión USB. Aparece unha notificación de seguridade ou verificación cando selecciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, o que garante unha transferencia de datos segura.
Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (outubro 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટમાં, હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નો છુપાવી શકાય છે અને USB કનેક્શનનો ઉપયોગ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. આ અપડેટ સ્થિતિ પટ્ટીમાં ટેક્સ્ટ અને ચિહ્નોના પ્રદર્શનને પણ ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે. વધુમાં, આ રિલિઝ સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતાને સુધારે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે. અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી">
<feature>ટેક્સ્ટનું કદ વધે છે અને માહિતીને ઓળખવામાં સરળ બનાવવા માટે ચિહ્નોને બોલ્ડ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>તમારાં ઉપકરણને વધુ સ્થિર રીતે ચલાવવા સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>તમે હવે હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન છુપાવી શકો છો. આના પર જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > સુરક્ષા અને ગોપનીયતા > ઉપકરણ અને ડેટા સંરક્ષણ > હોમ સ્ક્રીન પરથી એપ્લિકેશન્સ છુપાવો.
USB કનેક્શનનો ઉપયોગ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. જ્યારે તમે સુરક્ષિત ડેટા ટ્રાન્સફરને સુનિશ્ચિત કરીને ફોટા ટ્રાન્સફર કરો અથવા ફાઇલો ટ્રાન્સફર કરો / Android Auto પસંદ કરો ત્યારે ચકાસણી અથવા સુરક્ષા પ્રોમ્પ્ટ દેખાય છે.
સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે એન્ડ્રોઇડ Android પેચ (ઓક્ટો 2024) સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से होम स्क्रीन आइकन छिपाए जा सकते हैं और इसमें USB कनेक्शन का उपयोग होने के समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। इस अद्यतन से स्थिति बार में पाठ और आइकन के प्रदर्शन को भी अनुकूलित किया जाता है। इसके अतिरिक्त, इस रिलीज़ से सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता है। अद्यतन करने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति बार">
<feature>जानकारी की पहचान करना आसान बनाने के लिए पाठ का आकार बढ़ाया जाता है और आइकन को बोल्ड किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>आपके डिवाइस को अधिक स्थिर रूप से चलाने के लिए सिस्टम की स्थिरता में सुधार करता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>अब आप होम स्क्रीन के आइकन छिपा सकते हैं। इसे आज़माने के लिए यहाँ जाएँ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा और गोपनीयता > डिवाइस और डेटा सुरक्षा > ऐप्स को होम स्क्रीन से छिपाएँ।
USB कनेक्शन का उपयोग होने के समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक है। जब आप फ़ोटो ट्रांसफ़र करें या फ़ाइलें ट्रांसफ़र करें / Android Auto चुनते हैं, तो सत्यापन या सुरक्षा संकेत दिखता है जिससे सुरक्षित डेटा ट्रांसफ़र सुनिश्चित होता है।
सिस्टम सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा के अद्यतन के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, zahvaljujući ovom ažuriranju moguće je sakriti ikone s početnog zaslona, a potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom povezivanja putem USB-a. Ovim se ažuriranjem također optimizira prikaz teksta i ikona na statusnoj traci. Osim toga, ovim se izdanjem poboljšava stabilnost sustava, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusna traka">
<feature>Povećava se veličina teksta i podebljavaju se ikone radi lakšeg prepoznavanja informacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Poboljšava se stabilnost sustava pa uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Sada možete sakriti ikone s početnog zaslona. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija s Početnog zaslona.
Prilikom povezivanja putem USB-a potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Kada odaberete Prenesi fotografije ili Prenesi datoteke / Android Auto, pojavljuje se upit za provjeru ili sigurnost, čime se osigurava sigurniji prijenos podataka.
Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (listopad 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ettől a frissítéstől kezdve elrejtheti a kívánt ikonokat a főképernyőn, és felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges az USB-kapcsolat használatához. A frissítés ezenfelül optimalizálja a szövegek és az ikonok megjelenítését az állapotsávban. Emellett ez a verzió a rendszer stabilitását is javítja, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Állapotsáv">
<feature>Növeli a szöveg méretét és félkövérrel jeleníti meg az ikonokat, hogy az információk átláthatóbbak legyenek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Javítottuk a rendszer stabilitását, így a készülék zökkenőmentesebben működik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Mostantól elrejtheti a főképernyő ikonjait. Próbálja ki az alábbi útvonalon: Beállítások > Biztonság és adatvédelem > Készülék és adatvédelem > Alkalmazások elrejtése a főképernyőről.
Az USB-kapcsolat használatához felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ha a Fotók átvitele vagy a Fájlok átvitele/Android Auto opciót választja, megjelenik egy hitelesítési vagy biztonsági üzenet, amelynek célja, hogy az adatátvitel garantáltan biztonságos legyen.
A rendszerbiztonság érdekében a frissítés tartalmazza az Android biztonsági frissítését (2024. október) is. A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, dalam pembaruan ini, ikon layar beranda dapat disembunyikan, dan autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat menggunakan koneksi USB. Pembaruan ini juga mengoptimalkan tampilan teks dan ikon di bilah status. Selain itu, rilis ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bilah status">
<feature>Menambah ukuran teks, dan menebalkan ikon agar informasi lebih mudah dimengerti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem sehingga perangkat Anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Anda kini dapat menyembunyikan ikon layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat menggunakan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, sehingga memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.
Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, dalam pembaruan ini, ikon layar beranda dapat disembunyikan, dan autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat menggunakan koneksi USB. Pembaruan ini juga mengoptimalkan tampilan teks dan ikon di bilah status. Selain itu, rilis ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bilah status">
<feature>Menambah ukuran teks, dan menebalkan ikon agar informasi lebih mudah dimengerti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem sehingga perangkat Anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Anda kini dapat menyembunyikan ikon layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat menggunakan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, sehingga memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.
Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home e introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si utilizza la connessione USB. Inoltre ottimizza la visualizzazione del testo e delle icone nella barra di stato. Questa versione migliora anche la stabilità del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra di stato">
<feature>È stata aumentata la dimensione del testo e formattato in grassetto il testo delle icone per facilitare la lettura delle informazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home.
Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si utilizza la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home e introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si utilizza la connessione USB. Inoltre ottimizza la visualizzazione del testo e delle icone nella barra di stato. Questa versione migliora anche la stabilità del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra di stato">
<feature>È stata aumentata la dimensione del testo e formattato in grassetto il testo delle icone per facilitare la lettura delle informazioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home.
Viene introdotto l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si utilizza la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.
È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, בעדכון זה, ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית, ואימות משתמש נדרש בעת שימוש בחיבור USB. כמו כן, עדכון זה גם ממטב את התצוגה של טקסט וסמלים בשורת מצב. בנוסף, שחרור זה משפר את יציבות המערכת ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="שורת מצב">
<feature>מגדיל את גודל הטקסט ומבליט את הסמלים כדי להקל על זיהוי המידע.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על ההתקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
אימות משתמש נדרש בעת שימוש בחיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.
תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, בעדכון זה, ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית, ואימות משתמש נדרש בעת שימוש בחיבור USB. כמו כן, עדכון זה גם ממטב את התצוגה של טקסט וסמלים בשורת מצב. בנוסף, שחרור זה משפר את יציבות המערכת ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="שורת מצב">
<feature>מגדיל את גודל הטקסט ומבליט את הסמלים כדי להקל על זיהוי המידע.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על ההתקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
אימות משתמש נדרש בעת שימוש בחיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.
תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の更新では、ホーム画面のアイコンを非表示にできるようになり、USB接続の使用時にユーザー認証が必要になります。また、今回の更新では、ステータスバーでのテキストとアイコンの表示が最適化されます。さらに、今回のリリースでは、システムの安定性が改善され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。更新することをおすすめします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ステータスバー">
<feature>文字サイズを大きくして、アイコンを太字化することで、情報を認識しやすくなります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>システムの安定性が改善され、デバイスがより安定して動作するようになります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>ホーム画面のアイコンを非表示にできるようになりました。[設定] > [セキュリティとプライバシー] > [デバイスとデータ保護] > [ホーム画面でアプリを非表示]に移動して、試してみてください。
USB接続の使用時にユーザー認証が必要になります。[写真を転送]または[ファイルを転送/Android Auto]を選択すると、認証プロンプトまたはセキュリティプロンプトが表示されます。
システムセキュリティのために、Androidセキュリティパッチ（2024年10月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ამ განახლებით შესაძლებელი ხდება საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების დამალვა, ხოლო USB კავშირის გამოყენებისას მოითხოვება მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. ამავე განახლებაში ოპტიმიზებულია სტატუსის ზოლში ტექსტისა და პიქტოგრამების ჩვენება. ამასთან, ამ გამოშვებაში გაუმჯობესებულია სისტემის სტაბილურობა და შესულია უსაფრთხოების შესწორება. გირჩევთ, განაახლოთ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სტატუსის ზოლი">
<feature>ზრდის ტექსტის ზომას და ამუქებს პიქტოგრამებს, რომ ინფორმაცია მარტივად ამოსაცნობი იყოს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას, რის შედეგადაც მოწყობილობა უფრო სტაბილურად მუშაობს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>ახლა შეგიძლიათ დამალოთ საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამები. ეს შეგიძლიათ სცადოთ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > უსაფრთხოება და კონფიდენციალურობა > მოწყობილობისა და მონაცემთა დაცვა > აპების დამალვა საწყისი ეკრანიდან.
USB კავშირის გამოყენებისას მოითხოვება მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. გადამოწმების ან უსაფრთხოების მოთხოვნა გამოჩნდება, როცა აირჩევთ ფოტოების გადაცემას ან ფაილების გადაცემას / Android Auto-ს, რაც უზრუნველყოფს მონაცემების უსაფრთხო გადაცემას.
სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩართულია Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ოქტომბერი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңартуда негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыруға болады және USB байланысын пайдаланған кезде пайдаланушы аутентификациясы қажет. Сондай-ақ бұл жаңарту күй жолағындағы мәтін мен белгішелердің көрсетілуін оңтайландырады. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым жүйе тұрақтылығын жақсартады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жаңарту ұсынылады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Күй жолағы">
<feature>Ақпаратты тануды жеңілдету үшін мәтін өлшемін үлкейтеді және белгішелерді қалыңдатады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>Құрылғының тұрақты жұмыс істеуі үшін жүйенің тұрақтылығын жақсартады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Енді негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыра аласыз. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Қауіпсіздік және құпиялық» > «Құрылғыны және деректерді қорғау» > «Негізгі экрандағы қолданбаларды жасыру».
USB байланысын пайдаланған кезде пайдаланушы аутентификациясы қажет. Деректерді қауіпсіз тасымалдауды қамтамасыз ететін «Фотосуреттерді тасымалдау» немесе «Файлдарды тасымалдау/Android Auto» параметрін таңдаған кезде растау немесе қауіпсіздік сұрауы пайда болады.
Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қазан, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន នៅក្នុងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះ រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមអាចលាក់បាន ហើយតម្រូវឱ្យធ្វើការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើ នៅពេលប្រើការតភ្ជាប់តាម USB។ បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះក៏ធ្វើឱ្យការបង្ហាញអត្ថបទ និងរូបតំណាងក្នុងរបារ​ស្ថានភាពប្រសើរឡើងផងដែរ។ លើសពីនេះ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះកែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខផងដែរ។ សូមណែនាំឱ្យធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="របារ​ស្ថានភាព">
<feature>បង្កើនទំហំអត្ថបទ និងធ្វើឱ្យរូបតំណាងដិត ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យព័ត៌មានកាន់តែងាយស្រួលចំណាំ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>កែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យឧបករណ៍របស់អ្នកដំណើរការបានកាន់តែមានស្ថិរភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>ឥឡូវនេះ អ្នកអាចលាក់រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមបានហើយ។ សាកល្បងវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > សន្តិសុខ និងឯកជនភាព > ការការពារឧបករណ៍ និងទិន្នន័យ > លាក់កម្មវិធីពីអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។
តម្រូវឱ្យមានការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើ នៅពេលប្រើការតភ្ជាប់តាម USB។ សារតម្រុយផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់ ឬសារតម្រុយសន្តិសុខមួយបង្ហាញ នៅពេលអ្នកជ្រើសរើស "ផ្ទេររូបថត" ឬ "ផ្ទេរ​ឯកសារ / Android Auto" ដែលធានាបាននូវការផ្ទេរទិន្នន័យដែលកាន់តែមានសុវត្ថិភាព។
បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (តុលា 2024) ត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូលសម្រាប់សន្តិសុខប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់ព័ត៌មានបន្ថែមអំពីបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពសន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅកាន់គេហទំព័ររបស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣದಲ್ಲಿ, ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬಳಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿಯಲ್ಲಿ ಪಠ್ಯ ಮತ್ತು ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳ ಪ್ರದರ್ಶನವನ್ನು ಸಹ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ನವೀಕರಿಸಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ">
<feature>ಪಠ್ಯದ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿ ಗುರುತಿಸಲು ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಬೋಲ್ಡ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಾಧನವು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಸ್ಥಿರವಾಗಿ ಕಾರ್ಯನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಲು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ನೀವು ಈಗ ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್ಗಳು > ಭದ್ರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಗೌಪ್ಯತೆ > ಸಾಧನ ಮತ್ತು ಡೇಟಾ ರಕ್ಷಣೆ > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ನಿಂದ ಆ್ಯಪ್ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಿ.
USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್ ಬಳಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿದೆ. ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಡೇಟಾ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಲು ಫೋಟೋಗಳ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆ ಅಥವಾ ಫೈಲ್ಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ / Android Auto ಎಂಬುದನ್ನು ನೀವು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಿದಾಗ ಪರಿಶೀಲನೆ ಅಥವಾ ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ರಾಂಪ್ಟ್ ಕಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ.
Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಅಕ್ಟೋಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್ಸೈಟ್ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트에서는 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨길 수 있으며, USB 연결 시 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 이번 업데이트에서는 상태 표시줄의 텍스트와 아이콘 표시도 최적화됩니다. 또한 이번 릴리스에는 시스템 안정성이 개선되었으며 보안 패치도 포함되어 있습니다. 업데이트하는 것이 좋습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="상태 표시줄">
<feature>텍스트 크기를 늘리고 아이콘을 굵게 표시하여 정보를 더 쉽게 알아볼 수 있도록 합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>시스템 안정성을 개선하여 장치를 더욱 안정적으로 실행할 수 있도록 합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>이제 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨길 수 있습니다. 설정 > 보안 및 개인 정보 보호 > 장치 및 데이터 보호 > 홈 화면에서 앱 숨기기로 이동하여 사용해 보십시오.
USB 연결 사용 시에는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 사진 전송 또는 파일 전송/Android Auto를 선택하면 인증 또는 보안 메시지가 표시되어 더욱 안전하게 데이터를 전송할 수 있습니다.
시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 10월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ໃນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້, ສາ​ມາດ​ເຊື່ອງໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກໄດ້ ແລະ ​ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້ ເມື່ອ​ໃຊ້​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ນອກນັ້ນ ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຍັງ​ປັບ​ການ​ສະ​ແດງ​ຜົນ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ ແລະ ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໃນ​ແຖບ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ. ນອກຈາກ​ນີ້, ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວ​ນີ້​ຍັງ​ປັບປຸງຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ​​ຂອງລະ​ບົບ ແລະ ລວມ​ເອົາ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ. ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ອັບ​ເດດ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແຖບສະຖານະ">
<feature>ເພີ່ມ​ຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ ແລະ ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ເປັນ​ຕົວ​ໜາ ເພື່ອ​ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ຮັບ​ຮູ້​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ໄດ້​ງ່າຍ​ຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ ເພື່ອເຮັດໃຫ້ອຸປະກອນຂອງທ່ານເຮັດວຽກໄດ້ສະຖຽນຍິ່ງຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ເຊື່ອງ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ແລະ ຄວາມ​ເປັນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ > ການ​ປົກ​ປ້ອງ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ ແລະ ຂໍ້​ມູນ > ເຊື່ອງ​ແອັບຈາກໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​.
ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ໃຊ້ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ການກວດ​ສອບ ຫຼື ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ປະ​ກົດຂຶ້ນ​ເມື່ອ​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ ໂອນ​ຍ້າຍ​ຮູບ ຫຼື ໂອນຍ້າຍໄຟລ໌ / Android Auto, ເຊິ່ງ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ການ​ໂອນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ທີ່​ປອດ​ໄພ​ກວ່າ.
ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ຕຸ​ລາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo naujiniu leidžiama paslėpti piktogramas pradžios ekrane, o naudojant USB jungtį reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Šiuo naujiniu taip pat optimizuojamas teksto ir piktogramų rodymas būsenos juostoje. Be to, šioje laidoje pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas ir įtraukiama saugumo pataisa. Rekomenduojama atnaujinti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Būsenos juosta">
<feature>Padidinamas tekstas ir paryškinamos piktogramos, kad būtų lengviau atpažinti informaciją.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas, todėl įrenginys veikia stabiliau.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Dabar galite paslėpti pradžios ekrano piktogramas. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos > Saugumas ir privatumas > Įrenginys ir duomenų apsauga > Slėpti programėles iš pradžios ekrano“.
Naudojant USB jungtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Pasirinkus „Persiųsti nuotraukas“ arba „Persiųsti failus („Android Auto“)“, pateikiamas patvirtinimo arba saugumo raginimas. Taip užtikrinamas saugesnis duomenų persiuntimas.
Sistemos saugumui užtikrinti įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. spalio mėn.). Daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius rasite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu sākuma ekrāna ikonas var paslēpt, un, izmantojot USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Šis atjauninājums arī optimizē teksta un ikonu rādīšanu statusa joslā. Turklāt ar šo laidienu tiek arī uzlabota sistēmas stabilitāte, kā arī ir iekļauts drošības ielāps. Ieteicams atjaunināt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusa josla">
<feature>Palielina teksta izmēru un izveido ikonas treknrakstā, lai informācija būtu vieglāk atpazīstama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti, padarot jūsu ierīci stabilāku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Tagad varat paslēpt sākuma ekrāna ikonas. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Drošība un konfidencialitāte > Ierīces un datu aizsardzība > Slēpt lietotnes sākuma ekrānā.
USB savienojumam ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Izvēloties Pārsūtīt fotoattēlus vai Pārsūtīt failus/Android Auto, tiek parādīta verifikācijas vai drošības uzvedne, garantējot drošāku datu pārsūtīšanu.
Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada oktobris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, एहि अपडेट मे होम स्क्रीन आइकन केँ नुकाओल जा सकैत अछि आओर USB कनेक्शन उपयोग करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। ई अपडेट स्थिति बार मे टेक्स्ट आ आइकन सभक डिस्प्ले केँ सेहो अनुकूलित करैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, ई रिलीज सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि। अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति बार">
<feature>जानकारी केँ आसानी सँ पहिचान करबाक लेल टेक्स्टक आकार बढ़बैत अछि आओर आइकन सभ केँ बोल्ड करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि, जाहि सँ अहाँक डिवाइस बेसी स्थिर रूप सँ चलि सकए।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>आब अहाँ होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ नुका सकैत छी। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा आ गोपनीयता > डिवाइस आ डेटा सुरक्षा > होम स्क्रीन सँ एप सभ नुकाउ।
USB कनेक्शन उपयोग करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। बेहतर डेटा ट्रांसफर सुनिश्चित करबाक लेल, जखन अहाँ फोटो सभ ट्रांसफर करू वा फाइल सभ / Android ऑटो ट्रांसफर करू केर चयन करैत छी, तखन एकटा सत्यापन वा सुरक्षा प्रॉम्प्ट देखायत।
सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टू 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, i tēnei whakahōu, ka taea te huna i ngā ata mata kāinga, ā, e hiahiatia ana he motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakamahi i te tūhononga USB. Ka arotautia hoki e tēnei whakahōu te whakaaturanga o kuputuhi me ngā ata i te pae tūnga. Tērā anō, ka whakapai ake tēnei putanga i te taimautanga pūnaha, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. E tūtohutia ana kia whakahōu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pae tūnga">
<feature>Ka whakanui ake i te rahi kuputuhi, ā, ka taekaha hoki i ngā ata kia māmā ake ai te mōhio ki ngā mōhiohio.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>Ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga pūnaha kia ētahi anō ai te whakahaere o tō pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Ka taea e koe te huna i ngā tohu o te mata kāinga. Whakamātauria mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga > Haumarutanga me te tūmataitinga > Te pūrere me te parenga raraunga > Huna ngā taupānga mai i te mata Kāinga.
E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakamahi i te tūhononga USB. Ka puta mai tētahi manatokonga, tohuāki haumarutanga rānei ina tīpako koe i Whakawhiti whakaahua, i rānei Whakawhitia ngā kōnae / Android Auto, me te whakarite i te whakawhiti raraunga haumaru ake.
Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Oketopa 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, во ова ажурирање може да се кријат иконите на почетниот екран и потребна е автентикација од корисникот кога се користи поврзување преку USB. Ова ажурирање исто така го оптимизира приказот на текстот и иконите во статусната лента. Дополнително, ова издание ја подобрува стабилноста на системот и вградува безбедносна крпеница. Се препорачува да ажурирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Статусна лента">
<feature>Големината на текстот се зголемува и иконите за задебелуваат за да биде полесно препознавањето на информациите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Ја подобрува стабилноста на системот за уредот да работи постабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Сега може да ги криете иконите на почетниот екран. Пробајте преку одење во: Нагодување > Безбедност и приватност > Заштита на уредот и податоците > Скриј апликации од почетниот екран.
Потребна е автентикација од корисникот кога се користи поврзување преку USB. Се појавува укажување за потврдување или безбедносно укажување кога ќе изберете Пренос на фотографии или Пренос на датотеки / Android Auto со што се осигурува побезбеден пренос на податоците.
Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (октомври 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за Ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја наша веб-локација: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или одете во сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിൽ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാൻ കഴിയുമെന്ന് മാത്രമല്ല, USB കണക്ഷൻ ഉപയോഗിക്കുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടതും ആവശ്യമാണ്. കൂടാതെ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാറിലെ ടെക്‌സ്റ്റിന്റെയും ഐക്കണുകളുടെയും ഡിസ്‌പ്ലേ ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, ഈ റിലീസ് സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ">
<feature>വിവരങ്ങൾ എളുപ്പത്തിൽ തിരിച്ചറിയുന്നതിനായി ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് വലുപ്പം വർദ്ധിപ്പിക്കുകയും ഐക്കണുകൾ ബോൾഡാക്കുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>നിങ്ങളുടെ ഉപകരണം കൂടുതൽ സ്ഥിരതയോടെ പ്രവർത്തിക്കാൻ സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാവുന്നതാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > സുരക്ഷയും സ്വകാര്യതയും > ഉപകരണ, ഡാറ്റാ പരിരക്ഷ > ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ നിന്ന് ആപ്പുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കുക.
USB കണക്ഷൻ ഉപയോഗിക്കുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടത് ആവശ്യമാണ്. നിങ്ങൾ 'ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈമാറുക' അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 'ഫയലുകൾ കൈമാറുക / Android Auto' എന്നത് തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുമ്പോൾ ഒരു പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സുരക്ഷാ നിർദ്ദേശം ദൃശ്യമാകുന്നു, ഇത് സുരക്ഷിതമായ ഡാറ്റാ കൈമാറ്റം ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നു.
സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഒക്‌ടോബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой болж, USB холболтод хэрэглэгчийн зөвшөөрлийг шаарддаг боллоо. Энэ шинэчлэлтээр мөн төлөвийн мөр дэх бичвэр, шигтгээ зургийн харагдах байдлыг оновчлов. Мөн энэ шинэчлэлтээр системийн тогтвортой байдлыг сайжруулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаалаа. Шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Төлөвийн мөр">
<feature>Бичвэрийн хэмжээг томруулж, шигтгээ зургийг тодруулсан тул мэдээллийг илүү хялбар таних боломжтой боллоо.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Таны төхөөрөмжийг илүү тогтвортой ажиллуулахын тулд системийн тогтвортой байдлыг нэмэгдүүлсэн.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Одоо та үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой боллоо. Тохиргоо > Хамгаалалт ба нууцлал > Төхөөрөмж ба өгөгдөл хамгаалалт > Үндсэн дэлгэцээс апликэйшн нуух руу очиж үүнийг туршиж үзнэ үү.
USB холболтод хэрэглэгчийн зөвшөөрлийг шаарддаг боллоо. Өгөгдлийг аюулгүй дамжуулах үүднээс Зураг дамжуулах, эсвэл Файл шилжүүлэх / Андройд автомат сонголтыг сонгосон үед хамгаалалтыг баталгаажуулах заавар дэлгэцэд харагдана.
Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны 10-р сар) системийн аюулгүй байдалд зориулж нэгтгэсэн. HONOR хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаарх дэлгэрэнгүй мэдээллийг авах бол манай https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 вэбсайтад зочилно уу</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, या अद्यतनामध्ये, मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे लपवली जाऊ शकतात आणि USB कनेक्शन वापरताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. हे अद्यतन स्टेटस बारमधील मजकूर आणि चिन्हांचे प्रदर्शन देखील ऑप्टिमाइझ करते. याव्यतिरिक्त, हे रिलीझ सिस्टम स्थिरता सुधारते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते. अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्टेटस बार">
<feature>माहिती ओळखणे सोपे करण्यासाठी मजकूराचा आकार वाढवते आणि चिन्हे ठळक करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>आपले उपकरण अधिक स्थिरपणे चालण्‍यासाठी सिस्‍टम स्‍थिरता सुधारते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>आपण आता मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे लपवू शकता. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुरक्षितता आणि गोपनीयता > उपकरण आणि डेटा संरक्षण > मुख्य स्क्रीनवरून ॲप्स लपवा.
USB कनेक्शन वापरताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. आपण फोटोज स्‍थानांतरित करा किंवा फाइल्स/Android स्वयं स्‍थानांतरित करा निवडता तेव्हा पडताळणी किंवा सुरक्षितता सूचना दिसून येते, सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करते.
सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षिता पॅच (ऑक्टो 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, dalam kemas kini ini, ikon skrin utama boleh disembunyikan dan pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menggunakan sambungan USB. Kemas kini ini juga mengoptimumkan paparan teks dan ikon dalam bar status. Selain itu, keluaran ini juga meningkatkan kestabilan sistem dan memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Anda disyorkan agar mengemas kini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bar status">
<feature>Besarkan saiz teks dan tebalkan ikon untuk menjadikan maklumat lebih mudah dikenal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Tingkatkan kestabilan sistem untuk membolehkan peranti anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Anda kini boleh menyembunyikan ikon skrin utama. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Keselamatan dan privasi > Perlindungan peranti dan data > Sembunyikan aplikasi daripada Skrin utama.
Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menggunakan sambungan USB. Pengesahan atau gesaan keselamatan muncul apabila anda memilih Pindahkan foto atau Pindahkan fail / Auto Android, demi memastikan pemindahan data yang lebih selamat.
Tampalan keselamatan Android (Okt 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်သည်၊ USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှုကို အသုံးပြုသည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အခြေအနေပြဘားတွင် စာသားနှင့် အိုင်ကွန်များ၏ ပြသမှုကိုလည်း အကောင်းဆုံးဖြစ်စေရန် ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။ ထို့အပြင် ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အခြေအနေပြဘား">
<feature>စာလုံး အရွယ်အစားကို ကြီးမားအောင်လုပ်ပေးထားပြီး အိုင်ကွန်များကို စာလုံးမည်းပေးထားသဖြင့် အချက်အလက်များကို ပိုမိုလွယ်ကူစွာ သိရှိနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>သင့်စက်ကို ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စွာ လုပ်ဆောင်နိုင်စေရန် စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို တိုးမြှင့်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်ပါပြီ။ ဖော်ပြပါသို့သွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > လုံခြုံရေးနှင့် ကိုယ်ပိုင် အချက်အလက် > စက်နှင့် ဒေတာ ကာကွယ်ရေး > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်မှ အက်ပ်များကို ဝှက်ရန်။
USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှုကို အသုံးပြုသည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဓာတ်ပုံများ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် သို့မဟုတ် ဖိုင်များ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် / Android Auto ကို ရွေးချယ်ပါက အတည်ပြုမှု သို့မဟုတ် လုံခြုံရေး ညွှန်ကြားချက် ပေါ်လာပြီး ဒေတာ လွှဲပြောင်းမှုကို ပို၍လုံခြုံစေသည်။
စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (အောက်တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း အချက်အလက်များ ပိုမိုသိရှိလိုပါက ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ် https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္သည္၊ USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈကို အသုံးျပဳသည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အေျခအေနျပဘားတြင္ စာသားႏွင့္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား၏ ျပသမႈကိုလည္း အေကာင္းဆုံးျဖစ္ေစရန္ ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အေျခအေနျပဘား">
<feature>စာလုံး အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ႀကီးမားေအာင္လုပ္ေပးထားၿပီး အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို စာလုံးမည္းေပးထားသျဖင့္ အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ပိုမိုလြယ္ကူစြာ သိရွိႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>သင့္စက္ကို ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္စြာ လုပ္ေဆာင္ႏိုင္ေစရန္ စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို တိုးျမႇင့္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔သြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > လုံျခံဳေရးႏွင့္ ကိုယ္ပိုင္ အခ်က္အလက္ > စက္ႏွင့္ ေဒတာ ကာကြယ္ေရး > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္မွ အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ရန္။
USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈကို အသုံးျပဳသည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ဓာတ္ပုံမ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ဖိုင္မ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ / Android Auto ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္ပါက အတည္ျပဳမႈ သို႔မဟုတ္ လုံၿခဳံေရး ၫႊန္ၾကားခ်က္ ေပၚလာၿပီး ေဒတာ လႊဲေျပာင္းမႈကို ပို၍လုံၿခဳံေစသည္။
စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ေအာက္တိုဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း အခ်က္အလက္မ်ား ပိုမိုသိရွိလိုပါက ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, i denne oppdateringen kan du skjule ikoner på startskjermen, og brukerautentisering kreves ved bruk av USB-tilkobling. Denne oppdateringen optimerer også visningen av tekst og ikoner i statuslinjen. I tillegg vil denne utgivelsen forbedre systemstabiliteten og innlemme en sikkerhetsoppdatering. Oppdateringen anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statuslinje">
<feature>Øker tekststørrelsen og fremhever ikonene for å gjøre informasjonen lettere å gjenkjenne.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Forbedrer systemstabiliteten, slik at enheten kjører mer stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Du kan nå skjule ikoner på startskjermen. Prøv det ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Sikkerhet og personvern > Enhets- og databeskyttelse > Skjul apper på startskjermen.
Brukerautentisering kreves ved bruk av USB-tilkobling. En bekreftelses- eller sikkerhetsforespørsel vises når du velger Overfør bilder eller Overfør filer / Android Auto, noe som sikrer tryggere dataoverføring.
Android sikkerhetsoppdatering (oktober 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om HONOR-sikkerhetsoppdateringer, vennligst besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटमा गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन मिल्छ र USB जडान प्रयोग गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । यो अपडेटले स्थिति पट्टीमा पाठ र आइकनहरूको डिस्प्ले पनि अप्टिमाइज गर्छ । साथै, यो रिलिजले प्रणालीको स्थिरता सुधार गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ । अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="स्थिति पट्टी">
<feature>यसले पाठको आकार बढाउँछ र जानकारी सजिलै पहिचान गर्न सकियोस् भन्नाका लागि आइकनहरू बोल्ड बनाउँछ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>तपाईंको यन्त्रलाई थप स्थिर रूपमा चल्ने बनाउन प्रणालीको स्थिरतामा सुधार ल्याउँछ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>तपाईं अब गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सुरक्षा तथा गोपनीयता > यन्त्र तथा डाटाको सुरक्षा > गृह स्क्रिनबाट एपहरू लुकाउनुहोस् ।
USB जडान प्रयोग गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । तपाईंले फोटोहरू स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् वा फाइलहरू स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् / एन्ड्रोइड अटो चयन गर्नुभयो भने प्रमाणीकरण वा सुरक्षा प्रम्प्ट देखिने छ ।
एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अक्टोबर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, in deze update kunnen pictogrammen op het startscherm worden verborgen en is gebruikersverificatie vereist bij gebruik van een USB-verbinding. Deze update optimaliseert ook de weergave van tekst en pictogrammen in de statusbalk. Bovendien verbetert deze release de stabiliteit van het systeem en bevat deze een beveiligingspatch. Het wordt aanbevolen om bij te werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusbalk">
<feature>Vergroot de tekstgrootte en maakt de pictogrammen vet om de informatie gemakkelijker herkenbaar te maken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Verbetert de systeemstabiliteit om uw apparaat stabieler te laten werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>U kunt nu pictogrammen op het startscherm verbergen. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Beveiliging en privacy > Apparaat- en gegevensbescherming > Apps verbergen van Startscherm.
Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist bij gebruik van een USB-verbinding. Er verschijnt een verificatie- of beveiligingsprompt wanneer u Foto's overdragen of Bestanden overdragen / Android Auto selecteert, wat zorgt voor een veiligere gegevensoverdracht.
Android-beveiligingspatch (oktober 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ, ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଲୁଚାଯାଇ ପାରିବ, ଏବଂ USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ବ୍ୟବହାର କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌ରେ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍‌ ଏବଂ ଆଇକନ୍‌ର ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶନ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍‌ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବଢାଏ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌">
<feature>ସୂଚନାକୁ ସହଜରେ ଚିହ୍ନଟ କରାଇବାକୁ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍‌ ଆକାରକୁ ବଢାଏ ଏବଂ ଆଇକନ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ବୋଲ୍ଡ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ ଅଧିକ ସ୍ଥିର ଭାବେ ଚଲାଇବାକୁ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବଢ଼ାଇଥାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>ର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ଆପଣ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଆଇକନ୍ ଲୁଚାଇ ପାରିବେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଓ ଗୋପନୀୟତା > ଡିଭାଇସ୍ ଓ ଡାଟା ସୁରକ୍ଷା > ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ରୁ ଆପସ୍ ଲୁଚାନ୍ତୁ।
USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ବ୍ୟବହାର କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଆପଣ ଫଟୋଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରନ୍ସଫର୍ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ଫାଇଲ୍ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍ କରନ୍ତୁ / Android Auto ଚୟନ କରିବା ବେଳେ, ନିରାପଦ ଡାଟା ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍ ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି ଏକ ଯାଞ୍ଚ କିମ୍ବା ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ରମ୍ପଟ୍ ଦେଖାଯଏ।
ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ (ଅକ୍ଟୋବର 2024) ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି।HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ, ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾਏ ਜਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ, ਅਤੇ USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਦੇ ਸਮੇਂ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣਿਕਤਾ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ ਵਿੱਚ ਟੈਕਸਟ ਅਤੇ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਦੇ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ">
<feature>ਟੈਕਸਟ ਆਕਾਰ ਨੂੰ ਵਧਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਪਛਾਣਨਾ ਆਸਾਨ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਗੂੜ੍ਹਾ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਹੋਰ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਨਾਲ ਕੰਮ ਕਰੇਗਾ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਹੁਣ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅਤੇ ਪਰਦੇਦਾਰੀ > ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਅਤੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਤੋਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਲੁਕਾਓ।
USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਦੇ ਸਮੇਂ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣਿਕਤਾ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ / Android Auto ਦੀ ਚੋਣ ਕਰਦੇ ਹੋ, ਤਾਂ ਇੱਕ ਪੁਸ਼ਟੀਕਰਨ ਜਾਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪ੍ਰੌਂਪਟ ਦਿਖਾਈ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਡੇਟਾ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ।
ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਕਤੂਬਰ 2024) ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਵਾਸਤੇ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja wprowadza możliwość ukrywania ikon ekranu głównego, a do korzystania z połączenia USB jest wymagane uwierzytelnianie użytkownika. Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje również wyświetlanie tekstu i ikon na pasku stanu. Ponadto ta wersja poprawia stabilność systemu i zawiera poprawkę zabezpieczeń. Zaleca się zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pasek stanu">
<feature>Zwiększono rozmiar tekstu i pogrubiono ikony, aby poprawić czytelność informacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Poprawiono stabilność systemu, dzięki czemu urządzenie działa bardziej niezawodnie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Można już ukrywać ikony ekranu głównego. Aby wypróbować tę funkcję, wybierz Ustawienia > Bezpieczeństwo i prywatność > Ochrona danych i urządzenia > Ukryj aplikacje na Ekranie głównym.
Do korzystania z połączenia USB jest potrzebne uwierzytelnienie użytkownika. Po wybraniu opcji Przenosić zdjęcia lub Przenosić pliki / Android Auto pojawia się monit dotyczący weryfikacji lub zabezpieczeń w celu zapewnienia bezpieczniejszego transferu danych.
Poprawka zabezpieczeń systemu Android (październik 2024) została dodana w celu zapewnienia bezpieczeństwa systemu. Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń HONOR można uzyskać na stronie internetowej https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, nesta atualização, os ícones da tela inicial podem ser ocultados e a autenticação de usuário é necessária ao usar a conexão USB. Esta atualização também otimiza a exibição de texto e ícones na barra de status. Além disso, esta versão melhora a estabilidade do sistema e incorpora um patch de segurança. É recomendado atualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de status">
<feature>Aumenta o tamanho do texto e coloca os ícones em negrito para facilitar o reconhecimento das informações.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Melhora a estabilidade do sistema para que seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Agora você pode ocultar ícones da tela inicial. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Segurança e privacidade > Proteção de dispositivos e dados > Ocultar aplicativos da Tela inicial.
A autenticação de usuário é necessária ao usar a conexão USB. Um aviso de verificação ou de segurança aparece quando você seleciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir arquivos/Android Auto, garantindo uma transferência de segurança mais segura.
O patch de segurança do Android (Outubro de 2024) foi incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, nesta atualização, os ícones do ecrã inicial podem ser ocultados e a autenticação do utilizador é necessária quando se utiliza uma ligação USB. Esta atualização também otimiza a apresentação de texto e ícones na barra de estado. Além disso, esta versão melhora a estabilidade do sistema e incorpora uma correção de segurança. A atualização é recomendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Barra de estado">
<feature>Aumenta o tamanho do texto e realça os ícones para tornar a informação mais fácil de reconhecer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Melhora a estabilidade do sistema para que o seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Pode agora ocultar os ícones do ecrã inicial. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Segurança e privacidade > Dispositivo e proteção de dados > Ocultar aplicações ao Ecrã inicial.
A autenticação do utilizador é necessária quando se utiliza a ligação USB. Aparece uma mensagem de verificação ou segurança quando seleciona Transferir fotografias ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.
Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (outubro de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de Segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, în această actualizare, pictogramele de pe ecranul de pornire pot fi ascunse și este necesară autentificarea utilizatorului la utilizarea conexiunii USB. De asemenea, această actualizare optimizează afișarea textelor și pictogramelor în bara de stare. În plus, această versiune îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului și include un patch de securitate. Se recomandă actualizarea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bară de stare">
<feature>Mărește dimensiunea textului și accentuează pictogramele pentru a face informațiile mai ușor de recunoscut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului pentru ca dispozitivul să funcționeze mai stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Acum puteți ascunde pictogramele ecranului de pornire. Încercați de la: Setări > Siguranță și confidențialitate > Protecția dispozitivului și a datelor > Ascundere aplicații din Ecranul de pornire.
Autentificarea utilizatorului este obligatorie la utilizarea conexiunii USB. Atunci când selectați Transfer de fotografii sau Transferare fișiere / Android Auto va fi afișat un prompt de verificare sau de securitate, pentru a asigura transferul mai sigur al datelor.
Patchul de securitate pentru Android (oct 2024) a fost inclus pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы добавить возможность скрытия значков на рабочем столе, добавить аутентификацию пользователя при использовании USB-подключения, оптимизировать отображение значков в строке состояния, улучшить производительность и стабильность системы, а также внедрить исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Строка состояния">
<feature>Увеличен размер текста и добавлено выделение значков жирным шрифтом для более удобного распознавания.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Повышена стабильность системы и, соответственно, работа вашего устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>Теперь вы можете скрыть значки на рабочем экране. Для этого перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Безопасность и конфиденциальность > Защита устройства и данных > Скрыть значки приложений на рабочем экране».
При использовании USB-подключения требуется аутентификация пользователя. При выборе режима «Передача фото» или «Передача файлов/Android Auto» появляется запрос проверки или безопасности, что обеспечивает более безопасную передачу данных.
В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (октябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලකභවතුනි, මෙම යාවත්කාලයේ දී, මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවිය හැකිවනු ඇති අතර, USB සම්බන්ධතාවය භාවිත කරන විට පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. මෙම යාවත්කාලීනය තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩේ පෙළ සහ අයිකන සංදර්ශණය කිරීම ද ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි. අතිරේකව, මෙම නිකුතුව පද්ධති ස්ථායීතාවය වැඩි දියුණු කරන අතර ආරක්ෂක පිළියමක් ඇතුළත් කරයි. යාවත්කාල කරන්නට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ">
<feature>පාඨ විශාලත්වය ඉහළ නංවන අතර තොරතුරු හඳුනා ගැනීම වඩා පහසු කිරීමට අයිකන තද පැහැ කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>ඔබගේ උපාංගය වඩා ස්ථායීව ධාවනය කරවීමට පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාවය වැඩිදියුණු කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>ඔබට දැන් මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවිය හැකිවේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ආරක්ෂාව සහ රහස්‍යතාව > උපාංග සහ දත්ත ආරක්ෂාව > මුල් තිරයෙන් යෙදුම් සඟවන්න.
USB සම්බන්ධතාවය භාවිත කරන විට පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. ඔබ ඡායාරූප මාරු කරන්න හෝ ගොනු මාරු කරන්න / Android Auto තෝරාගත් විට, වඩා ආරක්ෂිත දත්ත මාරුව තහවුරු කරමින් සත්‍යාපන හෝ ආරක්ෂක ප්‍රේරණයක් දිස්වේ.
පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ඔක්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, v tejto aktualizácii možno skryť ikony na domovskej obrazovke a pri používaní pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Táto aktualizácia tiež optimalizuje zobrazenie textu a ikon v stavovom riadku. Toto vydanie navyše zlepšuje stabilitu systému a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizácia sa odporúča.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stavový riadok">
<feature>Zväčší veľkosť textu a zvýrazní ikony, aby sa informácie dali ľahšie rozpoznať.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Zlepšuje stabilitu systému, vďaka čomu zariadenie funguje stabilnejšie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Teraz môžete skryť ikony domovskej obrazovky. Vyskúšajte to v ponuke Nastavenia > Zabezpečenie a súkromie > Ochrana zariadenia a údajov > Skryť aplikácie na domovskej obrazovke.
Pri používaní pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Pri výbere možnosti Prenos fotografií alebo Prenos súborov/Android Auto sa zobrazí výzva na overenie alebo zabezpečenie, čím sa zaistí bezpečnejší prenos dát.
Obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu systému Android (okt. 2024) na zabezpečenie systému. Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev omogoča skrivanje ikon na začetnem zaslonu, za uporabo povezave USB pa je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. V tej posodobitvi je tudi optimiziran prikaz besedila ter ikon v vrstici stanja. Poleg tega je v tej izdaji izboljšana stabilnost sistema ter vključen varnostni popravek. Priporočamo posodobitev.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vrstica stanja">
<feature>Povečana je velikost besedila in ikone so poudarjene za enostavnejše branje podatkov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Izboljšana je stabilnost sistema za stabilnejše delovanje naprave.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Zdaj lahko skrijete ikone na začetnem zaslonu. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite v razdelku Nastavitve > Varnost in zasebnost > Zaščita naprave in podatkov > Skrij aplikacije na začetnem zaslonu.
Za uporabo povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ko izberete možnost Prenos fotografij ali Prenos datotek/Android Auto, se prikaže poziv za preverjanje ali varnostni poziv, s tem pa je zagotovljen varnejši prenos podatkov.
Varnostni popravek za Android (oktober 2024) je vključen za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, i den här uppdateringen kan ikoner på startsidan döljas, och användarautentisering krävs när du använder USB-anslutning. Genom uppdateringen optimeras också visningen av text och ikoner i statusfältet. Dessutom förbättras systemets prestanda och en säkerhetskorrigering implementeras. Du rekommenderas att uppdatera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Statusfält">
<feature>Ökar textstorleken och visar ikonerna i fetstil så att informationen lättare kan kännas igen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Förbättrar systemets stabilitet så att enheten körs stabilare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Du kan nu dölja ikoner på startsidan. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Säkerhet och sekretess > Enhets- och dataskydd > Dölj appar från startsidan.
Användarautentisering krävs när USB-anslutning används. En verifierings- eller säkerhetsuppmaning visas när du väljer Överföra foton eller Överföra filer/Android Auto, vilket ger en säkrare dataöverföring.
Android-säkerhetskorrigering (oktober 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, kwenye sasisho hili, aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo zinaweza kufichwa na uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitaji unapotumia muunganisho wa USB. Sasisho hili pia linaboresha onyesho la maandishi na aikoni kwenye upau wa hali. Pia, toleo hili pia linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama. Inapendekezwa usasishe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Upau wa hali">
<feature>Linaongeza ukubwa wa maandishi na linaongeza uzito wa aikoni ili kufanya kuwa rahisi kutambua maelezo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo ili kufanya kifaa chako kiendeshwe kwa uthabiti zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Sasa unaweza kuficha aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwa: Mipangilio > Usalama na faragha > Ulinzi wa data na kifaa > Ficha programu kutoka kwenye Skrini ya mwanzo.
Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapotumia muunganisho wa USB. Ibukizi la usalama au uthibitishaji hutokea unapochagua Hamisha picha au Hamisha faili / Android Otomatiki hivyo basi kuhakikisha uhamishaji salama wa data.
Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Okt 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பில் முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்க முடியும் மற்றும் USB இணைப்பைப் பயன்படுத்தும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு நிலைப் பட்டியில் உள்ள உரை மற்றும் ஐகான்களின் காட்சியையும் உகந்ததாக்குகிறது. கூடுதலாக, இந்த வெளியீடு சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது. இதைப் புதுப்பிக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="நிலைப் பட்டி">
<feature>தகவல்களை எளிதாக அடையாளம் காண, உரை அளவை அதிகரிக்கிறது மற்றும் ஐகான்களைத் தடிமனாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>உங்கள் சாதனத்தை மேலும் நிலையாக இயங்கச் செய்ய, சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>நீங்கள் இப்போது முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்கலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > பாதுகாப்பு மற்றும் தனியுரிமை > சாதனம் மற்றும் தரவுப் பாதுகாப்பு > முகப்புத் திரையிலிருந்து செயலிகளை மறைக்கவும்.
USB இணைப்பைப் பயன்படுத்தும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவைப்படுகிறது. பாதுகாப்பான தரவுப் பரிமாற்றத்தை உறுதிசெய்யும் வகையில், புகைப்படங்களைப் பரிமாற்று அல்லது கோப்புகளைப் பரிமாற்று / Android Auto என்பதைத் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கும்போது சரிபார்ப்பு அல்லது பாதுகாப்புத் தூண்டுதல் தோன்றும்.
சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (அக் 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌లో, హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచవచ్చు మరియు USB కనెక్షన్‌ను ఉపయోగిస్తున్నప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రామాణీకరణ అవసరం. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ స్థితి బార్‌లోని టెక్స్ట్ మరియు చిహ్నాల ప్రదర్శనను కూడా ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది. అదనంగా, ఈ విడుదల సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ చేర్చుతుంది. అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="స్టేటస్ బార్">
<feature>సమాచారాన్ని సులభంగా గుర్తించడానికి టెక్స్ట్ పరిమాణాన్ని పెంచుతుంది మరియు చిహ్నాలను బోల్డ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>మీ పరికరం మరింత స్థిరంగా అమలు అయ్యేలా చేయడానికి సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>మీరు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచవచ్చు. దీనిని ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > భద్రత మరియు గోప్యత > పరికరం మరియు డేటా సంరక్షణ > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ నుండి అప్లికేషన్‌లను దాచండి.
USB కనెక్షన్‌ను ఉపయోగిస్తున్నప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రామాణీకరణ అవసరం. డేటా బదిలీ సురక్షితమని నిర్ధారించడానికి మీరు ఫోటోలను బదిలీ చేయండి లేదా ఫైల్స్ బదిలీ చేయి / Android Auto ఎంచుకున్నప్పుడు ధృవీకరణ లేదా భద్రతా ప్రాంప్ట్ కనిపిస్తుంది.
Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (అక్టో 2024) అనేది సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రతా అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ ในการอัปเดตครั้งนี้ คุณจะสามารถซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลักได้ และจะจำเป็นต้องทำการตรวจสอบยืนยันผู้ใช้เมื่อใช้การเชื่อมต่อ USB และการอัปเดตครั้งนี้ได้เพิ่มประสิทธิภาพการแสดงผลข้อความและไอคอนในแถบสถานะ นอกจากนี้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้พัฒนาความเสถียรของระบบ และรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยด้วย เราขอแนะนำให้คุณทำการอัปเดต</feature>
</features>
<features module="แถบสถานะ">
<feature>เพิ่มขนาดข้อความ และทำให้ไอคอนหนาขึ้น เพื่อให้รับรู้ข้อมูลได้ง่ายดายยิ่งขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบเพื่อให้อุปกรณ์ของคุณใช้งานได้อย่างเสถียรมากขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>ต่อไปนี้คุณจะสามารถซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลักได้แล้ว ลองใช้ได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ความปลอดภัยและความเป็นส่วนตัว > อุปกรณ์และการปกป้องข้อมูล > ซ่อนแอปจากหน้าจอหลัก
จำเป็นต้องมีการตรวจสอบยืนยันผู้ใช้เมื่อใช้การเชื่อมต่อ USB โดยการยืนยันหรือข้อความแจ้งเกี่ยวกับความปลอดภัยจะปรากฏขึ้นเมื่อคุณเลือกถ่ายโอนภาพถ่ายหรือถ่ายโอนไฟล์ / Android Auto เพื่อให้การถ่ายโอนข้อมูลปลอดภัยยิ่งขึ้น
มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย Android (ต.ค. 2024) เพื่อรักษาความปลอดภัยระบบ หากต้องการข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตด้านความปลอดภัยของ HONOR โปรดไปที่เว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, sa update na ito, puwedeng itago ang mga icon ng home screen, at kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag ginagamit ang koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize din ng update na ito ang display ng text at mga icon sa status bar. Bukod pa rito, pinapahusay ng release na ito ang stability ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Pinapalaki ang text, at ginagawang bold ang mga icon para gawing mas madaling matukoy ang impormasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang matago ng mga icon ng home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag ginagamit ang koneksyon sa USB. May lalabas na pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, na tumitiyak samas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.
Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, sa update na ito, puwedeng itago ang mga icon ng home screen, at kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag ginagamit ang koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize din ng update na ito ang display ng text at mga icon sa status bar. Bukod pa rito, pinapahusay ng release na ito ang stability ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Status bar">
<feature>Pinapalaki ang text, at ginagawang bold ang mga icon para gawing mas madaling matukoy ang impormasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang matago ng mga icon ng home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag ginagamit ang koneksyon sa USB. May lalabas na pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, na tumitiyak samas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.
Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcı, bu güncellemede başlangıç ekranı simgeleri gizlenebilir ve USB bağlantısı kullanıldığında kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekir. Bu güncelleme ayrıca durum çubuğundaki metin ve simgelerin görüntülenmesini optimize eder. Bu sürüm ayrıca sistem kararlılığını iyileştirir ve bir güvenlik yaması içerir. Güncellemeniz önerilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Durum çubuğu">
<feature>Metin boyutu büyütülmüş ve bilgiler daha kolay anlaşılsın diye simgeler kalınlaştırılmıştır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Sistem kararlılığı iyileştirilerek cihazınız daha kararlı hale getirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Artık başlangıç ekranı simgelerini gizleyebilirsiniz. Şuraya giderek deneyin: Ayarlar > Güvenlik ve gizlilik > Cihaz ve veri koruması > Uygulamaları Başlangıç Ekranından gizleyin.
USB bağlantısı kullanılırken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekir. Fotoğraf aktarma veya Dosya aktarma / Android Auto seçeneğini işaretlediğinizde bir doğrulama ya da güvenlik istemi görünür, bu da daha güvenli veri aktarımı sağlar.
Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yaması (Eylül 2024) dahil edilmiştir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/10 adresinden web sitemizi ziyaret edin</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ۋە USB ئۇلىغاندا ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ھالەت بالدىقىدىكى خەت نۇسخىسى سىنبەلگىسىنى كۆرسىتىش ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ھالەت بالدىقى»">
<feature>ھالەت بالدىقىدىكى خەت نۇسخىسى سىنبەلگىسىنى كۆرسىتىش، خەت نۇسخىسىنى چوڭايتىش، توملىتىش سىنبەلگىسى ئۇسلۇبى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلۇپ، ئۇچۇر تونۇش نىسبىتى ئۆستۈرۈلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«سىستېما»">
<feature>‏سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى ئۆستۈرۈلۈپ، يانفونىڭىزنىڭ ئىجرا قىلىنىشى تېخىمۇ مۇقىملاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > بىخەتەرلىك ۋە مەخپىيەتلىك > ئۈسكۈنە ۋە مەلۇمات قوغداش > ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش.
USB ئۇلىنىشى ئارقىلىق ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، «رەسىم يوللاش» ياكى «ھۆججەت يوللاش/Android Auto» نى تاللىغاندا سالاھىيەت دەلىللەش كېرەك، مەلۇمات يوللىشىڭىز تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر.
ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 10-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! У цьому оновленні піктограми головного екрана можна приховати, а під час підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. Це оновлення також оптимізує відображення тексту та піктограм у рядку стану. Крім того, цей випуск покращує стабільність системи та містить виправлення системи безпеки. Рекомендуємо встановити це оновлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Рядок стану">
<feature>Збільшено розмір тексту та виділено жирним піктограми, щоб полегшити розпізнавання інформації.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Підвищено стабільність функціонування системи для надійнішої роботи пристрою.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Тепер ви можете приховати значки на головному екрані. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Налаштування" > "Безпека та конфіденційність" > "Захист пристрою та даних" > "Приховати додатки на головному екрані".
Під час підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. Коли ви вибираєте "Передавання фотографії" або "Передавання файлів / Android Auto", з’являється запит на перевірку, що забезпечує безпечніше передавання даних.
Для посилення безпеки системи впроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки Android від жовтня 2024 року. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، اس اپ ڈیٹ میں، ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کو چھپایا جا سکتا، اور USB کنکشن استعمال کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ یہ اپ ڈیٹ اسٹیٹس بار میں متن اور آئیکنز کے ڈسپلے کو بھی بہتر بناتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، یہ ریلیز سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="اسٹیٹس بار">
<feature>متن کے سائز کو بڑھاتی ہے، اور معلومات کو آسانی سے پہچاننے کے لیے آئیکنز کو بولڈ کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>آپ کی ڈیوائس کو زیادہ مستحکم طریقے سے چلانے کے لیے سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>اب آپ ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کو پوشیدہ کر سکتے ہیں۔ اسے یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: ترتیبات > سکیورٹی اور رازداری > ڈیوائس اور ڈیٹا کا تحفظ > ہوم اسکرین سے ایپس پوشیدہ کریں۔
‏USB کنکشن استعمال کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ جب آپ ڈیٹا کی محفوظ منتقلی کو یقینی بنا کر، تصاویر منتقل کریں یا فائلز منتقل کریں / Android خود کار کا انتخاب کرتے ہیں تو ایک تصدیق یا سکیورٹی پرامپٹ ظاہر ہوتا ہے۔
سسٹم سکیورٹی کے لیے Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اکتوبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10 ملاحظہ کریں</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanishda bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitish imkoniyati taqdim etildi va USB aloqasi uchun foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. Bu yangilanishda holat qatoridagi matn va belgilarning koʻrinishi ham optimallandi. Bundan tashqari, ushbu nashrda tizim barqarorligi yaxshilandi hamda xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi. Uni yangilash tavsiya etiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Holat qatori">
<feature>Axborotni oʻqishni osonlashtirish uchun matn oʻlchami kattalashtirildi va belgilar qalinlashtirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>Qurilmangiz yanada barqaror ishlashi uchun tizim barqarorligi oshirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Endi bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitishingiz mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Xavfsizlik va maxfiylik > Qurilma va maʼlumotlar himoyasi > Bosh ekranda ilovalarni berkitish.
USB aloqasi uchun foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. “Suratlarni uzatish” yoki “Fayllarni o‘tkazish / Android Auto” tanlaganida, maʼlumotlarni xavfsiz uzatishni taʼminlash uchun tasdiqlash yoki xavfsizlik haqida ogohlantirish oynasi ochiladi.
Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, oktabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, trong bản cập nhật này, bạn có thể ẩn các biểu tượng trên màn hình chính và cần xác thực người dùng khi sử dụng kết nối USB. Bản cập nhật này cũng tối ưu hóa khả năng hiển thị văn bản và biểu tượng trên thanh trạng thái. Ngoài ra, bản phát hành này cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống và tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Bạn nên cập nhật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Thanh trạng thái">
<feature>Tăng kích thước văn bản và in đậm các biểu tượng để dễ nhận biết thông tin hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống để giúp thiết bị của bạn chạy ổn định hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể ẩn các biểu tượng trên màn hình chính. Hãy thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Bảo mật và quyền riêng tư > Bảo vệ thiết bị và dữ liệu > Ẩn ứng dụng khỏi Màn hình chính.
Cần xác thực người dùng khi sử dụng kết nối USB. Một thông báo nhắc xác minh hoặc bảo mật sẽ xuất hiện khi bạn chọn Truyền tải ảnh hoặc Truyền tệp tin/Android Auto, giúp truyền dữ liệu an toàn hơn.
Bản cập nhật này tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 10 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標和 USB 連接用戶身份驗證功能，優化狀態欄字體圖標顯示，提升系統穩定性，整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【狀態欄】">
<feature>優化狀態欄字體圖標顯示，增大字體大小，加粗圖標樣式，提高資訊識別度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機運行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全性和私隱 > 裝置和數據保護 > 隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標。
新增USB連接用戶身份驗證功能，在選擇「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」時，需要進行身份驗證，讓您的數據傳輸更安全。
整合 Android 2024年10月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增隱藏應用程式桌面圖示和 USB 連接使用者身分驗證功能，最佳化狀態列字體和圖示顯示，提升系統穩定性，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【狀態列】">
<feature>最佳化狀態列字體和圖示顯示，增大字體大小，加粗圖示樣式，並提高資訊辨識度。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機執行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>新增隱藏應用程式桌面圖示功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全和隱私 > 裝置與資料保護 > 隱藏應用程式桌面圖示。
新增 USB 連接使用者身分驗證功能，在選取「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」時，需要進行身分驗證，讓您的資料傳輸更安全。
整合 Android 2024 年 10 月安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/10</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
