<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增隐藏应用桌面图标功能，相机新增三倍无损变焦功能，应用分身支持更多三方应用，优化部分场景相机拍摄效果，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="相机">
<feature>•  新增三倍无损变焦功能。
•  优化部分场景相机拍摄效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="应用分身">
<feature>•  新增支持更多三方应用。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  新增隐藏应用桌面图标功能，体验路径：设置>安全和隐私>设备与数据保护>隐藏应用桌面图标。
•  合入安卓2024年11月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update allows you to hide Home screen icons, and brings 3x Lossless Zooming to Camera. App Twin supports more third-party apps. This release also optimizes the shooting effect in some scenarios, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>• Camera enables you to use 3x Lossless Zooming.
• Optimizes the shooting effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Twin">
<feature>• App Twin supports more third-party apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>• You can now hide Home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen.
• Android Security Patch (Nov 2024) has been incorporated for the system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚዎች፣ ይህ ዝማኔ የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎችን እንዲደብቁ ይፈቅድልዎታል፣ እና 3x ጥራት ጉድለት የሌለው ማጉላት ወደ ካሜራ ያመጣል። መንታ መተግበሪያ ተጨማሪ የሦስተኛ-ወገን መተግበሪያዎችን ይደግፋል። ይህ ልቀት በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የማንሳት ተጽእኖን ያተባል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል። እንዲያዘምኑ ይመከራል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ካሜራ">
<feature>• ካሜራ 3x ጥራት ጉድለት የሌለው ማጉላትን እንዲጠቀሙ ያስችልዎታል።
• በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የማንሳት ተጽእኖን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="መንታ መተግበሪያ">
<feature>• መንታ መተግበሪያ ተጨማሪ የሦስተኛ-ወገን መተግበሪያዎችን ይደግፋል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>• አሁን የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎችን መደበቅ ይችላሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ደህንነት እና ግላዊነት > የመሳሪያ እና የውሂብ ጥበቃ > መተግበሪያዎችን ከመነሻ ገጽ ደብቅ።
• የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኖቬምበር 2024) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝመናዎች የበለጠ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድረ ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 ላይ ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በግል ውሂብዎ ላይ ተጸእኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድመው መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በዝማኔው ወቅት ማናቸውም አይነት ችግሮች ካጋጠሙዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يسمح لك هذا التحديث بإخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية، ويضيف إلى الكاميرا ميزة التكبير بمقدار 3 مرات بدون فقدان الجودة. تدعم ميزة الدخول المتعدد للتطبيقات المزيد من التطبيقات التابعة لطرف ثالث. يحسّن هذا الإصدار أيضًا تأثير التصوير في بعض السيناريوهات، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان. من المستحسن التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الكاميرا">
<feature>• تتيح لك الكاميرا استخدام التكبير بمقدار 3 مرات بدون فقدان الجودة. 
• يحسّن تأثير التصوير في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الدخول المتعدد للتطبيقات">
<feature>• تدعم ميزة الدخول المتعدد للتطبيقات المزيد من التطبيقات التابعة لطرف ثالث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>• يمكنك الآن إخفاء أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الأمان والخصوصية > حماية الجهاز > إخفاء التطبيقات من الشاشة الرئيسية. 
• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (نوفمبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে আপোনাক হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে আৰু কেমেৰালৈ 3x ক্ষতিহীন ঝুমিং লৈ আহে। এপ্প্‌ টুইনে অধিক তৃতীয়-পক্ষৰ এপ্প্‌ সমৰ্থন কৰে। এই মুক্তিয়ে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত শ্বুটিঙৰ প্ৰভাৱো অনুকূলন কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কেমেৰা">
<feature>• কেমেৰাই আপোনাক 3x ক্ষতিহীন ঝুমিং ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিবলৈ সক্ষম কৰে। 
• কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত শ্বুটিঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="এপ্প্‌ টুইন">
<feature>• এপ্প্‌ টুইনে অধিক তৃতীয়-পক্ষৰ এপ্প্‌ সমৰ্থন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>• আপুনি এতিয়া হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ লুকুৱাব পাৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > নিৰাপত্তা আৰু গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইচ আৰু ডাটা সুৰক্ষা > হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ পৰা এপ্প্‌সমূহ লুকুৱাওক। 
• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (নবেম্বৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ’লে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰক বা সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাওক।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçilər, bu yeniləmə sizə Əsas ekran nişanlarını gizlətməyə imkan verir və Kameraya 3x İtkisiz Böyütmə gətirir. Əkiz proqram daha çox üçüncü tərəf proqramını dəstəkləyir. Bu buraxılış həmçinin bəzi ssenarilərdə çəkiliş effektini optimallaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketini özündə birləşdirir. Yeniləmək tövsiyə olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera 3x İtkisiz Böyütmədən istifadə etməyə imkan verir.
• Bəzi ssenarilərdə çəkiliş effektini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Əkiz proqram">
<feature>• Əkiz proqram daha çox üçüncü tərəf proqramını dəstəkləyir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>• İndi siz Əsas ekran nişanlarını gizlədə bilərsiniz. Bu bölmələrə keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Təhlükəsizlik və məxfilik > Cihaz və verilənlərin mühafizəsi > Proqramları Əsas ekrandan gizlədin.
• Sistemin təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Noyabr 2024) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki mbisakake sampeyan ndhelikake ikon Layar ngarep, lan menehi Zoom Tanpa Ilang 3x kanggo Kamera. Apl Kembar ndhukung luwih akeh apl pihak katelu. Rilis iki uga ngoptimalake efek ngrekam ing sawetara skenario, lan nggabungake patch keamanan. Sampeyan disaranake supaya nganyarake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera mbisakake sampeyan nggunakake Zoom Tanpa Ilang 3x.
• Ngoptimalake efek ngrekam ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apl Kembar">
<feature>• Apl Kembar ndhukung luwih akeh apl pihak katelu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Sampeyan saiki bisa ndhelikake ikon Layar ngarep. Coba fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Keamanan lan privasi > Piranti lan proteksi data> Dhelikake apl saka Layar ngarep.
• Patch Keamanan Android (Nop 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dhukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem biće vam omogućeno sakrivanje ikona na početnom ekranu. Ovim ažuriranjem se u aplikaciji Kamera uvodi 3x zumiranje bez gubitaka. Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava više aplikacija treće strane. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se optimizuje učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama i ovo ažuriranje sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• U aplikaciji Kamera omogućeno je korišćenje 3x zumiranja bez gubitaka.
• Optimizovan je učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blizanac aplikacija">
<feature>• Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava još aplikacija trećih strana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete ući u Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Uređaji i zaštita podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi HONOR, posetite našu veb-stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem biće vam omogućeno sakrivanje ikona na početnom ekranu. Ovim ažuriranjem se u aplikaciji Kamera uvodi 3x zumiranje bez gubitaka. Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava više aplikacija treće strane. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se optimizuje učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama i ovo ažuriranje sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• U aplikaciji Kamera omogućeno je korišćenje 3x zumiranja bez gubitaka.
• Optimizovan je učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blizanac aplikacija">
<feature>• Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava još aplikacija trećih strana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete ući u Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Uređaji i zaštita podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi HONOR, posetite našu veb-stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem biće vam omogućeno sakrivanje ikona na početnom ekranu. Ovim ažuriranjem se u aplikaciji Kamera uvodi 3x zumiranje bez gubitaka. Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava više aplikacija treće strane. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se optimizuje učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama i ovo ažuriranje sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• U aplikaciji Kamera omogućeno je korišćenje 3x zumiranja bez gubitaka.
• Optimizovan je učinak snimanja u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blizanac aplikacija">
<feature>• Funkcija Blizanac aplikacija podržava još aplikacija trećih strana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Sada možete da sakrijete ikone na početnom ekranu. Isprobajte tako što ćete ući u Podešavanja > Bezbednost i privatnost > Uređaji i zaštita podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija sa početnog ekrana.
• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2024) uključena je radi bezbednosti sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi HONOR, posetite našu veb-stranicu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне дазваляе хаваць значкі галоўнага экрана і дадае ў праграму «Камера» функцыю трохкратнага павелічэння без страты якасці выявы. Двайнік праграмы цяпер падтрымліваецца ў большай колькасці праграм трэціх бакоў. Гэта версія аптымізуе эфект здымкі ў некаторых сцэнарыях і ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Рэкамендуецца ўстанавіць абнаўленне.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• У праграму «Камера» дададзена функцыя трохкратнага павелічэння без страты якасці выявы.
• У некаторых сцэнарыях аптымізаваны эфект здымкі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Двайнік праграмы">
<feature>• Двайнік праграмы падтрымліваецца ў большай колькасці праграм трэціх бакоў.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>• Цяпер вы можаце хаваць значкі галоўнага экрана. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Бяспека і прыватнасць > Абарона прылады і даных > Схаваць праграмы з галоўнага экрана».
• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (лістапад 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация ви позволява да скривате иконите на началния екран и намалява загубите при мащабиране на камерата 3 пъти. Приложението-близнак поддържа повече приложения от трети страни. Тази версия също така оптимизира ефекта на заснемане в някои ситуации и включва корекция за сигурност. Препоръчва се да актуализирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• Камерата ви дава възможност да използвате мащабиране с 3 пъти по-малко загуби.
-• Оптимизира ефекта на заснемане в някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Приложение-близнак">
<feature>• Приложението-близнак поддържа повече приложения от трети страни.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>• Вече можете да скривате иконите на началния екран. Изпробвайте това, като отидете на: „Настройки > Сигурност и поверителност > Защита на устройството и данните > Скриване на приложения от началния екран“.
• Включена е корекция за сигурност на Android (ноември 2024 г.) за сигурност на системата. За повече информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR, моля, посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারীরা, এই আপডেটটি আপনাকে হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলি লুকাতে দেয় এবং ক্যামেরায় 3x লসলেস জুমিং নিয়ে আসে। অ্যাপ টুইন আরো তৃতীয় পক্ষের অ্যাপকে সমর্থন করে। এছাড়াও এই রিলিজটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে শুটিং এফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে এবং এতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। আপডেট করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ক্যামেরা">
<feature>• ক্যামেরা আপনাকে 3x লসলেস জুমিং ব্যবহার করতে সক্ষম করে। 
• কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে শুটিং এফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="অ্যাপ টুইন">
<feature>• অ্যাপ টুইন আরো তৃতীয় পক্ষের অ্যাপকে সমর্থন করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>• আপনি এখন হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলি লুকাতে পারেন। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > নিরাপত্তা ও গোপনীয়তা > ডিভাইস এবং ডেটা সুরক্ষা > হোম স্ক্রিন থেকে অ্যাপগুলি লুকান। 
• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (নভেম্বর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་པ་དང་། པར་ཆས་ཀྱིས་ལྡབ་གསུམ་སྐྱོན་མེད་མདོ་འགྱུར་གྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཆ་གཅིག་གིས་དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་ཕྱོགས་གསུམ་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་བརྙན་ལེན་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད།རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་གཤིས་ནུས་དང་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="པར་ཆས།">
<feature>• ལྡབ་གསུམ་སྐྱོན་མེད་མདོ་འགྱུར་གྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད།
• བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་བརྙན་ལེན་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཆ་གཅིག">
<feature>• དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་ཕྱོགས་གསུམ་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད་པ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="བདེ་འཇགས།">
<feature>• སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བདེ་འཇགས་དང་སྒེར་གསང་། དེ་ནས་སྒྲིག་ཆས་དང་གཞི་གྲངས་སྲུང་སྐྱོབ། དེ་ནས་སྦས་སྐུང་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཀྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།
• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 11 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/11 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་སྔར་བཞིན་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ལེགས་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovo ažuriranje vam omogućava da sakrijete ikone sa početnog ekrana te vam donosi 3x Zumiranje bez gubitka podataka na Fotoaparatu. Blizanac aplikacija podržava više aplikacija treće strane. Ovo izdanje također optimizira efekat snimanja u nekim scenarijima te ugrađuje sigurnosne zakrpe. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>• Fotoaparat vam omogućava 3x Zumiranje bez gubitka podataka.
• Optimizira efekat snimanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Blizanac aplikacija">
<feature>• Blizanac aplikacija podržava više trećih strana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>• Sada možete sakriti ikone sa početnog ekrana. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Sakrivanje aplikacija s početnog ekrana.
• Sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2024.) je ugrađena radi sigurnosti sistema. Za više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima, posjetite našu web lokaciju https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolguts usuaris, aquesta actualització us permet amagar les icones de la pantalla inicial, i aporta un zoom 3x sense pèrdua a la càmera. Aplicació doble és compatible amb més aplicacions de tercers. Aquesta versió també optimitza l'efecte de captura en determinades situacions, i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Es recomana que feu l'actualització.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càmera">
<feature>• La càmera us permet utilitzar un zoom 3x sense pèrdua.
• Optimitza l'efecte de captura en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicació doble">
<feature>• L'Aplicació doble és compatible amb més aplicacions de tercers.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>• Ara podeu amagar les icones de la pantalla inicial. Proveu-ho des de: Configuració > Seguretat i privacitat > Dispositiu i protecció de dades > Amagar aplicacions de la Pantalla inicial.
• S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (novembre de 2024) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, visiteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però, així i tot, us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato aktualizace vám umožňuje skrýt ikony na domovské obrazovce a přináší 3x bezztrátové přiblížení do Fotoaparátu. Zdvojení aplikace podporuje více aplikací třetích stran. Tato verze také v některých scénářích optimalizuje fotografování a instaluje bezpečnostní opravu. Doporučujeme aktualizovat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>• Fotoaparát umožňuje používat 3x bezztrátový zoom. 
• Optimalizuje fotografování v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zdvojení aplikace">
<feature>• Zdvojení aplikace podporuje více aplikací třetích stran.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>• Nyní můžete skrýt ikony domovské obrazovky. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Zabezpečení a soukromí > Ochrana zařízení a dat > Skrýt aplikace na domovské obrazovce. 
• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (listopad 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne opdatering lader dig skjule ikoner på Startskærmen og bringer Kamera 3x zoom uden tab. App-tvilling understøtter flere tredjeparts-apps. Denne udgave optimerer optagelseseffekten i nogle scenarier og integrerer en sikkerhedspatch. Opdatering anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera lader dig bruge 3x zoom uden tab.
• Optimerer optagelseseffekten i nogle scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-tvilling">
<feature>• App-tvilling understøtter flere tredjeparts-apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>• Nu kan du skjule ikoner på Startskærmen. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Sikkerhed og personlige oplysninger > Enhed og databeskyttelse > Skjul apps på Startskærmen.
• Android sikkerhedspatch (nov 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht es Ihnen, Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm auszublenden, und Sie erhalten verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen für die Kamera. App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps. Diese Version optimiert außerdem den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Die Kamera ermöglicht Ihnen verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen. 
• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Twin">
<feature>• App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Sicherheit und Datenschutz > Gerät und Datenschutz > Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden. 
• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht es Ihnen, Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm auszublenden, und Sie erhalten verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen für die Kamera. App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps. Diese Version optimiert außerdem den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Die Kamera ermöglicht Ihnen verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen. 
• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Twin">
<feature>• App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Sicherheit und Datenschutz > Gerät und Datenschutz > Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden. 
• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, dieses Update ermöglicht es Ihnen, Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm auszublenden, und Sie erhalten verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen für die Kamera. App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps. Diese Version optimiert außerdem den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Die Kamera ermöglicht Ihnen verlustfreies 3-faches Zoomen. 
• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Twin">
<feature>• App-Twin unterstützt mehr Drittanbieter-Apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Sie können jetzt die Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm ausblenden. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Sicherheit und Datenschutz > Gerät und Datenschutz > Apps vom Startbildschirm ausblenden. 
• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητοί χρήστες, αυτή η ενημέρωση σας επιτρέπει να αποκρύπτετε τα εικονίδια της Αρχικής οθόνης και φέρνει τη Μεγέθυνση χωρίς απώλειες 3x στην Κάμερα. Η Δίδυμη εφαρμογή υποστηρίζει περισσότερες εφαρμογές τρίτων. Αυτή η έκδοση βελτιστοποιεί επίσης το αποτέλεσμα λήψης σε ορισμένα σενάρια και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Συνιστάται η ενημέρωση.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κάμερα">
<feature>• Η Κάμερα σας επιτρέπει να χρησιμοποιείτε τη Μεγέθυνση χωρίς απώλειες 3x. 
• Βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα λήψης σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Δίδυμη εφαρμογή">
<feature>• Η Δίδυμη εφαρμογή υποστηρίζει περισσότερες εφαρμογές τρίτων.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>• Πλέον μπορείτε να αποκρύψετε τα εικονίδια της Αρχικής οθόνης. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Ασφάλεια και απόρρητο > Προστασία συσκευής και δεδομένων > Απόκρυψη εφαρμογών από την Αρχική οθόνη. 
• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Νοέμβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update allows you to hide Home screen icons, and brings 3x Lossless Zooming to Camera. App Twin supports more third-party apps. This release also optimises the shooting effect in some scenarios, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>• Camera enables you to use 3x Lossless Zooming. 
• Optimises the shooting effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Twin">
<feature>• App Twin supports more third-party apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>• You can now hide Home screen icons. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security and privacy > Device and data protection > Hide apps from Home screen. 
• Android Security Patch (Nov 2024) has been incorporated for the system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios, esta actualización les permite ocultar los iconos de la pantalla principal y aporta zoom sin pérdida de 3 aumentos a la Cámara. App gemela admite más aplicaciones de terceros. Esta versión también optimiza el efecto de disparo en algunos escenarios e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>• Cámara le permite utilizar el zoom sin pérdida de 3 aumentos. 
• Optimiza el efecto de disparo en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App gemela">
<feature>• App gemela admite más aplicaciones de terceros.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>• Ahora puede ocultar los iconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección de dispositivos y datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal. 
• Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios, esta actualización permite ocultar los íconos de la pantalla principal y ofrece zoom sin pérdida de calidad de hasta 3x en la Cámara. App gemela admite más aplicaciones de terceros. Esta versión también optimiza el efecto de captura en algunos escenarios e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Se recomienda actualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>• La Cámara permite utilizar el zoom sin pérdida de hasta 3x. 
• Optimiza el efecto de captura en algunas situaciones.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App gemela">
<feature>• App gemela admite más aplicaciones de terceros.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>• Ahora puede ocultar los íconos de la pantalla principal. Para probarlo, vaya a: Ajustes > Seguridad y privacidad > Protección del dispositivo y de los datos > Ocultar aplicaciones de la pantalla principal. 
• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus võimaldab peita avakuva ikoonid ja toob Kaamerasse kolmekordse kadudeta suumi. Kaksikrakendus toetab rohkemaid kolmanda osapoole rakendusi. See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras jäädvustamisefekti ja sisaldab turvapaika. Soovitatav on värskendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaamera">
<feature>• Kaamera võimaldab kasutada kolmekordset kadudeta suumi. 
• Optimeerib mõnes olukorras jäädvustamisefekti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaksikrakendus">
<feature>• Kaksikrakendus toetab rohkemaid kolmanda osapoole rakendusi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>• Nüüd saate avakuva ikoonid ära peita. Proovige seda, minnes menüüsse Sätted > Turve ja privaatsus > Seadme- ja andmekaitse > Peida avakuval olevad rakendused. 
• Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (november 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, eguneratze honetan Hasierako pantailako ikonoak ezkuta ditzakezu eta 3 aldiz gutxiago galtzen duen zoom-efektua gehitu da Kameran. Aplikazio bikiak hirugarrenen aplikazio gehiago onartzen ditu. Bertsio honetan egoera batzuetako kapturatze-efektua ere optimizatu da eta segurtasun-adabakiak gehitu dira. Eguneratzea gomendatzen da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamerak 3 aldiz gutxiago galtzen duen zoom-efektua dauka.
• Egoera batzuetako kapturatze-efektua optimizatu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikazio bikia">
<feature>• Aplikazio bikiak hirugarrenen aplikazio gehiago onartzen ditu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>• Orain hasierako pantailaren ikonoak ezkuta ditzakezu. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Segurtasuna eta pribatutasuna > Gailuen eta datuen babesa > Ezkutatu hasierako pantailako aplikazioak.
• Sistemaren segurtasunerako, Android-en segurtasun-adabakia gehitu da (2024ko aza). HONOR segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, bisitatu gure webgunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia egitea bertsioa eguneratu baino lehen.
2. Eguneratzeko unean arazorik baduzu, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربران گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به شما امکان می‌دهد آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را پنهان کنید و «زوم بدون افت» ۳ برابری را در «دوربین» فراهم می‌کند. «برنامۀ جفتی» از برنامه‌های شخص ثالث بیشتری پشتیبانی می‌کند. این نسخه همچنین جلوه تصویربرداری را در برخی شرایط بهینه می‌کند و یک وصله امنیتی در آن گنجانده شده است. توصیه می‌شود به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="دوربین">
<feature>‏• «دوربین» این امکان را به شما می‌دهد که از «زوم بدون افت» ۳ برابری استفاده کنید
‏• جلوه تصویربرداری را در برخی شرایط بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="برنامۀ جفتی">
<feature>‏• «برنامۀ جفتی» از برنامه‌های شخص ثالث بیشتری پشتیبانی می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>‏• اکنون می توانید آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را پنهان کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: تنظیمات > امنیت و حریم خصوصی > محافظت از دستگاه و داده‌ها > پنهان کردن برنامه‌ها از «صفحۀ اصلی».
‏• وصله امنیتی Android (نوامبر ۲۰۲۴) برای امنیت سیستم گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر درباره به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به نشانی https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 مراجعه کنید</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات:" type="end">
<feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvät käyttäjät, tämä päivitys mahdollistaa aloitusnäytön kuvakkeiden piilottamisen ja lisää Kameraan 3-kertaisen häviöttömän zoomauksen. Kaksoissovellus tukee lisää kolmannen osapuolen sovelluksia. Tämä päivitys myös optimoi kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen. Päivittämistä suositellaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kameralla voidaan käyttää 3-kertaista häviötöntä zoomausta.
• Optimoi kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaksoissovellus">
<feature>• Kaksoissovellus tukee lisää kolmannen osapuolen sovelluksia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>• Voit nyt piilottaa aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet. Kokeile sitä menemällä kohtaan Asetukset > Turvallisuus ja tietosuoja > Laitteen ja tietojen suojaus > Piilota sovellukset aloitusnäytöltä.
• Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (marraskuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Chers utilisateurs, cette mise à jour vous permet de masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil et apporte un zoom sans perte 3x à l'Appareil photo. Application jumelle prend en charge davantage d'applications tierces. Cette version optimise également l'effet de prise de vue dans certains scénarios et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>• L'appareil photo vous permet d'utiliser un zoom sans perte 3x. 
• Optimise l'effet de prise de vue dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Application jumelle">
<feature>• Application jumelle prend en charge davantage d'applications tierces.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>• Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil. 
• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Chers utilisateurs, cette mise à jour vous permet de masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil et apporte un zoom sans perte 3x à l'Appareil photo. Application jumelle prend en charge davantage d'applications tierces. Cette version optimise également l'effet de prise de vue dans certains scénarios et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>• L'appareil photo vous permet d'utiliser un zoom sans perte 3x. 
• Optimise l'effet de prise de vue dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Application jumelle">
<feature>• Application jumelle prend en charge davantage d'applications tierces.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>• Vous pouvez désormais masquer les icônes de l'écran d'accueil. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en allant dans : Paramètres > Sécurité et vie privée > Protection des appareils et des données > Masquer les applications de l'écran d'accueil. 
• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios, esta actualización permítelles ocultar as iconas da pantalla de inicio e incorpora un triplo aumento sen perdas para a Cámara. Aplicación xemelga é compatible con máis aplicacións de terceiros. Esta versión tamén optimiza o efecto de captura nalgunhas situacións e incorpora un parche de seguranza. Recoméndase actualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>• Cámara permítelle usar un triplo aumento sen perdas.
• Optimiza o efecto de captura nalgunhas situacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicación xemelga">
<feature>• Aplicación xemelga é compatible con máis aplicacións de terceiros.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>• Agora pode ocultar as iconas da Pantalla de inicio. Pode probalo indo a: Configuración > Seguranza e privacidade > Dispositivo e protección de datos > Ocultar aplicacións de Pantalla de inicio.
•Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (novembro 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તાઓ, આ અપડેટ તમને હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નો છુપાવવાની અનુમતિ આપે છે અને કૅમેરામાં 3x લોસલેસ ઝૂમિંગ લાવે છે. એપ ટ્વીન વધુ તૃતીય પક્ષ એપ્લિકેશન્સને સમર્થન કરે છે. આ રિલીઝ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં શૂટિંગ પ્રભાવને પણ ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે. અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કૅમેરા">
<feature>• કૅમેરા તમને 3x લોસલેસ ઝૂમિંગનો ઉપયોગ કરવા સક્ષમ બનાવે છે.
• કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં શૂટિંગ પ્રભાવને ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="એપ ટ્વીન">
<feature>• એપ ટ્વીન વધુ તૃતીય-પક્ષની એપ્લિકેશન્સને સમર્થન કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>તમે હવે હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન છુપાવી શકો છો. આના પર જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > સુરક્ષા અને ગોપનીયતા > ઉપકરણ અને ડેટા સુરક્ષા > હોમ સ્ક્રીન પરથી એપ્લિકેશન્સ છુપાવો.
• સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે એન્ડ્રોઇડ Android પેચ (નવે 2024) સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ताओं, इस अद्यतन से आपको होम स्क्रीन के आइकन छिपाने की अनुमति मिलती है और कैमरे में 3x लॉसलेस ज़ूमिंग दी जाती है। ऐप ट्विन में अधिक तृतीय-पक्ष ऐप्स का समर्थन किया जाता है। इस रिलीज़ से कुछ परिदृश्यों में शूटिंग प्रभाव को भी अनुकूलित किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता है। अद्यतन करने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>• कैमरा से आप 3x लॉसलेस ज़ूमिंग का उपयोग करने में सक्षम हो जाते है।
• कुछ परिदृश्यों में शूटिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ऐप ट्विन">
<feature>• ऐप ट्विन में अधिक तृतीय-पक्ष ऐप्स का समर्थन किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• अब आप होम स्क्रीन आइकन छिपा सकते हैं। इसे आज़माने के लिए यहाँ जाएँ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा और गोपनीयता > डिवाइस और डेटा सुरक्षा > ऐप्स को होम स्क्रीन से छिपाएँ।
• सिस्टम सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवंबर 2024) शामिल किया जाता है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovo vam ažuriranje omogućuje skrivanje ikona s Početnog zaslona i donosi 3x zumiranje bez gubitaka u aplikaciji Fotoaparat. Aplikacija blizanac podržava više aplikacija treće strane. Ovim se izdanjem optimizira i efekt snimanja u nekim scenarijima, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>• Fotoaparat vam omogućuje korištenje 3x zumiranje bez gubitaka. 
• Optimizira se efekt snimanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacija blizanac">
<feature>• Aplikacija blizanac podržava više aplikacija treće strane.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>• Sada možete sakriti ikone s Početnog zaslona. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Sigurnost i privatnost > Zaštita uređaja i podataka > Skrivanje aplikacija s Početnog zaslona. 
• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (studeni 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználók! Ez a frissítés lehetővé teszi a főképernyő ikonjainak az elrejtését, és bevezeti a 3-szoros veszteségmentes nagyítást a Kamera alkalmazásban. Az Ikeralkalmazás mostantól több harmadik féltől származó alkalmazást támogat. Ez a verzió emellett bizonyos esetekben optimalizálja a felvételkészítés hatását, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• A Kamera mostantól támogatja a 3-szoros veszteségmentes nagyítást. 
• Bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizáltuk a fényképezés működését.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikeralkalmazás">
<feature>• Az Ikeralkalmazás mostantól több harmadik féltől származó alkalmazást támogat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>• Mostantól elrejtheti a főképernyő ikonjait. Próbálja ki az alábbi útvonalon: Beállítások > Biztonság és adatvédelem > Készülék- és adatvédelem > Alkalmazások elrejtése a főképernyőről. 
• Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. november). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel a weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memungkinkan Anda untuk menyembunyikan ikon Layar beranda, dan membawakan Perbesaran Tanpa Kehilangan 3x ke Kamera. Kembaran Aplikasi mendukung lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar di beberapa skenario, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera memungkinkan Anda untuk menggunakan Perbesaran Tanpa Kehilangan 3x.
• Mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kembaran Aplikasi">
<feature>• Kembaran Aplikasi mendukung lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Kini, Anda dapat menyembunyikan ikon Layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini memungkinkan Anda untuk menyembunyikan ikon Layar beranda, dan membawakan Perbesaran Tanpa Kehilangan 3x ke Kamera. Kembaran Aplikasi mendukung lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar di beberapa skenario, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera memungkinkan Anda untuk menggunakan Perbesaran Tanpa Kehilangan 3x.
• Mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kembaran Aplikasi">
<feature>• Kembaran Aplikasi mendukung lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Kini, Anda dapat menyembunyikan ikon Layar beranda. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Keamanan dan privasi > Perlindungan data dan perangkat > Sembunyikan aplikasi dari Layar beranda.
• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentili utenti, questo aggiornamento consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home e aggiunge lo zoom 3x senza perdita di qualità alla Fotocamera. È stato ampliato il numero delle app di terze parti supportate da App gemella. Questa versione ottimizza anche l'effetto di scatto in alcuni scenari e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>• La Fotocamera consente di utilizzare lo zoom 3x senza perdita di qualità. 
• Viene ottimizzato l'effetto di scatto in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App gemella">
<feature>• È stato ampliato il numero delle app di terze parti supportate da App gemella.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>• Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home. 
• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentili utenti, questo aggiornamento consente di nascondere le icone della schermata Home e aggiunge lo zoom 3x senza perdita di qualità alla Fotocamera. È stato ampliato il numero delle app di terze parti supportate da App gemella. Questa versione ottimizza anche l'effetto di scatto in alcuni scenari e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>• La Fotocamera consente di utilizzare lo zoom 3x senza perdita di qualità. 
• Viene ottimizzato l'effetto di scatto in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App gemella">
<feature>• È stato ampliato il numero delle app di terze parti supportate da App gemella.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>• Ora è possibile nascondere le icone della schermata Home. Per provare la funzione, vai a: Impostazioni > Sicurezza e privacy > Protezione dei dispositivi e dei dati > Nascondi le app dalla schermata Home. 
• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמשים יקרים, עדכון זה מאפשר להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית ומביא עימו הגדלה 3x ללא אובדן ל'מצלמה'. 'יישום תאום' תומך בעוד יישומי צד שלישי. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את אפקט הצילום בתרחישים מסוימים ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>‏• היישום 'מצלמה' מאפשר להשתמש בהגדלה 3x ללא אובדן.
‏• ממטב את אפקט הצילום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישום תאום">
<feature>‏• 'יישום תאום' תומך בעוד יישומי צד שלישי.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏• כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על התקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמשים יקרים, עדכון זה מאפשר להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית ומביא עימו הגדלה 3x ללא אובדן ל'מצלמה'. 'יישום תאום' תומך בעוד יישומי צד שלישי. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את אפקט הצילום בתרחישים מסוימים ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>‏• היישום 'מצלמה' מאפשר להשתמש בהגדלה 3x ללא אובדן.
‏• ממטב את אפקט הצילום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישום תאום">
<feature>‏• 'יישום תאום' תומך בעוד יישומי צד שלישי.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏• כעת ניתן להסתיר את סמלי מסך הבית. נסה זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'אבטחה ופרטיות' > 'הגנה על התקן ועל נתונים' > 'הסתר יישומים ממסך הבית'.
‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新によって、ホーム画面のアイコンの非表示が可能になり、カメラに3倍のロスレスズームが搭載されます。また、ツインアプリでサポートされるサードパーティ製アプリが増えます。さらに今回のリリースでは、一部の状況における撮影効果が最適化され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。更新することをおすすめします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="カメラ">
<feature>• カメラで3倍のロスレスズームを利用できます。
• 一部の状況で撮影効果が最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ツインアプリ">
<feature>• ツインアプリがサポートするサードパーティ製アプリが増えます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>• ホーム画面のアイコンを非表示にできるようになりました。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [セキュリティとプライバシー] > [デバイスとデータ保護] > [ホーム画面でアプリを非表示]に移動してください。
• システムセキュリティのために、Androidセキュリティパッチ（2024年11月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებლებო, ამ განახლების საშუალებით შეძლებთ საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების დამალვას და კამერის 3-მაგი უდანაკარგო მასშტაბირებით სარგებლობას. ტყუპ აპს აქვს მესამე მხარის მეტი აპის მხარდაჭერა. ამ გამოშვებაში ოპტიმიზებულია გადაღების ეფექტებიც გარკვეულ სცენარებში და მასში შესულია უსაფრთხოების შესწორება. გირჩევთ განახლებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="კამერა">
<feature>• კამერა საშუალებას გაძლევთ, გამოიყენოთ 3-მაგი უდანაკარგო მასშტაბირება.
• ოპტიმიზებულია გადაღების ეფექტები გარკვეულ სცენარებში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ტყუპი აპი">
<feature>• ტყუპ აპს აქვს მესამე მხარის მეტი აპის მხარდაჭერა.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>• უკვე შეგიძლიათ საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების დამალვა. საცდელად გადადით: პარამეტრები > უსაფრთხოება და კონფიდენციალურობა > მოწყობილობისა და მონაცემთა დაცვა > აპების დამალვა საწყისი ეკრანიდან.
• Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (ნოემბერი, 2024) ჩაშენებულია სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის. HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыруға мүмкіндік береді және «Камера» қолданбасына 3 есе еш жоғалтусыз масштабтау мүмкіндігін береді. «Қолданба көшірмесі» мүмкіндігі қосымша үшінші тарап қолданбаларын қолдайды. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым кейбір сценарийлерде түсіру әсерін оңтайландырады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жаңарту ұсынылады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• «Камера» сізге 3 есе еш жоғалтусыз масштабтауды пайдалануға мүмкіндік береді.
• Кейбір сценарийлерде түсіру әсерін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қолданба көшірмесі">
<feature>• «Қолданба көшірмесі» көбірек үшінші тарап қолданбаларына қолдау көрсетеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Енді негізгі экран белгішелерін жасыра аласыз. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Қауіпсіздік және құпиялық» > «Құрылғыны және деректерді қорғау» > «Негізгі экрандағы қолданбаларды жасыру».
• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қараша, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យអ្នកលាក់រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម និងនាំយកការពង្រីក 3x ដោយមិនបាត់បង់គុណភាពទៅក្នុងកាមេរ៉ា។ កម្មវិធីភ្លោះអាចប្រើជាមួយកម្មវិធីរបស់ភាគីទីបី។ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះក៏ធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនថតប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខផងដែរ។ សូមណែនាំឱ្យធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កាមេរ៉ា">
<feature>• កាមេរ៉ាអាចឱ្យអ្នកប្រើការពង្រីក 3x ដោយមិនបាត់បង់គុណភាព។
• ធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនថតប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កម្មវិធីភ្លោះ">
<feature>• កម្មវិធីភ្លោះអាចប្រើជាមួយកម្មវិធីរបស់ភាគីទីបីច្រើនទៀត។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>• ឥឡូវ អ្នកអាចលាក់រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។ សាកល្បងប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > សន្តិសុខ និងឯកជនភាព > ការការពារឧបករណ៍ និងទិន្នន័យ > លាក់កម្មវិធីពីអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។
• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (វិច្ឆិកា 2024) ត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូលសម្រាប់សន្តិសុខប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់ព័ត៌មានបន្ថែមអំពីបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពសន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅគេហទំព័ររបស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಲು ನಿಮಗೆ ಅವಕಾಶ ಕಲ್ಪಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾಗೆ 3x ಲಾಸ್‌ಲೆಸ್ ಜೂಮಿಂಗ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಟ್ವಿನ್ ಹೆಚ್ಚು ತರ್ಡ್-ಪಾರ್ಟಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್ ಪರಿಣಾಮವನ್ನು ಕೂಡ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಒಂದು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಂಡಿದೆ. ನವೀಕರಿಸುವಂತೆ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
<feature>• ನೀವು 3x ಲಾಸ್‌ಲೆಸ್‌ ಜೂಮಿಂಗ್ ಬಳಸಲು ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ ಅವಕಾಶ ಕಲ್ಪಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.
• ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್ ಪರಿಣಾಮವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಟ್ವಿನ್">
<feature>• ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಟ್ವಿನ್ ಹೆಚ್ಚು ತರ್ಡ್-ಪಾರ್ಟಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>• ನೀವು ಈಗ ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಭದ್ರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಗೌಪ್ಯತೆ > ಸಾಧನ ಮತ್ತು ಡೇಟಾ ರಕ್ಷಣೆ > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌‍ನಿಂದ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಮರೆಮಾಡಿ.
• Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ನವೆಂಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트를 통해 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨기고 카메라에 3배 무손실 줌 기능을 추가할 수 있습니다. 트윈 앱은 더 많은 타사 앱을 지원합니다. 또한 이번 릴리스에서는 일부 시나리오에서 촬영 효과를 최적화하고 보안 패치를 적용했습니다. 업데이트하는 것이 좋습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="카메라">
<feature>• 카메라에서 3배 무손실 확대/축소를 실행할 수 있습니다. 
• 일부 시나리오에서 촬영 효과를 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="트윈 앱">
<feature>• 트윈 앱은 더 많은 타사 앱을 지원합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>• 이제 홈 화면 아이콘을 숨길 수 있습니다. 설정 > 보안 및 개인 정보 보호 > 장치 및 데이터 보안 > 홈 화면에서 앱 숨기기로 이동하여 사용해 보십시오. 
• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 11월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ເຊື່ອມໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ນຳການ​ຊູມແບບ​ບໍ່​ສູນ​ເສຍ 3x ມາ​ສູ່​ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ. ແອັບຄູ່​ຮອງ​ຮັບ​ແອັບ​ພາກ​ສ່ວນ​ທີ​ສາມ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ແລ້ວ. ນອກນັ້ນ ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວ​ນີ້ຍັງ​ປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ຖ່າຍ​​ຮູບ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ພາບ​ການໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ ແລະ ລວມ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ. ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ອັບ​ເດດ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
<feature>• ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​​ຊ່ວຍ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ໃຊ້ການ​ຊູມແບບ​ບໍ່​ສູນ​ເສຍ 3x ໄດ້. 
• ປັບເອັບ​ເຝັກການ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບໃນບາງສະພາບການ​ໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແອັບຄູ່​">
<feature>• ແອັບຄູ່​ຮອງ​ຮັບ​ແອັບ​ພາກ​ສ່ວນ​ທີ​ສາມ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ແລ້ວ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>• ຕອນ​ນີ້ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ເຊື່ອງ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ແລະ ຄວາມ​ເປັນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ > ການ​ປົກ​ປ້ອງ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ ແລະ ຂໍ້​ມູນ > ເຊື່ອງ​ແອັບຈາກໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​. 
• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ພະ​ຈິກ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys leidžia paslėpti pradžios ekrano piktogramas ir į Kamerą įtraukia 3 k. nenuostolinį priartinimą. Programėlių dvynė dera su daugiau trečiųjų šalių programėlių. Šioje laidoje taip pat kai kuriais atvejais optimizuojamas fotografavimo efektas ir įtraukiama saugumo pataisa. Rekomenduojama atnaujinti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera leidžia naudoti 3 k. nenuostolinį priartinimą.
• Kai kuriais atvejais optimizuojamas fotografavimo efektas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programėlė dvynė">
<feature>• Programėlių dvynė dera su daugiau trečiųjų šalių programėlių.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>• Nuo šiol galėsite paslėpti pradžios ekrano piktogramas. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nustatymai > Saugumas ir privatumas > Įrenginio ir duomenų apsauga > Slėpti programėles iš pradžios ekrano“.
• Sistemos saugumui užtikrinti buvo įdiegta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. lapkričio mėn.). Daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius rasite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę duomenų kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu var paslēpt sākuma ekrāna ikonas, un kamerai tas nodrošina trīskārtīgu bezzudumu tālummaiņu. Lietotnes pāris atbalsta vairāk trešo pušu lietotņu. Šis laidiens arī optimizē uzņemšanas efektu dažos gadījumos un ietver drošības ielāpu. Ieteicams atjaunināt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera ļauj izmantot trīskārtīgu bezzudumu tālummaiņu. 
• Optimizē uzņemšanas efektu dažiem scenārijiem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lietotnes pāris">
<feature>• Lietotnes pāris atbalsta vairāk trešo pušu lietotņu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>• Tagad varat paslēpt sākuma ekrāna ikonas. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Drošība un konfidencialitāte > Ierīču un datu aizsardzība > Slēpt lietotnes sākuma ekrānā. 
• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada novembris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता सभ, ई अपडेट अहाँ केँ होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ नुकयबाक अनुमति दैत अछि आओर कैमरा मे 3x साफ जूम दैत अछि। एप ट्विन आओर बेसी तेसर-पक्षक एप सभक सपोर्ट करैत अछि। ई रिलीज किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे शूटिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि आओर एकटा सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि। अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>• कैमरा अहाँ केँ 3x साफ जूम करबाक सुविधा दैत अछि।
• किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे शूटिंग प्रभाव अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एप ट्विन">
<feature>• एप ट्विन आओर तेसर-पक्षक एप सभक सपोर्ट करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• आब अहाँ होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ नुका सकैत छी। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > सुरक्षा आ गोपनीयता > डिवाइस आ डेटा संरक्षण > होम स्क्रीन सँ एप सभ नुकाउ।
सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवं 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणी:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E ngā kaiwhakamahi aroha, mā tēnei whakahōu ka tukua e koe te huna i ngā ata Mata kāinga, me te kawe mai i te Topa Kore ana 3x ki te Kāmera. E tautoko ana te Māhanga taupānga i ētahi anō taupānga rōpū kē. Ka arotautia hoki e tēnei putanga te pānga tākaro i ētahi tauari, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. E tūtohutia ana kia whakahōu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kāmera">
<feature>• Kāmera whakahohe e koe te whakamahi i te Topa Kore ana 3x.
• Ka arotautia te pānga tākaro i ētahi ngā tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Māhanga taupānga">
<feature>• E tautoko ana te Māhanga taupānga i ētahi anō ngā taupānga rōpū kē.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>• Ka taea ināianei te huna i ngā ata mata kāinga. Whakamātauria mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga > Te haumarutanga me te tūmataitinga > Parenga pūrere me raraunga hoki > Huna ngā taupānga mai i te mata Kāinga.
• Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Noema 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитувани корисници, ова ажурирање ви овозможува да ги скриете иконите на почетниот екран и воведува 3x зумирање без загуби за Камера. Апликација-близнак поддржува повеќе апликации од други производители. Оваа верзија го оптимизира и ефектот при фотографирање во некои сценарија и воведува безбедносна крпеница. Се препорачува да ажурирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• Камера ви овозможува да користите 3x зумирање без загуби.
• Го оптимизира ефектот при фотографирање во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Апликација-близнак">
<feature>• Апликација-близнак поддржува повеќе апликации од други производители.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>• Сега може да ги скриете иконите на почетниот екран. Испробајте така што ќе отидете до: Нагодување > Безбедност и приватност > Уред и заштита на податоци > Скриј апликации од почетниот екран.
• Безбедносната крпеница за Android (ноември 2024 г.) е вградена за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за безбедносните ажурирања од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но, се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако се појават проблеми во текот на ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താക്കളേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാൻ നിങ്ങളെ അനുവദിക്കുകയും ക്യാമറയിൽ 3x ലോസ്‌ലസ് സൂമിംഗ് കൊണ്ടുവരുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. 'ആപ്പ് ദ്വയം' കൂടുതൽ മൂന്നാം-കക്ഷി ആപ്പുകളെ പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു. കൂടാതെ, ഈ റിലീസ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ഷൂട്ടിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ക്യാമറ">
<feature>• 3x ലോസ്‌ലസ് സൂമിംഗ് ഉപയോഗിക്കാൻ ക്യാമറ നിങ്ങളെ പ്രാപ്‌തമാക്കുന്നു.
• ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ഷൂട്ടിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ആപ്പ് ദ്വയം">
<feature>• ആപ്പ് ദ്വയം കൂടുതൽ മൂന്നാം-കക്ഷി ആപ്പുകളെ പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>• നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കാവുന്നതാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > സുരക്ഷയും സ്വകാര്യതയും > ഉപകരണ, ഡാറ്റാ പരിരക്ഷ > ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ നിന്ന് ആപ്പുകൾ മറയ്‌ക്കുക.
• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (നവംബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="ശ്രദ്ധിക്കുക:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой болж, Камерт 3х Алдагдалгүй томруулах сонголт нэмлээ. Ихэр Апп илүү олон гуравдагч этгээдийн апликэйшн дэмждэг болов. Энэ шинэчлэлтээр мөн зарим тохиолдолд зураг авах нөлөөг оновчилж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаалаа. Шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камер">
<feature>• Камерт 3x Алдагдалгүй томруулах боломжтой болсон.
• Зарим тохиолдолд зураг авах нөлөөг оновчлов.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ихэр Апп">
<feature>• Ихэр Апп илүү олон гуравдагч этгээдийн апликэйшнийг дэмждэг болсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Одоо та Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийг нуух боломжтой боллоо. Та Тохиргоо > Хамгаалалт ба нууцлал > Төхөөрөмж ба өгөгдөл хамгаалалт > Үндсэн дэлгэцээс апликэйшн нуух руу очиж үүнийг туршиж үзнэ үү.
 Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны 11-р сар) системийн аюулгүй байдалд зориулж нэгтгэсэн. HONOR хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаарх дэлгэрэнгүй мэдээллийг авах бол манай https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 вэбсайтад зочилно уу</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्त्यांनो, हे अद्यतन आपल्याला मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्‍ह लपवण्याची अनुमती देते आणि कॅमेरामध्ये 3x लॉसलेस झूमिंग आणते. अ‍ॅप ट्विन अधिक तृतीय-पक्ष ॲप्सना समर्थन देते. हे प्रकाशन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये शूटिंग प्रभाव देखील अनुकूल करते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते. अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कॅमेरा">
<feature>• कॅमेरा आपल्याला 3x लॉसलेस झूमिंग वापरण्यास सक्षम करतो.
• काही परिस्थितींमध्ये शूटिंग प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="अ‍ॅप ट्विन">
<feature>• ॲप ट्विन अधिक तृतीय-पक्ष ॲप्सना समर्थन देते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>आपण आता मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे लपवू शकता. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुरक्षितता आणि गोपनीयता > उपकरण आणि डेटा संरक्षण > मुख्य स्क्रीनवरून ॲप्स लपवा.
• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षिता पॅच (नोव्हें 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini membolehkan anda menyembunyikan ikon Skrin utama dan menyediakan Pengezuman Tak Hilang 3x pada Kamera. Kembar Aplikasi menyokong lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga. Keluaran ini juga mengoptimumkan kesan penangkapan dalam beberapa senario dan memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Anda disyorkan agar mengemas kini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera membolehkan anda menggunakan Pengezuman Tak Hilang 3x. 
• Optimumkan kesan penangkapan dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kembar Aplikasi">
<feature>• Kembar Aplikasi menyokong lebih banyak aplikasi pihak ketiga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>• Anda kini boleh menyembunyikan ikon Skrin utama. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Keselamatan dan privasi > Perlindungan peranti dan data > Sembunyikan aplikasi daripada Skrin utama. 
• Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Nov 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ဖြင့် သင်သည် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်သည်၊ ကင်မရာဖြင့် မူရင်းမပျက် 3x ဆ ဇူးမ်ချုံ့၊ ချဲ့နိုင်သည်။ အက်ပ် အမြွှာသည် နောက်ထပ် ပြင်အဖွဲ့အစည်း အက်ပ်များကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။ ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ရိုက်ကူးမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကိုလည်း အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင်မရာ">
<feature>• ကင်မရာသည် မူရင်းမပျက် 3x ဆ ဇူးမ်ချုံ့၊ ချဲ့ပေးနိုင်သည်။
• အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ရိုက်ကူးမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက်ပ် အမြွှာ">
<feature>• အက်ပ် အမြွှာသည် နောက်ထပ် ပြင်ပအဖွဲ့အစည်း အက်ပ်များကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>• ယခုအခါ ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ အိုင်ကွန်များကို ဝှက်နိုင်ပါပြီ။ ဖော်ပြပါသို့သွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > လုံခြုံရေးနှင့် ကိုယ်ပိုင် အချက်အလက် > စက်နှင့် ဒေတာ ကာကွယ်ရေး > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်မှ အက်ပ်များကို ဝှက်ရန်။
• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (နိုဝင်ဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေးအပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း အချက်အလက်များ ပိုမိုသိရှိလိုပါက ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဖော်ပြပါဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ျဖင့္ သင္သည္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္သည္၊ ကင္မရာျဖင့္ မူရင္းမပ်က္ 3x ဆ ဇူးမ္ခ်ဳံ႕၊ ခ်ဲ႕ႏိုင္သည္။ အက္ပ္ အျမႊာသည္ ေနာက္ထပ္ ျပင္အဖြဲ႕အစည္း အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ႐ိုက္ကူးမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကိုလည္း အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင္မရာ">
<feature>• ကင္မရာသည္ မူရင္းမပ်က္ 3x ဆ ဇူးမ္ခ်ဳံ႕၊ ခ်ဲ႕ေပးႏိုင္သည္။
• အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ႐ိုက္ကူးမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက္ပ္ အျမႊာ">
<feature>• အက္ပ္ အျမႊာသည္ ေနာက္ထပ္ ျပင္ပအဖြဲ႕အစည္း အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>• ယခုအခါ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔သြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > လုံၿခဳံေရးႏွင့္ ကိုယ္ပိုင္ အခ်က္အလက္ > စက္ႏွင့္ ေဒတာ ကာကြယ္ေရး > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္မွ အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဝွက္ရန္။
• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ႏိုဝင္ဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရးအပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း အခ်က္အလက္မ်ား ပိုမိုသိရွိလိုပါက ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ေဖာ္ျပပါဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne oppdateringen gjør at du kan skjule Startskjerm-ikonene og gir 3x lossless zooming til kameraet. Tvillingapp støtter flere tredjepartsapper. Denne utgivelsen optimerer også opptakseffekten i noen scenarioer, og den integrerer en sikkerhetsoppdatering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera gjør at du kan bruke 3x lossless zooming.
• Optimerer opptakseffekten i noen scenarioer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tvillingapp">
<feature>• Tvillingapp støtter flere tredjepartsapper.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Du kan nå skjule startskjermikonene. Prøv dette ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Sikkerhet og personvern > Enhets- og databeskyttelse > Skjul apper på startskjermen.
• Android sikkerhetsoppdatering (nov. 2024) har blitt integrert for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om HONOR Sikkerhet-oppdateringer, se vårt nettsted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ताहरू, तपाईं यो अपडेटका सहायताले गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन सक्नुहुन्छ र गुणस्तर नगुमाइकनै क्यामेरामा 3 गुणा जुम गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । एप ट्विनमा थप तेस्रो-पक्ष एपहरू प्रयोग गर्न मिल्छ । यो रिलिजले केही परिदृश्यमा सुटिङको प्रभाव पनि अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ । अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="क्यामेरा">
<feature>• तपाईं गुणस्तर नगुमाइकनै क्यामेरामा 3 गुणा जुम गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । 
• यसले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा सुटिङको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एप ट्विन">
<feature>• एप ट्विनमा थप तेस्रो-पक्ष एपहरू प्रयोग गर्न मिल्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• तपाईं अब गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू लुकाउन सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सुरक्षा तथा गोपनीयता > यन्त्र तथा डाटाको सुरक्षा > गृह स्क्रिनबाट एपहरू लुकाउनुहोस् । 
• एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (नोभेम्बर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruikers, met deze update kunt u pictogrammen op het Startscherm verbergen en deze update brengt 3x Lossless Zooming naar de Camera. App-tweeling ondersteunt meer apps van derden. Deze release optimaliseert ook het opname-effect in bepaalde scenario's en bevat een beveiligingspatch. Het wordt aanbevolen om bij te werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>• Camera stelt u in staat om 3x Lossless Zooming te gebruiken.
• Optimaliseert het opname-effect in bepaalde scenario's.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-tweeling">
<feature>• App-tweeling ondersteunt meer apps van derden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>• U kunt nu Startschermpictogrammen verbergen. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Beveiliging en privacy > Apparaat en gegevensbescherming > Apps verbergen van Startscherm.
• Android-beveiligingspatch (november 2024) is opgenomen voor de systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ ଲୁଚାଇବାକୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ, ଏବଂ କ୍ୟାମେରାରେ 3x ବିନାହାନୀ ବିଶିଷ୍ଟ ଜୁମିଂ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଆପ୍‌ ଟ୍ୱିନ୍‌ ଆହୁରି ଅଧିକ ତୃତୀୟ-ପକ୍ଷ ଆପସ୍‌କୁ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ। ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍‌ କିଛି କ୍ଷେତ୍ରରେ ଶୁଟିଂ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
<feature>• କ୍ୟାମେରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ପାଇଁ 3x ବିନାହାନୀ ବିଶିଷ୍ଟ ଜୁମିଂ ସକ୍ଷମ କରାଏ।
• କେତେକ ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଶୁଟିଂ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଆପ୍ ଟ୍ୱିନ୍">
<feature>• ଆପ୍‌ ଟ୍ୱିନ୍‌ ଆହୁରି ଅଧିକ ତୃତୀୟ-ପକ୍ଷ ଆପସ୍‌କୁ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>• ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ଆପଣ ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ ଲୁଚାଇ ପାରିବେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଓ ଗୋପନୀୟତା > ଡିଭାଇସ୍ ଏବଂ ଡାଟା ସୁରକ୍ଷା > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ରୁ ଆପସ୍ ଲୁଚାନ୍ତୁ।
• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ନଭେମ୍ବର 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾਉਣ ਦੀ ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਦਿੱਤੀ ਗਈ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਕੈਮਰੇ ਵਿੱਚ 3x ਲੂਜ਼ਲੈੱਸ ਜ਼ੂਮਿੰਗ ਨੂੰ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਜੋੜੇਦਾਰ ਐਪ ਹੋਰ ਤੀਜੀ ਧਿਰ ਦੀਆਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਦ੍ਰਿਸ਼ਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
<feature>• ਕੈਮਰਾ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ 3x ਲੂਜ਼ਲੈੱਸ ਜ਼ੂਮਿੰਗ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਨ ਦੇ ਯੋਗ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ।
• ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਜੋੜੇਦਾਰ ਐਪ">
<feature>• ਜੋੜੇਦਾਰ ਐਪ ਹੋਰ ਤੀਜੀ ਧਿਰ ਦੀਆਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਹੁਣ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਲੁਕਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅਤੇ ਪਰਦੇਦਾਰੀ > ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਅਤੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਤੋਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਲੁਕਾਓ।
• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਨਵੰਬਰ 2024) ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਵਾਸਤੇ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja umożliwia ukrywanie ikon ekranu głównego i wprowadza 3-krotny bezstratny zoom w aparacie. Aplikacja bliźniacza obsługuje więcej aplikacji innych firm. Ta wersja optymalizuje również efekt działania aparatu w niektórych sytuacjach i zawiera poprawkę bezpieczeństwa. Zaleca się instalację tej aktualizacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aparat">
<feature>• Aparat umożliwia korzystanie z 3-krotnego bezstratnego zoomu.
• Zoptymalizowano efekt działania aparatu w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacja bliźniacza">
<feature>• Aplikacja bliźniacza obsługuje więcej aplikacji innych firm.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>• Można już ukrywać ikony ekranu głównego. Aby wypróbować tę funkcję, wybierz Ustawienia > Bezpieczeństwo i prywatność > Ochrona danych i urządzenia > Ukryj aplikacje na Ekranie głównym.
• Poprawka zabezpieczeń systemu Android (listopad 2024) została dodana w celu zapewnienia bezpieczeństwa systemu. Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń HONOR można uzyskać na stronie internetowej https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezados(as) usuários(as), essa atualização permite que você oculte os ícones da tela inicial e traz Zoom de 3x sem perdas para a Câmera. O Aplicativo gêmeo oferece suporte a mais aplicativos de terceiros. Essa versão também otimiza o efeito de captura em alguns cenários e incorpora um patch de segurança. É recomendável atualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmera">
<feature>• A Câmera permite que você use Zoom de 3x sem perdas.
• Otimiza o efeito de captura em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicativo gêmeo">
<feature>• O Aplicativo gêmeo oferece suporte a mais aplicativos de terceiros.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>• Agora você pode ocultar os ícones da Tela inicial. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Segurança e privacidade > Proteção de dados e dispositivos > Ocultar aplicativos da tela inicial.
• O patch de segurança do Android (novembro de 2024) foi incorporado para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as Atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caros utilizadores, esta atualização permite ocultar os ícones do ecrã inicial e traz o zoom 3x sem perdas para a câmara. As Aplicações clonadas suportam mais aplicações de terceiros. Esta versão também otimiza o efeito de disparo em alguns cenários e incorpora uma correção de segurança. Recomenda-se a atualização.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmara">
<feature>• A câmara permite-lhe utilizar o zoom 3x sem perdas.
• Otimiza o efeito de disparo em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicações clonadas">
<feature>• As Aplicações clonadas suportam mais aplicações de terceiros.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>• Pode agora ocultar ícones do Ecrã inicial. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Segurança e privacidade > Dispositivo e proteção de dados > Ocultar aplicações ao Ecrã inicial.
• Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (novembro de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre atualizações de Segurança HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização de uma cópia de segurança antes da atualização.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimați utilizatori, această actualizare vă permite să ascundeți pictogramele ecranului de pornire și aduce Zoom 3x fără pierderi la Camera foto. Aplicație geamănă acceptă mai multe aplicații terțe. Această versiune optimizează, de asemenea, efectul de fotografiere în anumite scenarii și încorporează o corecție de securitate. Se recomandă actualizarea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cameră foto">
<feature>• Camera foto vă permite să folosiți Zoom 3x fără pierderi.
• Optimizează efectul de fotografiere în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicație geamănă">
<feature>• Aplicație geamănă acceptă acum mai multe aplicații terțe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Acum puteți ascunde pictogramele Ecranului de pornire. Încercați-o accesând la: Setări > Siguranță și confidențialitate > Protecția dispozitivului și a datelor > Ascundere aplicații din Ecranul de pornire.
• Corecția de securitate Android (noiembrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de Securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu vă va afecta datele personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемые пользователи! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы добавить возможность скрытия значков на рабочем экране и внедрить зум 3x без потери качества для «Камеры». Приложение-клон теперь поддерживает больше сторонних приложений. В этом выпуске также оптимизирована съемка для некоторых сценариев и внедрено исправление безопасности. Рекомендуем установить это обновление.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• Теперь «Камера» поддерживает зум 3x без потери качества.
• Оптимизирована съемка для некоторых сценариев.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Приложение-клон">
<feature>• Приложение-клон теперь поддерживает больше сторонних приложений.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>• Теперь вы можете скрыть значки на рабочем экране. Для этого выберите «Настройки > Безопасность и конфиденциальность > Защита устройства и данных > Скрыть значки приложений на рабочем экране».
• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (ноябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලකයිනි, මෙම යාවත්කාලය මගින් ඔබට මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවීමට ඉඩ දෙන අතර, කැමරාවට 3x ව්‍යය රහිත විශාලනය ගෙන එයි. යෙදුම් නිවුන් තවත් තෙවන පාර්ශ්ව යෙදුම් සඳහා සහය දක්වයි. මෙම නිකුතුව සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී රූගත කිරීමේ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරන අතර ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ඇතුළත් කරයි. යාවත්කාල කරන්නට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කැමරාව">
<feature>• කැමරාව ඔබට 3x ව්‍යය රහිත විශාලනය භාවිත කිරීමට හැකියාව ලබා දෙයි. 
• සමහර අවස්ථාවල රූගත කිරීමේ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="යෙදුම් නිවුන්">
<feature>• යෙදුම් නිවුන් තවත් තෙවන පාර්ශ්ව යෙදුම් සඳහා සහය දක්වයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>• ඔබට දැන් මුල් තිර අයිකන සැඟවිය හැකිවේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ආරක්ෂාව සහ රහස්‍යතාව > උපාංගය සහ දත්ත ආරක්ෂාව > මුල් තිරයෙන් යෙදුම් සඟවන්න. 
• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 නොවැ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení používatelia, táto aktualizácia umožňuje skryť ikony na domovskej obrazovke a do aplikácie Fotoaparát prináša 3-násobné bezstratové priblíženie. Paralelná aplikácia podporuje viac aplikácií tretích strán. Toto vydanie tiež optimalizuje efekt snímania v niektorých situáciách a zahŕňa bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizácia sa odporúča.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>• Fotoaparát umožňuje používať 3-násobné bezstratové priblíženie. 
• Optimalizuje efekt snímania v niektorých situáciách.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Paralelná aplikácia">
<feature>• Paralelná aplikácia podporuje viac aplikácií tretích strán.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>• Môžete skryť ikony na domovskej obrazovke. Vyskúšajte to v ponuke Nastavenia > Zabezpečenie a súkromie > Ochrana zariadenia a údajov > Skryť aplikácie na domovskej obrazovke. 
• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z novembra 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabniki, ta posodobitev omogoča skrivanje ikon na začetnem zaslonu in 3-kratno optično povečavo brez izgub za aplikacijo Kamera. Dvojnik aplikacije podpira več aplikacij drugih ponudnikov. Poleg tega ta izdaja optimizira učinke pri slikanju v nekaterih situacijah ter vključuje varnostni popravek. Priporočamo, da namestite posodobitev.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera omogoča uporabo 3-kratne optične povečave brez izgub.
• Optimizira učinke pri slikanju v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Dvojnik aplikacije">
<feature>• Dvojnik aplikacije podpira več aplikacij drugih ponudnikov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>• Zdaj lahko skrijete ikone na začetnem zaslonu. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite v razdelku Nastavitve > Varnost in zasebnost > Zaščita naprave in podatkov > Skrij aplikacije na začetnem zaslonu.
• Varnostni popravek za Android (november 2024) je vključen za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, med den här uppdateringen får du möjlighet att dölja ikoner på startsidan, och Kamera får 3x förlustfri zoomning. Tvillingapp har stöd för fler tredje parts appar. Den här utgåvan optimerar också fotograferingseffekten i vissa scenarier och implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering. Du rekommenderas att uppdatera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Med Kamera kan du använda 3x förlustfri zoomning. 
• Optimerar fotograferingseffekten i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tvillingapp">
<feature>• Tvillingapp har stöd för fler tredje parts appar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>• Du kan nu dölja ikoner på startsidan. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Säkerhet och sekretess > Enhets- och dataskydd > Dölj appar från startsidan. 
• Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (november 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerheten. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili hukuwezesha kuficha aikoni za Skrini ya mwanzo na huleta Ukuzaji wa mara 3 Usio na Hasara kwenye Kamera. Programu Pacha inaruhusu programu zaidi za wahusika wengine. Toleo hili pia huboresha athari ya upigaji picha katika baadhi ya miktadha na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama. Inapendekezwa usasishe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera hukuwezesha kutumia Ukuzaji wa mara 3 Usio na Hasara.
• Huboresha athari ya upigaji picha katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programu Pacha">
<feature>• Programu pacha inaruhusu programu zaidi za wahusika wengine.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>• Sasa unaweza kuficha aikoni za Skrini ya mwanzo. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Usalama na faragha > Ulinzi wa kifaa na data > Ficha programu kutoka kwenye Skrini ya mwanzo.
• Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Nov 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili upate maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனர்களே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்க உங்களை அனுமதிக்கிறது மற்றும் கேமராவிற்கு 3x இழப்பற்ற ஜூமிங்கைக் கொண்டு வருகிறது. இரட்டைச் செயலி மேலும் பல மூன்றாம் தரப்புச் செயலிகளை ஆதரிக்கிறது. இந்த வெளியீடு சில காட்சிகளில் ஷுட்டிங் விளைவையும் உகந்ததாக்குகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது. இதைப் புதுப்பிக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேமரா">
<feature>• கேமரா, 3x இழப்பற்ற ஜூமிங்கைப் பயன்படுத்த உங்களை அனுமதிக்கிறது.
• சில காட்சிகளில் ஷுட்டிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="இரட்டைச் செயலி">
<feature>• இரட்டைச் செயலி மேலும் பல மூன்றாம் தரப்புச் செயலிகளை ஆதரிக்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>• நீங்கள் இப்போது முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களை மறைக்கலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > பாதுகாப்பு மற்றும் தனியுரிமை > சாதனம் மற்றும் தரவுப் பாதுகாப்பு > முகப்புத் திரையிலிருந்து செயலிகளை மறைக்கவும்.
• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (நவ 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారులకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచడానికి మిమ్మల్ని అనుమతిస్తుంది మరియు కెమెరాకు 3x లాస్‌లెస్ జూమింగ్‌ను అందిస్తుంది. అప్లికేషన్ ట్విన్ మరిన్ని థర్డ్-పార్టీ అప్లికేషన్లకు సపోర్ట్ చేస్తుంది. ఈ విడుదల కొన్ని దృశ్యాలలో షూటింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని కూడా ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది మరియు సెక్యూరిటీ ప్యాచ్‌ను కలిగి ఉంటుంది. అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కెమెరా">
<feature>• 3x లాస్‌లెస్ జూమింగ్‌ను ఉపయోగించడానికి కెమెరా మిమ్మల్ని అనుమతిస్తుంది.
• కొన్ని దృశ్యాలలో షూటింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="అప్లికేషన్ ట్విన్">
<feature>•అప్లికేషన్ ట్విన్ మరిన్ని మూడవ పక్ష అప్లికేషన్‌లకు మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>మీరు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలను దాచవచ్చు. దీనిని ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > భద్రత మరియు గోప్యత > పరికరం మరియు డేటా రక్షణ > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ నుండి అప్లికేషన్‌లను దాచండి.
Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (నవం 2024) అనేది సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రతా అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้อนุญาตให้คุณซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก และให้การซูมแบบไม่สูญเสียรายละเอียด 3 เท่าแก่กล้องถ่ายรูป คู่แฝดแอปจะรองรับแอปของบุคคลที่สามได้มากขึ้น รีลีสนี้ยังปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์การถ่ายภาพในบางสถานการณ์และรวมแพตช์รักษาความปลอดภัยด้วย เราขอแนะนำให้คุณทำการอัปเดต</feature>
</features>
<features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
<feature>• กล้องถ่ายรูปให้คุณใช้การซูมแบบไม่สูญเสียรายละเอียด 3 เท่า
• ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์การถ่ายภาพในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="คู่แฝดแอป">
<feature>• คู่แฝดแอปรองรับแอปของบุคคลที่สามได้มากขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>ในตอนนี้คุณสามารถซ่อนไอคอนหน้าจอหลักได้ ทดลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ความปลอดภัยและความเป็นส่วนตัว > การป้องกันอุปกรณ์และข้อมูล > ซ่อนแอปจากหน้าจอหลัก
มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (พ.ย. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang update na ito na itago ang mga icon ng Home screen, at naghahatid ng 3x Lossless Zooming sa Camera. Sinusuportahan ng App Twin ang higit pang third-party na app. Ino-optimize din ng release na ito ang effect sa pag-shoot sa ilang sitwasyon, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>• Nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang Camera na gamitin ang 3x Lossless Zooming.
• Ino-optimize ang effect sa pag-shoot sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Twin">
<feature>• Sinusuportahan ng App Twin ang higit pang third-party na app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang magtago ng mga icon ng Home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Nob 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang update na ito na itago ang mga icon ng Home screen, at naghahatid ng 3x Lossless Zooming sa Camera. Sinusuportahan ng App Twin ang higit pang third-party na app. Ino-optimize din ng release na ito ang effect sa pag-shoot sa ilang sitwasyon, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>• Nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang Camera na gamitin ang 3x Lossless Zooming.
• Ino-optimize ang effect sa pag-shoot sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Twin">
<feature>• Sinusuportahan ng App Twin ang higit pang third-party na app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Puwede ka nang magtago ng mga icon ng Home screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa Mga Setting > Seguridad at privacy > Proteksyon ng device at data > Magtago ng mga app mula sa Home screen.
Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Nob 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcılarımız, bu güncelleme ile Başlangıç ekranı simgeleri gizlenebilir, ayrıca Kamera için 3 kat Kayıpsız Yakınlaştırma sağlar. İkiz Uygulamanın desteklediği üçüncü taraf uygulama sayısı artırılmıştır. Bu sürüm ayrıca bazı senaryolarda çekim efektini optimize eder ve bir güvenlik yaması içerir. Güncellemeniz önerilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera ile 3 kat Kayıpsız Yakınlaştırma yapabilirsiniz.
• Bazı senaryolarda çekim efektini optimize eder.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İkiz Uygulama">
<feature>• İkiz Uygulama ile daha fazla üçüncü taraf uygulaması desteklenmektedir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Artık Başlangıç ekranı simgelerini gizleyebilirsiniz. Şuraya giderek deneyin: Ayarlar > Güvenlik ve gizlilik > Cihaz ve veri koruması > Uygulamaları Başlangıç Ekranından gizleyin.
Android güvenlik yaması (Kasım 2024) sistem güvenliği için dahil edilmiştir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/11 adresinden web sitemizi ziyaret edin</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، كامېراغا ئۈچ ھەسسە ئەسلىي ھالەت بويىچە فوكۇس ئۆزگەرتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، قوشماق ئەپ تېخىمۇ كۆپ ئۈچىنچى تەرەپ ئەپلەرنى قوللايدىغان بولدى، بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى كامېرانىڭ سۈرەتكە ئېلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏‏كامېرا">
<feature>‏•  ئۈچ ھەسسە ئەسلىي ھالەت بويىچە فوكۇس ئۆزگەرتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى.
• كامېرانىڭ بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى سۈرەتكە ئېلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏قوشماق ئەپ">
<feature>‏•  ‏تېخىمۇ كۆپ ئۈچىنچى تەرەپ ئەپلىرىنى قوللايدىغان بولدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏بىخەتەرلىك">
<feature>‏•  ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > بىخەتەرلىك ۋە مەخپىيەتلىك > ئۈسكۈنە ۋە مەلۇمات قوغداش > ئەپنىڭ ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگىسىنى يوشۇرۇش.
•  ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىلى 11-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановні користувачі! Це оновлення дає змогу приховувати значки на головному екрані й забезпечує можливість 3-кратного масштабування без втрати якості в додатку "Камера". Функція "Копія додатка" тепер підтримує більше сторонніх додатків. У цьому випуску також оптимізовано ефект зйомки в деяких сценаріях і впроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки. Радимо встановити оновлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>• Додаток "Камера" дає змогу використовувати 3-кратне масштабування без втрати якості.
• Оптимізує ефект зйомки в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Копія додатка">
<feature>• Функція "Копія додатка" тепер підтримує більше сторонніх додатків.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>• Тепер ви можете приховати значки на головному екрані. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Налаштування" > "Безпека й конфіденційність" > "Захист пристрою та даних" > "Приховати додатки на головному екрані".
•Для посилення безпеки системи впроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки Android від листопада 2024 року. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارفین، یہ اپ ڈیٹ آپ کو ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کو چھپانے کی اجازت دیتی، اور کیمرے میں 3x بے ضرر زومنگ متعارف کرواتی ہے۔ جڑواں ایپس مزید فریق ثالث ایپس میں تعاون کرتی ہے۔ یہ ریلیز کچھ منظرناموں میں شوٹنگ کے اثر کو بھی بہتر بناتی ہے، اور سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کیمرہ">
<feature>‏• کیمرہ آپ کو 3x بے ضرر زومنگ استعمال کرنے کے قابل بناتا ہے۔
‏• کچھ منظرناموں میں شوٹنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="جڑواں ایپس">
<feature>‏• جڑواں ایپس مزید فریق ثالث ایپس میں تعاون کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>اب آپ ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کو پوشیدہ کر سکتے ہیں۔ اسے یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: ترتیبات > سکیورٹی اور رازداری > ڈیوائس اور ڈیٹا کی حفاظت > ہوم اسکرین سے ایپس پوشیدہ کریں۔
‏•سسٹم سکیورٹی کے لیے Android سکیورٹی پیچ (نومبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11 ملاحظہ کریں</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchilar, ushbu yangilanishda Bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitish hamda Kamera ilovasida 3x yoʻqotishsiz masshtablash imkoniyatlari taqdim etildi. Egizak ilova funksiyasi endi yanada koʻproq tashqi ilovalarni dastaklaydi. Shuningdek, ushbu nashrda ayrim holatlardagi tasvirga olish effekti optimallandi va xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi. Yangilash tavsiya etiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>• Kamera 3x yoʻqotishsiz masshtablashdan foydalanish imkonini beradi. 
• Ayrim holatlardagi tasvirga olish effekti optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Egizak ilova">
<feature>• Egizak ilova funksiyasi endi yanada koʻproq tashqi ilovalarni dastaklaydi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>• Endi Bosh ekrandagi belgilarni berkitishingiz mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Xavfsizlik va maxfiylik > Qurilma va maʼlumotlar himoyasi > Bosh ekranda ilovalarni berkitish. 
• Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, noyabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này giúp bạn ẩn các biểu tượng trên Màn hình chính và mang đến tính năng Thu phóng không mất dữ liệu 3 lần cho Máy ảnh. Tính năng Nhân bản ứng dụng hỗ trợ nhiều ứng dụng bên thứ ba hơn. Bản phát hành này cũng tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng quay/chụp trong một số trường hợp và tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Bạn nên cập nhật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Máy ảnh">
<feature>• Máy ảnh cho phép bạn sử dụng chế độ Thu phóng không mất dữ liệu 3 lần.
• Tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng quay/chụp trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nhân bản ứng dụng">
<feature>• Tính năng Nhân bản ứng dụng hỗ trợ nhiều ứng dụng bên thứ ba hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể ẩn các biểu tượng trên Màn hình chính. Hãy thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Bảo mật và quyền riêng tư > Bảo vệ thiết bị và dữ liệu > Ẩn ứng dụng khỏi Màn hình chính.
• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 11 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標功能，相機新增三倍無損變焦功能，應用程式分身支援更多第三方應用程式，優化部分場景相機拍攝效果，整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="相機">
<feature>•  新增三倍無損變焦功能。
•  優化部分場景相機拍攝效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="應用程式分身">
<feature>•  新增支援更多第三方應用程式。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  新增隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全性和私隱 > 裝置和數據保護 > 隱藏應用程式主屏幕圖標。
•  整合 Android 2024年11月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增隱藏應用程式桌面圖示功能，相機新增三倍無損變焦功能，應用程式雙開支援更多第三方應用程式，最佳化在部分場景下的相機拍攝效果，並整合安全修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="相機">
<feature>•  新增三倍無損變焦功能。
•  最佳化在部分場景下的相機拍攝效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="應用程式雙開">
<feature>•  新增支援更多第三方應用程式。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  新增隱藏應用程式桌面圖示功能，體驗路徑：設定 > 安全和隱私 > 裝置與資料保護 > 隱藏應用程式桌面圖示。
•  整合 Android 2024 年 11 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/11</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
