<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>This recommended update includes system optimizations for your device.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Center.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ ለመሳሪያዎ የስርዓት ማትቢያዎችን ያካትታል።</feature>
</features>

<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን የግል ውሂብዎን አይደመስስም፣ ነገር ግን አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ መያዝ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. በዝማኔው ወቅት ማንኛውንም ችግር ካጋጠመዎት ለHONOR አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHONOR የደንበኞች አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት እርዳታችንን ማግኘት ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>يتضمن هذا التحديث الموصى به تحسينات نظام لجهازك.</feature>
</features>

<features module="ملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. لن يؤدّي تثبيت هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ومع ذلك نوصي بإجراء النسخ الاحتياطي مسبقًا.
‏2. إذا واجهت أي مشكلات في أثناء التحديث، فيُمكنك الحصول على المساعدة من خلالنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء HONOR أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটত আপোনাৰ ডিভাইচৰ বাবে ছিষ্টেম অনুকূলিতকৰণ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত আছে।</feature>
</features>

<features module="টোকাসমূহ:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেট ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহাৰি নেপেলাব, কিন্তু তাৰ পূৰ্বে বেকআপ লোৱাটো এতিয়াও অনুমোদিত।
2. আপুনি আপডেটটোৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি HONOR সেৱাৰ হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰ দৰ্শন কৰি আমাৰ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bu tövsiyə edilən yeniləməyə cihazınız üçün sistem optimallaşdırmaları daxildir.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınızı silməyəcək, lakin yenə də əvvəlcədən ehtiyat nüsxənin yaradılması tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə üzləşsəniz, HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya HONOR Müştəri Xidməti Mərkəzinə getməklə bizdən kömək əldə edə bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Panganyaran sing disaranake iki kalebu pangoptimalan sistem kanggo piranti sampeyan.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep dhisik tetep disaranake.
2. Yen ana samubarang masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa njaluk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan HONOR utawa marani Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ovo preporučeno ažuriranje obuhvata optimizacije sistema za vaš uređaj.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ovo preporučeno ažuriranje obuhvata optimizacije sistema za vaš uređaj.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ovo preporučeno ažuriranje obuhvata optimizacije sistema za vaš uređaj.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="be-by" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне ўключае ў сябе аптымізацыю сістэмы вашай прылады.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, вы можаце патэлефанаваць на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або наведаць сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Тази препоръчана актуализация съдържа оптимизация на системата за вашето устройство.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да доведе до изтриване на личните ви данни, но все пак се препоръчва предварително архивиране.
2. Ако по време на актуализацията срещнете някакви проблеми, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на HONOR или посетите Сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি আপনার ডিভাইসের জন্য সিস্টেম অপটিমাইজেশন অন্তর্ভুক্ত করেছে।</feature>
</features>

<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে যাবে না, কিন্তু আগে থেকেই ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার সুপারিশ করা হচ্ছে৷
2. আপডেটের সময় আপনি যদি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হন, তাহলে আপনি HONOR সেবার হটলাইনে কল করে বা HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পাবেন।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>བརྩེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>

<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་ལ་དོ་སྣང་བྱ་དགོས་པའི་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ovo preporučeno ažuriranje uključuje optimizacije sistema za vaš uređaj.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja se neće izbrisati lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Aquesta actualització recomanada inclou optimitzacions del sistema per al dispositiu.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Si instal·leu aquesta actualització, les dades personals no s'esborraran, però us recomanem que en feu una còpia de seguretat.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el Centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR per rebre ajuda.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Součástí této doporučené aktualizace jsou vylepšení systému vašeho zařízení.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalací této aktualizace nevymažete svá osobní data, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na zákaznickou linku HONOR nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Denne anbefalede opdatering indeholder systemoptimeringer til din enhed.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Bemærkninger:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ved installation af opdateringen slettes dine personlige data ikke, men det anbefales alligevel at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du få vores hjælp ved at ringe til HONOR's servicehotline eller besøge HONOR's kundeservicecenter.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Diese empfohlene Aktualisierung enthält Systemoptimierungen für Ihr Gerät.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Beim Installieren dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Diese empfohlene Aktualisierung enthält Systemoptimierungen für Ihr Gerät.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Beim Installieren dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Diese empfohlene Aktualisierung enthält Systemoptimierungen für Ihr Gerät.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Beim Installieren dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση περιλαμβάνει βελτιστοποιήσεις συστήματος για τη συσκευή σας.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται να δημιουργήσετε προηγουμένως ένα αντίγραφο ασφαλείας.
2. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της HONOR ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>This recommended update includes system optimisations for your device.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Center.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta actualización recomendada incluye optimizaciones del sistema para su dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aunque la instalación de esta actualización no borrará sus datos personales, se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda llamando a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visitando el Centro de servicios de atención al cliente de HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta actualización recomendada incluye optimizaciones de sistema para su dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visitar el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>See soovitatav värskendus sisaldab süsteemioptimeerimisi teie seadmele.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid soovitatav on siiski eelnevalt varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meie abi, helistades HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või külastades HONORi teeninduskeskust.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Eguneratze gomendatu honek barne ditu zure gailuaren sistemaren optimizazioak.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzean ez dira ezabatuko datu pertsonalak, baina, hala ere, aurretik haien babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da.
2. Eguneratzea instalatu bitartean arazoren batekin topo egiten baduzu, eskatu laguntza HONOR telefonozko arreta-lineara deituta edo HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora joanda.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی توصیه‌شده شامل بهینه‌سازی‌های سیستم برای دستگاه شما است.</feature>
</features>

<features module="‏نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏۱. با نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما پاک نخواهد شد، اما کماکان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.‎
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید جهت دریافت کمک با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به «مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR» مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Tämä suositeltu päivitys sisältää järjestelmäoptimoinnit laitteellesi.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei poista henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta ne on suositeltavaa varmuuskopioida etukäteen.
2. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, voit pyytää apua soittamalla HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä HONOR-huoltoliikkeessä.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cette mise à jour recommandée comprend des optimisations du système pour votre appareil.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est toujours recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service HONOR ou vous rendre dans un Centre de services client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cette mise à jour recommandée comprend des optimisations du système pour votre appareil.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est toujours recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service HONOR ou vous rendre dans un Centre de services client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta actualización recomendada inclúe optimizacións do sistema para o seu dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ao instalar esta actualización non se eliminarán os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou visite o Centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ભલામણ કરેલી આ અપડેટમાં તમારા ઉપકરણ માટેનાં સિસ્ટમ ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝેશનનો સમાવેશ થાય છે.</feature>
</features>

<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારો વ્યક્તિગત ડેટા ભૂંસાશે નહીં, પરંતુ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>इस अनुशंसित अद्यतन में आपके डिवाइस के लिए सिस्टम अनुकूलता शामिल हैं।</feature>
</features>

<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता प्राप्त कर सकते हैं।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ovo preporučeno ažuriranje obuhvaća optimizacije sustava za vaš uređaj.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Napomena:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće izbrisati vaše osobne podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje prethodno sigurnosno kopiranje.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete HONOR servisnu otvorenu liniju ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ez a javasolt frissítés rendszeroptimalizációkat tartalmaz a készülékével kapcsolatban.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. E frissítés telepítése nem törli a személyes adatokat, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. Ha bármilyen problémába ütközik a frissítés során, kérjen tőlünk segítséget: hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati vonalát, vagy keresse fel a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati központját.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini menyertakan optimalisasi sistem untuk perangkat Anda.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Memasang pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini menyertakan optimalisasi sistem untuk perangkat Anda.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Memasang pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento consigliato include ottimizzazioni di sistema per il tuo dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non eliminerà le informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di eseguire prima un backup.
2. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento consigliato include ottimizzazioni di sistema per il tuo dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non eliminerà le informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di eseguire prima un backup.
2. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>עדכון מומלץ זה כולל מיטובי מערכת עבור ההתקן שלך.</feature>
</features>

<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך. אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי קודם לכן.
‏‏2. אם תתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="he-" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>עדכון מומלץ זה כולל מיטובי מערכת עבור ההתקן שלך.</feature>
</features>

<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך. אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי קודם לכן.
‏‏2. אם תתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>この推奨更新には、デバイスのシステムの最適化が含まれています。</feature>
</features>

<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報が消去されることはありませんが、事前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターまでお問い合わせください。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება შეიცავს თქვენი მოწყობილობისთვის სისტემის ოპტიმიზაციებს.</feature>
</features>

<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. თუ განახლების დროს რაიმე პრობლემა შეგექმნათ, ჩვენგან დახმარების მისაღებად შეგიძლიათ დარეკოთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიოთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Бұл ұсынылған жаңарту құрылғыңызға арналған жүйелік оңтайландырулардан тұрады.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнатсаңыз, жеке деректер өшпейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​ដែលបានណែនាំនេះ​រួមបញ្ចូល​ការធ្វើឱ្យប្រព័ន្ធ​ប្រសើរឡើង​សម្រាប់​ឧបករណ៍​របស់អ្នក។</feature>
</features>

<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើ​អ្នក​ជួបប្រទះបញ្ហា​ណាមួយ​ក្នុងអំឡុង​ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ អ្នកអាច​ទទួល​ជំនួយ​របស់យើង​បាន​ដោយ​ហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័ស​សេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬ​ទៅកាន់​មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR។</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಾಧನಕ್ಕೆ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಜೇಶನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಂಡಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>

<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‌ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ನೀವು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>이 권장 업데이트에는 장치에 대한 시스템 최적화가 포함되어 있습니다.</feature>
</features>

<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터는 지워지지 않지만 미리 백업하는 것이 바람직합니다.
2. 업데이트 과정에서 문제가 발생하는 경우 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 지원을 받을 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ການອັບເດດທີ່ແນະນຳນີ້ລວມມີການປັບລະບົບໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມສຳລັບອຸປະກອນຂອງທ່ານ.</feature>
</features>

<features module="ໝາຍເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການຕິດຕັ້ງການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາກໍຍັງຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ທ່ານສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Įdiegus šį rekomenduojamą naujinį, optimizuojama įrenginio sistema.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegus šį naujinį jūsų asmeniniai duomenys nebus ištrinti, tačiau prieš tai vis tiek rekomenduojame sukurti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei atnaujinimo metu iškils problemų, galite kreiptis pagalbos paskambindami HONOR aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba apsilankykite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centre.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Šajā ieteicamajā atjauninājumā ir ietverti jūsu ierīces sistēmas optimizācijas risinājumi.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Instalējot šo atjauninājumu, jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz HONOR klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot HONOR klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>एहि अनुशंसित अपडेट मे अहांक डिवाइसक लेल सिस्टम अनुकूलन सम्मिलित अछि।</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोटस:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहि मेटायत, मुदा तैयो पहिने सँ एकटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जा कए अहाँ हमरासभ सँ मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kei roto i tēnei whakahōu kua tūtohua ko ngā arotautanga pūnaha mō tō pūrere.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ki te tāutahia tēnei whakahōu kāore e mukua ō raraunga whaiaro, engari e tūtohua ana kia pūruatia i mua.
2. Mēnā ka pā he raruraru i te wā whakahōu, ka taea e koe e ā mātou āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga a HONOR, te haere rānei ki te Pokapū Ratonga Kiritaki a HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ова препорачано ажурирање опфаќа оптимизации на системот за вашиот уред.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува претходно правење резервна копија.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посета на Центарот за услуги за корисници на HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ശുപാർശചെയ്യുന്ന ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ ഉപകരണത്തിനുള്ള സിസ്റ്റം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസേഷനുകൾ ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു.</feature>
</features>

<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Санал болгож буй энэхүү шинэчлэлтэд таны төхөөрөмжийн системийн оновчлол багтсан.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад аливаа асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR Хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авна уу.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>या शिफारस केलेल्या अद्यतनात आपल्या उपकरणासाठी सिस्टम ऑप्टिमायझेशन्स समाविष्ट आहे.</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटणार नाही, परंतु आधी बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्राला भेट देऊन आमची मदत मिळवू शकता.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kemas kini yang disyorkan ini menyertakan pengoptimuman sistem untuk peranti anda.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pemasangan kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa melakukan kemas kini ini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan daripada kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan HONOR atau melawati Pusat Khidmat Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ဤအကြံပြုထားသော အပ်ဒိတ်တွင် သင့်စက်အတွက် စနစ် အကောင်းဆုံးမြှင့်တင်မှုများ ပါဝင်သည်။</feature>
</features>

<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ပျက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်စဉ်အတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်စုံတစ်ရာ ကြုံရပါက HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းကို ဖုန်းခေါ်ဆို၍ဖြစ်စေ၊ HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွား၍ဖြစ်စေ ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူနိုင်ပါသည်။</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ဤအႀကံျပဳထားေသာ အပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ သင့္စက္အတြက္ စနစ္ အေကာင္းဆုံးျမႇင့္တင္မႈမ်ား ပါဝင္သည္။</feature>
</features>

<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ပ်က္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္စဥ္အတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္စုံတစ္ရာ ႀကဳံရပါက HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းကို ဖုန္းေခၚဆို၍ျဖစ္ေစ၊ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြား၍ျဖစ္ေစ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူႏိုင္ပါသည္။</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Denne anbefalte oppdateringen inkluderer systemoptimeringer til enheten din.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp av oss ved å ringe til HONOR-kundeservice eller besøke et HONOR-kundeservicesenter.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>यो सिफारिस गरिएको अद्यावधिकमा तपाईंको यन्त्रका लागि प्रणाली अप्टिमाइजेसनहरू समावेश हुन्छन् ।</feature>
</features>

<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अद्यावधिक स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेट्ने छैन तर पहिले नै डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न अझै पनि सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. तपाईंले अद्यावधिको अवधिमा कुनै पनि समस्या सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Deze aanbevolen update omvat systeemoptimalisaties voor uw apparaat.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Het installeren van deze update zal uw persoonlijke gegevens niet wissen, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u tijdens de update problemen ondervindt, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door te bellen met de HONOR-servicehotline of een bezoek te brengen aan een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ଏହି ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ ପାଇଁ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜେସନ୍‌ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୂକ୍ତ କରେ।</feature>
</features>

<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟାକୁ ଲିଭାଇବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ତଥାପି ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରାଯିବା ବେଳେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਲਈ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਅਨੁਕੂਲਣ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹਨ।</feature>
</features>

<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਨਹੀਂ ਮਿਟੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja obejmuje optymalizacje systemu dla Twojego urządzenia.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika. Zalecamy jednak uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, można uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta atualização recomendada inclui otimizações do sistema para o seu dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter ajuda ligando para a linha de atendimento da HONOR ou visitando a Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente da HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta atualização recomendada inclui otimizações do sistema para o seu dispositivo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não irá eliminar os seus dados pessoais, mas recomendamos que crie uma cópia de segurança previamente.
2. Se encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda telefonando para a linha direta do serviço de assistência da HONOR ou visitando o Centro de Serviços ao Cliente da HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Această actualizare recomandată include optimizări ale sistemului pentru dispozitivul dvs.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu vă va șterge datele personale, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă în prealabil.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți obține ajutorul nostru sunând la linia de asistență telefonică HONOR sau vizitând Centrul de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Это рекомендуемое обновление предназначено для оптимизации работы системы на вашем устройстве.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы рекомендуем сделать резервную копию всех важных данных, прежде чем приступить к установке.
2. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или в сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලයට ඔබගේ උපාංගය සඳහා පද්ධති ප්‍රශස්තකරණ ඇතුළත් වේ.</feature>
</features>

<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකිය.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Táto odporúčaná aktualizácia obsahuje optimalizácie systému pre vaše zariadenie.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie nevymaže osobné údaje, no odporúčame pred ňou vykonať zálohu.
2. Ak sa v priebehu aktualizácie vyskytne akýkoľvek problém, môžete získať pomoc zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo navštívte zákaznícke servisné stredisko spoločnosti HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta priporočena posodobitev vključuje sistemske optimizacije za napravo.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo izbrisala vaših osebnih podatkov, vendar priporočamo, da jih predhodno varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem naletite na težave, za pomoč pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Den här rekommenderade uppdateringar inkluderar systemoptimeringar för din enhet.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar uppdateringen.
2. Om du stöter på problem under uppdateringen kan du få hjälp från oss genom att ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs kundtjänstcenter.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linajumuisha maboresho ya mfumo ya kifaa chako.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado hifadhi rudufu inapendekezwa kabla ya kusakinisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au kutembelea Kituo cha Huduma kwa Wateja cha HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்பட்ட புதுப்பிப்பில் உங்கள் சாதனத்திற்கான சிஸ்டம் புதுப்பிப்புகளும் அடங்கும்.</feature>
</features>

<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్‌లో మీ పరికరం కోసం సిస్టమ్ ఆప్టిమైజేషన్‌లు ఉంటాయి.</feature>
</features>

<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ఎరేజ్ చేయబడదు, కాని ముందుగానే బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైనట్లయితే, మీరు HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి సందర్శించి మా సహాయాన్ని పొందవచ్చు.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>การอัปเดตที่แนะนำนี้รวมถึงการเพิ่มประสิทธิภาพของระบบสำหรับอุปกรณ์ของคุณ</feature>
</features>

<features module="หมายเหตุ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลล่วงหน้า
2. หากคุณประสบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถขอรับความช่วยเหลือจากเราได้โดยโทรไปที่สายด่วนบริการ HONOR หรือเข้าไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้า HONOR</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kasama sa inirerekomendang update na ito ang mga pag-optimize ng system para sa iyong device.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, puwede mong makuha ang aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kasama sa inirerekomendang update na ito ang mga pag-optimize ng system para sa iyong device.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, puwede mong makuha ang aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Tavsiye edilen bu güncelleme cihazınız için sistem optimizasyonları içermektedir.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorun yaşamanız durumunda HONOR servis yardım hattını arayarak veya HONOR Müşteri Servisi Merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېما ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>

<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىشقا تېگىشلىك ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
‏2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Це рекомендоване оновлення включає оптимізації системи для вашого пристрою.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Якщо встановити це оновлення, ваші особисті дані не буде стерто. Утім однаково радимо заздалегідь створити їх резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію HONOR або відвідайте сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>اس تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ میں آپ کی ڈیوائس کے لئے سسٹم کی احسن کاریاں شامل ہیں۔</feature>
</features>

<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1۔ اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹے گا، لیکن پھر بھی پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو آپ HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں۔</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bu tavsiya etilgan yangilanish qurilmangiz uchun tizim optimizatsiyalarini oʻz ichiga oladi.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish oʻrnatilsa shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringiz oʻchib ketmaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, bizdan HONOR mijozlarga xizmat tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki HONOR Mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bản cập nhật được đề xuất này bao gồm các nội dung tối ưu hóa hệ thống cho thiết bị của bạn.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Lưu ý:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị xóa. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu trước.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến Trung tâm Dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要優化了系統，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化處理，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>

<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features></language>

</root>