<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增AI 消除和面对面翻译功能，优化相机和荣耀笔记使用体验，更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【图库】">
<feature>新增AI 消除功能，智能消除照片中的路人、杂物等，一键拯救废片，体验路径：图库>图片>编辑>AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面对面翻译】">
<feature>支持轮流对话场景下，中文、英语、法语、德语、西班牙语、意大利语、俄语、土耳其语、马来西亚语、阿拉伯语之间的互译。支持语音和文本输入，以及翻译结果播报，体验路径：设置>智慧助手>面对面翻译。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相机】">
<feature>人像模式支持全新雅顾风格。
支持双击电源键快速启动相机。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【荣耀笔记】">
<feature>新增录音、语音转文本和录音实时翻译功能。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，从“仅充电”切换至“传输照片”或“传输文件 / Android Auto”模式时，弹出验证界面或安全提示，让您的数据传输更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年8月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update brings new features, including AI Eraser and Face-to-face translation. Additionally, user authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. This release also optimizes Camera and the user experience of HONOR Notes. Moreover, a security patch is incorporated.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>The new AI Eraser can help you intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images with a single tap. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select a photo > Edit > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face Translation">
<feature>In a turn-taking situation, it can provide mutual translation between Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, and Arabic. It also supports voice and text input, as well as translation broadcast. You can try it out by going to: Settings > Assistant > Face-to-face Translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Harcourt style is included in Portrait mode.
You can double-press the power button to quickly access the camera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes can help you with recording, voice-to-text, and real-time translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files/Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android security patch (Aug 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ ኤአይ መደምሰሻን እና የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉምን ጨምሮ አዳዲስ ባህሪያትን ያመጣል። በተጨማሪም የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ይህ ልቀት ካሜራን እና የHONOR ማስታወሻዎች የተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮንም ያሻሽላል። በተጨማሪም የደህንነት መጠገኛ ተካቷል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል">
<feature>አዲሱ ኤአይ መደምሰሻ መንገደኞችን እና ሌሎች አላስፈላጊ ነገሮችን በአንድ ጊዜ መታ በማድረግ ከምስሎች ላይ በብልህነት እንዲያስወግዱ ይረዳዎታል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል > ፎቶ ይምረጡ > አርትዕ > ኤአይ መደምሰሻ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉም">
<feature>በተለዋዋጭ-ተራ ሁኔታ፣ በቻይንኛ፣ እንግሊዝኛ፣ ፈረንሳይኛ፣ ጀርመንኛ፣ ስፔንኛ፣ ጣልያንኛ፣ ሩሲያኛ፣ ቱርክኛ፣ ማላይኛ እና አረብኛ መካከል የጋራ ትርጉም መስጠት ይችላል። እንዲሁም የድምጽ እና የጽሑፍ ግብዓትን እንዲሁም የትርጉም ስርጭትን ይደግፋል። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ሊሞክሩት ይችላሉ፦ ቅንብሮች > ረዳት > የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉም።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ካሜራ">
<feature>የሃርኮርት ዘይቤ በፖርትሬት ሁነታ ውስጥ ተካትቷል።
ካሜራውን በፍጥነት ለመድረስ የኃይል ቁልፉን ሁለቴ መጫን ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ማስታወሻዎች">
<feature>HONOR ማስታወሻዎች በመቅዳት፣ ከድምጽ-ወደ-ጽሑፍ እና በእውነተኛ ጊዜ ትርጉም ሊረዳዎት ይችላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ የውሂብ ማስተላለፍን የሚያረጋግጥ ኃይል መሙላት ብቻ የሚለውን አጥፍተው ፎቶዎችን አስተላልፍ ወይም ፋይሎችን አስተላልፍ / Android Autoን ሲመርጡ የማረጋገጫ ወይም የደህንነት ጥያቄ ይመጣል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ኦገ 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يقدم هذا التحديث الموصى به ميزات جديدة، بما فيها الممحاة الذكية والترجمة وجهًا لوجه. علاوةً على ذلك، يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB. ويحسّن هذا الإصدار أيضًا الكاميرا وتجربة المستخدم في الملاحظات من HONOR. علاوة على ذلك، تم تضمين تصحيح أمان.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المعرض">
<feature>بإمكان أداة الممحاة الذكية الجديدة أن تساعدك على إزالة المارة والعناصر غير المرغوب فيها الأخرى من الصور بذكاء بضغطة واحدة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: المعرض > تحديد صورة > تعديل > ممحاة ذكية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ترجمة وجهًا لوجه">
<feature>في حالة تناوب الأدوار، بإمكان هذه الميزة توفير الترجمة المتبادلة بين اللغات الصينية والإنجليزية والفرنسية والألمانية والإسبانية والإيطالية والروسية والتركية والماليزية والعربية. وهي تدعم أيضًا إدخال الصوت والنص، بالإضافة إلى بث الترجمة. يمكنك تجربة هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > المساعد > ترجمة وجهًا لوجه.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الكاميرا">
<feature>تم تضمين نمط Harcourt في الوضع الرأسي.
بإمكانك الضغط مرتين على زر الطاقة للوصول إلى الكاميرا بسرعة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات من HONOR">
<feature>بإمكان الملاحظات من HONOR أن تساعدك في التسجيل وتحويل الصوت إلى نص والترجمة في الوقت الفعلي.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB. تظهر مطالبة التحقق أو الأمان عندما تحدد "نقل الصور" أو "نقل الملفات/أندرويد أوتو"، بدلاً من "الشحن فقط"، مما يضمن نقل البيانات بشكل أكثر أمانًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أغسطس 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটটোৱে AI ৰবৰ আৰু পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদক অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰি নতুন ফিচাৰসমূহ লৈ আহে। অতিৰিক্তভাৱে, USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। এই মুক্তিয়ে কেমেৰা আৰু HONOR টোকাসমূহৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতাও অনুকূলন কৰে। ইয়াৰ উপৰিও, এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গেলাৰী">
<feature>নতুন AI ৰবৰে এবাৰ টিপি প্ৰতিচ্ছবিসমূহৰ পৰা পথচাৰী আৰু অন্য অবাঞ্ছিত উপাদানবোৰ বুদ্ধিমত্তাৰে আঁতৰোৱাত আপোনাক সহায় কৰিব। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: গেলাৰী > এখন ফটো বাছনি কৰক > সম্পাদনা কৰক > AI ৰবৰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদ">
<feature>কথোপকথনৰ সময়ত ই চীনা, ইংৰাজী, ফ্ৰেন্স, জাৰ্মান, স্পেনিচ, ইটালীয়ান, ৰাছিয়ান, তুৰ্কী, মালয় আৰু আৰবীৰ মাজত পাৰস্পৰিক অনুবাদ প্ৰদান কৰিব পাৰে। ই লগতে ভইচ আৰু পাঠ ইনপুটৰ লগতে অনুবাদৰ ব্ৰডকাষ্ট সমৰ্থন কৰে। আপুনি ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাব পাৰে: ছেটিংছ > সহায়ক > পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কেমেৰা">
<feature>প'ৰ্ট্ৰেইট মোডত Harcourt শৈলী অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হয়।
আপুনি কেমেৰাটোত দ্ৰুতভাৱে প্ৰৱেশ কৰিবলৈ পাৱাৰ বুটামটো দুবাৰ দবাব পাৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR টোকাসমূহ">
<feature>HONOR টোকাসমূহে আপোনাক ৰেকৰ্ডিং, মাতৰ পৰা পাঠ আৰু প্ৰকৃত-সময়ৰ অনুবাদৰ সৈতে সহায় কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। আপুনি কেৱল চাৰ্জ কৰকৰ পৰিৱৰ্তে ফটোসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক বা ফাইলসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক/Android Auto বাছনি কৰাৰ সময়ত এটা প্ৰমাণীকৰণ বা নিৰাপত্তাৰ সংকেত দেখা পায়, যিয়ে নিৰাপদ ডাটা স্থানান্তৰ নিশ্চিত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (আগষ্ট 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə AI Pozan və Üz-üzə tərcümə də daxil olmaqla yeni xüsusiyyətlər təqdim edir. Əlavə olaraq, USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Bu buraxılış Kamera və HONOR Qeydlər istifadəçi təcrübəsini də optimallaşdırır. Bundan əlavə, təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edilib.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qalereya">
<feature>Yeni AI Pozan sizə bir toxunuşla kənardan keçənləri və digər arzuolunmaz elementləri şəkillərdən ağıllı qaydada silməyə kömək edə bilər. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Qalereya > Foto seçin > Redaktə edin > AI Pozan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Üz-üzə tərcümə">
<feature>Növbəli vəziyyətdə Çin, İngilis, Fransız, Alman, İspan, İtalyan, Rus, Türk, Malay və Ərəb dilləri arasında qarşılıqlı tərcümə təmin edə bilər. O, həmçinin səs və mətn daxiletməsini, eləcə də tərcümə yayımını dəstəkləyir. Parametrlər > Yardımçı > Üz-üzə tərcümə bölməsinə keçərək bunu sınaya bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Portret rejiminə Harcourt üslubu daxil edilib.
Kameraya cəld daxil olmaq üçün enerji düyməsinə iki dəfə basa bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Qeydlər">
<feature>HONOR Qeydlər səsyazma, səsdən mətnə və real zamanda tərcümə üzrə sizə kömək edə bilər.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Verilənlərin təhlükəsiz ötürülməsini təmin etmək üçün Yalnız doldurma əvəzinə Fotoları ötürün və ya Faylları ötürün/Android Auto seçdiyiniz zaman yoxlama və ya təhlükəsizlik sorğusu görünür.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (Avqust 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki nyuguhake sawetara fitur sing anyar, kalebu Setip AI lan Pertalan adhep-adhepan. Saliyane iku, otentikasi pangguna diwajibake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB. Rilis iki uga ngoptimalake Kamera lan pangalaman pangguna Cathetan HONOR. Saliyane iku, patch keamanan digabungake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Setip AI sing anyar bisa mbantu sampeyan mbusak wong liwat lan unsur sing ora dikarepake liyane kanthi wasis saka gambar kanthi nutul sepisan. Coba kanthi mbukak: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Setip AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pertalan Adhep-Adhepan">
<feature>Ing kahanan gantian, fitur iki bisa nyedhiyakake pertalan bebarengan antarane Basa Mandarin, Basa Inggris, Basa Prancis, Basa Jerman, Basa Spanyol, Basa Italia, Basa Rusia, Basa Turki, Basa Melayu, lan Basa Arab. Fitur iki uga ndhukung input swara lan teks, sarta giyaran pertalan. Sampeyan bisa nyoba fitur iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Assistant > Pertalan Adhep-Adhepan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Gaya Harcourt dilebokake ing mode Potret.
Sampeyan bisa menet kaping pindho tombol daya kanggo ngakses kamera kanthi cepet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan HONOR">
<feature>Cathetan HONOR bisa menehi sampeyan bantuan babagan ngrekam, swara-dadi-teks, lan pertalan ing wektu saknyatane.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Otentikasi pangguna diwajibake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB. Prentah verifikasi utawa keamanan ditampilake nalika sampeyan milih opsi Transfer foto utawa Transfer file/Android Auto, tinimbang Mung ngisi daya, saengga njamin transfer data sing luwih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch keamanan Android (Agustus 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i Simultano prevođenje. Osim toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje Kameru i korisničko iskustvo HONOR zabeleški. Takođe je uključena beznednosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Frizura je uključena u režim Portret.
Možete da dvaput pritisnete dugme za napajanje da biste brzo pristupili kameri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR zabeleške">
<feature>HONOR zabeleške mogu da vam pomognu sa snimanjem, prebacivanjem glasa u tekst i prevoda u stvarnom vremenu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Provera ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime obezbeđujete sigurniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i Simultano prevođenje. Osim toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje Kameru i korisničko iskustvo HONOR zabeleški. Takođe je uključena beznednosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Frizura je uključena u režim Portret.
Možete da dvaput pritisnete dugme za napajanje da biste brzo pristupili kameri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR zabeleške">
<feature>HONOR zabeleške mogu da vam pomognu sa snimanjem, prebacivanjem glasa u tekst i prevoda u stvarnom vremenu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Provera ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime obezbeđujete sigurniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i Simultano prevođenje. Osim toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Ovo izdanje takođe optimizuje Kameru i korisničko iskustvo HONOR zabeleški. Takođe je uključena beznednosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Frizura je uključena u režim Portret.
Možete da dvaput pritisnete dugme za napajanje da biste brzo pristupili kameri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR zabeleške">
<feature>HONOR zabeleške mogu da vam pomognu sa snimanjem, prebacivanjem glasa u tekst i prevoda u stvarnom vremenu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Potvrda identiteta korisnika je potrebna kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze. Provera ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuju kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android Auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime obezbeđujete sigurniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне ўводзіць новыя функцыі, у тым ліку Разумную гумку і Пераклад у рэальным часе. Акрамя таго, цяпер пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. У гэтай версіі аптымізавана функцыя «Камера» і выкарыстанне Нататак HONOR. Таксама гэта абнаўленне ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерэя">
<feature>Новая функцыя «Разумная гумка» выкарыстоўвае штучны інтэлект, каб вы маглі адным дотыкам выдаляць прахожых і іншыя непатрэбныя аб’екты са здымкаў. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Галерэя > Выбраць фота > Рэдагаваць > Разумная гумка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Пераклад у рэальным часе">
<feature>У сітуацыі, калі людзі размаўляюць па чарзе, гэта функцыя можа забяспечваць вусны пераклад паміж наступнымі мовамі: кітайская, англійская, французская, нямецкая, іспанская, італьянская, руская, турэцкая, малайская і арабская. Таксама яна падтрымлівае галасавы і тэкставы ўвод і галасавую трансляцыю перакладу. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Памочнік > Пераклад у рэальным часе».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>У рэжым «Партрэт» дададзены Harcourt-стыль.
Каб хутка адкрыць камеру, двойчы націсніце на кнопку ўключэння.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нататкі HONOR">
<feature>Функцыя «Нататкі HONOR» дазваляе рабіць запісы, пераўтвараць голас у тэкст і забяспечвае пераклад у рэальным часе.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Калі вы выбераце функцыю «Перадача фота» або «Перадача файлаў / Android Auto» замест функцыі «Зарадкі», з’явіцца падказка наконт праверкі або бяспекі, каб гарантаваць бяспечную перадачу даных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (жнівень 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази препоръчителна актуализация внася нови функции, включително „AI гумичка“ и „Превод лице в лице“. Освен това при превключване на целите на USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Тази версия също така оптимизира Камерата и потребителското изживяване с HONOR Бележки. Освен това е включена и корекция за сигурност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерия">
<feature>Новата „AI гумичка“ може да ви помогне да премахнете интелигентно минувачите и други нежелани елементи от изображенията с едно докосване. Изпробвайте я, като отидете на: „Галерия > Изберете снимка > Редактиране > AI гумичка“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Превод лице в лице">
<feature>В ситуация на изчакване на ред тази функция може да осигури взаимен превод между китайски, английски, френски, немски, испански, италиански, руски, турски, малайски и арабски език. Също така тя поддържа гласово и текстово въвеждане, както и излъчване на превод. Можете да я изпробвате, като отидете на „Настройки > Асистент > Превод лице в лице“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Стилът „Harcourt“ е включен в режим „Портрет“.
Можете да натиснете двукратно бутона за захранването, за да получите бърз достъп до Камерата.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Бележки">
<feature>HONOR Бележки може да ви помогне със запис, преобразуване на глас в текст и превод в реално време.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При превключване на целите на USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Когато изберете „Прехвърляне на снимки“ или „Прехвърляне на файлове/Android Auto“, вместо „Само зареждане“, се появява подкана за проверка или за сигурност, което гарантира по-безопасен трансфер на данни.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Защита">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (август 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивирането им преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি AI ইরেজার এবং মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ সহ নতুন বৈশিষ্ট্য নিয়ে এসেছে। এছাড়াও, USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুইচ করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। এই রিলিজটি ক্যামেরা এবং HONOR নোট-এর ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতাকেও অপটিমাইজ করে। তাছাড়া, একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গ্যালারি">
<feature>নতুন AI ইরেজার আপনাকে বুদ্ধিমত্তার সাথে একবার মাত্র ট্যাপ করে ছবি থেকে পথচারীদের এবং অন্যান্য অবাঞ্ছিত উপাদানগুলি সরিয়ে দিতে সাহায্য করতে পারে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: গ্যালারি > একটি ফটো নির্বাচন করুন > সম্পাদনা করুন > AI ইরেজার।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ">
<feature>পালাক্রমে কথোপকথনের পরিস্থিতিতে, এটি চীনা, ইংরেজি, ফরাসি, জার্মান, স্পেনীয়, ইতালীয়, রাশিয়ান, তুর্কি, মালয় এবং আরবি ভাষার মধ্যে পারস্পরিক অনুবাদ প্রদান করতে পারে। এটি ভয়েস এবং টেক্সট ইনপুটের পাশাপাশি অনুবাদ সম্প্রচারকেও সমর্থন করে। আপনি এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখতে পারেন: সেটিংস > সহকারী > মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ক্যামেরা">
<feature>হারকোর্ট স্টাইল পোর্ট্রেট মোডে অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে।
ক্যামেরাটি দ্রুত অ্যাক্সেস করতে আপনি পাওয়ার বোতামটি দুবার চাপতে পারেন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR নোট">
<feature>HONOR নোট আপনাকে রেকর্ডিং, ভয়েস-টু-টেক্সট এবং রিয়েল-টাইম অনুবাদে সাহায্য করতে পারে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুকরার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। আপনি যখন শুধুমাত্র চার্জ-এর পরিবর্তে ফটোগুলি ট্রান্সফার করুন বা ফাইলগুলি স্থানান্তর করুন / Android অটো নির্বাচন করেন তখন একটি যাচাইকরণ বা নিরাপত্তা প্রম্পট দেখতে পাওয়া যায়, যা নিরাপদ ডেটা স্থানান্তর নিশ্চিত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (আগস্ট 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་དུ་ AI གསུབ་འདོར་དང་གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། པར་ཆས་དང་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཟིན་བྲིས་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་མཛོད།】">
<feature>AI གསུབ་འདོར་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། རིག་ལྡན་གྱིས་འདྲ་པར་ཁྲོད་ཀྱི་ལམ་འགྲོ་བ་དང་ཅ་ལག་སྣ་ཚོགས་སོགས་གསུབ་འདོར་བྱས་ནས། མཐེབ་གཅིག་གིས་འདྲ་པར་ཇེ་ལེགས་གཏོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། པར་མཛོད་ནས་པར་རིས། དེ་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག AI གསུབ་འདོར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར།】">
<feature>རེས་མོས་སུ་ཁ་བརྡ་བྱེད་པའི་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་སུ། རྒྱ་ཡིག་དང་དབྱིན་ཡིག ཧྥ་རན་སེའི་སྐད། འཇར་མན་གྱི་སྐད། སི་ཕེན་གྱི་སྐད། དབྱི་ཐ་ལིའི་སྐད། ཨུ་རུ་སུའི་སྐད། ཐུར་ཁེའི་སྐད། མ་ལེ་ཞི་ཡའི་སྐད། ཨ་རབ་སྐད་བཅས་བར་ཕན་ཚུན་སྒྱུར་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྐད་གདངས་དང་ཡིག་གཞི་ནང་འཇུག ཡིག་སྒྱུར་མཇུག་འབྲས་སྒྲོག་གཏོང་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རིག་ལྡན་ལག་རོགས། དེ་ནས་གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་ཆས།】">
<feature>མི་གཟུགས་རྣམ་པས་ཡ་ཀུའུ་ཁྱད་ཆོས་གསར་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།
གློག་ཁུངས་མཐེབ་ལ་ཉིས་རྡེབ་བྱས་ནས་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་པར་ཆས་འགོ་སློང་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རུང་ཡོའོ་ཟིན་བྲིས།】">
<feature>སྒྲ་ཕབ་དང་སྐད་གདངས་ཡིག་གཞིར་སྒྱུར་བ། སྒྲ་ཕབ་དུས་དངོས་སུ་ཡིག་སྒྱུར་བཅས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ལག་ཁྱེར་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད། གློག་གསོག་པ་ཁོ་ན་ནས་འདྲ་པར་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ཡང་ན་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་། / Android Auto རྣམ་པ་རུ་བརྗེ་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྐབས། ར་སྤྲོད་མཚམས་ངོས་འཕར་བའམ་ཡང་ན་བདེ་འཇགས་དྲན་སྐུལ་བྱས་ནས། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་བརྒྱུད་སྐུར་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་ 8 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་བསྡེབས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་ཇེ་བཟང་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje uvodi nove funkcije, uključujući AI brisač i Direktan prijevod. Osim toga, prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze je obavezna provjera autentičnosti korisnika. Ovo izdanje također optimizira Fotoaparat i korisničko iskustvo s HONOR bilješkama. Nadalje, ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Novi AI brisač vam može pomoći da inteligentno uklonite prolaznike i druge neželjene elemente sa slika samo jednim dodirom. Isprobajte ga odlaskom u aplikaciju Galerija > Odaberite fotografiju > Uredi > AI brisač.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Direktan prijevod">
<feature>U situacijama kada se govornici izmjenjuju, može pružiti obostrani prijevod za kineski, engleski, francuski, njemački, španski, italijanski, ruski, turski, malajski i arapski jezik. Također podržava govorni i tekstualni unos, kao i emitiranje prijevoda. Možete ga isprobati odlaskom u Postavke > Pomoćnik > Direktan prijevod.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>U način rada Portret je uključen stil Harcourt.
Možete dvaput pritisnuti dugme za uključivanje da brzo pristupite fotoaparatu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR bilješke">
<feature>HONOR bilješke vam mogu pomoći u snimanju, pretvaranju govora u tekst i prevođenju u stvarnom vremenu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Obavezna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze. Kada odaberete opciju Prenošenje fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android automatski umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, prikazuje se upit za potvrdu ili sigurnosni upit, čime se omogućava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (aug 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada afegeix noves funcions, com ara Esborrador amb IA i Traducció directa. A més, es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan es canvia la connexió USB. Aquesta versió també optimitza la Càmera i l'experiència d'usuari d'HONOR Notes. A més, s'incorpora un pedaç de seguretat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>La nova funció Esborrador amb IA us ajuda a eliminar de manera intel·ligent els transeünts i altres elements que no voleu que apareguin de les imatges amb un sol toc. Proveu-ho des de: Galeria > Seleccioneu una foto > Editar > Esborrador amb IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducció directa">
<feature>En una situació de torns d'intervenció, proporciona traducció mútua entre xinès, anglès, francès, alemany, castellà, italià, rus, turc, malai i àrab. També és compatible amb l'entrada de veu i text, així com la reproducció de traduccions. Proveu-ho des de: Configuració > Assistent > Traducció directa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càmera">
<feature>L'estil Harcourt s'inclou en el Mode retrat.
Premeu dues vegades el botó d'engegada per accedir ràpidament a la càmera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes us pot ajudar amb la gravació, la conversió de veu a text i la traducció en temps real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan es canvia la connexió USB. Apareix una indicació de verificació o de seguretat quan seleccioneu Transferir fotos o Transferir fitxers/Android Auto, en lloc de Només carregar, per tal que la transferència de dades sigui més segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (agost del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato doporučená aktualizace přináší nové funkce, včetně AI Gumy a Osobního překladu. Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je dále vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Tato verze také optimalizuje Fotoaparát a uživatelské prostředí aplikace HONOR Poznámky. Navíc je instalována bezpečnostní oprava.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Nová funkce AI Guma vám pomůže inteligentně odstranit kolemjdoucí a další nežádoucí prvky ze snímků jediným klepnutím. Vyzkoušejte si to v nabídce: Galerie > Vybrat fotografii > Upravit > AI Guma.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Osobní překlad">
<feature>Během rozhovoru dokáže zajistit vzájemný překlad mezi čínštinou, angličtinou, francouzštinou, němčinou, španělštinou, italštinou, ruštinou, turečtinou, malajštinou a arabštinou. Podporuje také hlasový a textový vstup a vysílání překladů. Můžete si to vyzkoušet v nabídce: Nastavení > Asistent > Osobní překlad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Styl Harcourt je součástí režimu Portrét.
Chcete-li získat rychlý přístup k fotoaparátu, stiskněte dvakrát tlačítko napájení.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Poznámky">
<feature>HONOR Poznámky vám pomohou s nahráváním, převodem hlasu do textu a překladem v reálném čase.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Když vyberete možnost Přenos fotografií nebo Přenos souborů / Android Auto namísto možnosti Nabíjení, zobrazí se výzva k ověření nebo výzva zabezpečení, což zajistí bezpečnější přenos dat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (srpen 2024) pro systém Android zajišťující bezpečnost systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering bringer nye funktioner, inklusive AI-viskelæder og Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt. Derudover er brugergodkendelse påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål. Denne version optimerer også Kamera og brugeroplevelsen med HONOR Noter. Desuden er en sikkerhedsrettelse integreret.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Det nye AI-viskelæder kan på en intelligent måde hjælpe dig med at fjerne forbipasserende og andre uønskede elementer fra billeder med et enkelt tryk. Prøv det ved at gå til: Galleri > Vælg et foto > Rediger > AI-viskelæder.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt">
<feature>I en situation, hvor personer skiftes til at tale, kan det levere gensidig oversættelse mellem kinesisk, engelsk, fransk, tysk, spansk, italiensk, russisk, tyrkisk, malajisk og arabisk. Det understøtter også stemme- og tekstinput samt oversættelsestransmission. Du kan prøve det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Assistent > Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt-stil er inkluderet i tilstanden Portræt.
Du kan dobbelttrykke på tænd/sluk-knappen for at få hurtig adgang til kameraet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Noter">
<feature>HONOR Noter kan hjælpe dig med at optagelse, stemme-til-tekst og oversættelse i realtid.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål. En bekræftelses- eller sikkerhedsprompt bliver vist, når du vælger Overfør fotos eller Overfør filer / Android Auto i stedet for Oplad kun, hvilket garanterer en sikrere dataoverførsel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (aug 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. Du kan få flere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, inden du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen ein, darunter AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert auch die Kamera und das Benutzererlebnis von HONOR Notizen. Darüber hinaus ist ein Sicherheitspatch integriert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Der Harcourt-Stil ist im Porträtmodus enthalten.
Sie können die Ein-/Aus-Taste zweimal drücken, um schnell auf die Kamera zuzugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notizen">
<feature>HONOR Notizen kann Ihnen bei der Aufzeichnung, der Umwandlung von Sprache in Text und der Echtzeitübersetzung helfen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie Fotos übertragen oder Dateien Transfer / Android Auto anstelle von Nur laden auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen ein, darunter AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert auch die Kamera und das Benutzererlebnis von HONOR Notizen. Darüber hinaus ist ein Sicherheitspatch integriert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Der Harcourt-Stil ist im Porträtmodus enthalten.
Sie können die Ein-/Aus-Taste zweimal drücken, um schnell auf die Kamera zuzugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notizen">
<feature>HONOR Notizen kann Ihnen bei der Aufzeichnung, der Umwandlung von Sprache in Text und der Echtzeitübersetzung helfen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie Fotos übertragen oder Dateien Transfer / Android Auto anstelle von Nur laden auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen ein, darunter AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Diese Version optimiert auch die Kamera und das Benutzererlebnis von HONOR Notizen. Darüber hinaus ist ein Sicherheitspatch integriert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Der Harcourt-Stil ist im Porträtmodus enthalten.
Sie können die Ein-/Aus-Taste zweimal drücken, um schnell auf die Kamera zuzugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notizen">
<feature>HONOR Notizen kann Ihnen bei der Aufzeichnung, der Umwandlung von Sprache in Text und der Echtzeitübersetzung helfen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie Fotos übertragen oder Dateien Transfer / Android Auto anstelle von Nur laden auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση φέρνει νέες δυνατότητες, συμπεριλαμβανομένης της Γόμας AI και της Μετάφρασης πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο. Επιπλέον, απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB. Αυτή η έκδοση βελτιστοποιεί επίσης την Κάμερα και την εμπειρία χρήστη στις Σημειώσεις HONOR. Επιπλέον, ενσωματώθηκε μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Συλλογή">
<feature>Η νέα Γόμα AI μπορεί να σας βοηθήσει να αφαιρέσετε έξυπνα τα πρόσθετα στοιχεία και άλλα ανεπιθύμητα στοιχεία από τις εικόνες με ένα μόνο πάτημα. Δοκιμάστε τη μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Συλλογή > Επιλογή φωτογραφίας > Επεξεργασία > Γόμα AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Μετάφραση πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο">
<feature>Σε μια κατάσταση εναλλασσόμενης ακρόασης/ομιλίας, μπορεί να παρέχει αμοιβαία μετάφραση μεταξύ Κινεζικών, Αγγλικών, Γαλλικών, Γερμανικών, Ισπανικών, Ιταλικών, Ρωσικών, Τουρκικών, Μαλαισιανών και Αραβικών. Υποστηρίζει επίσης την φωνητική καταχώριση και την καταχώριση κειμένου, καθώς και τη μετάδοση μετάφρασης. Μπορείτε να τη δοκιμάσετε μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Βοηθός > Μετάφραση πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κάμερα">
<feature>Το στυλ Harcourt περιλαμβάνεται στη λειτουργία Πορτρέτο.
Μπορείτε να πατήσετε δύο φορές το κουμπί λειτουργίας για γρήγορη πρόσβαση στην κάμερα.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις HONOR">
<feature>Η εφαρμογή Σημειώσεις HONOR μπορεί να σας βοηθήσει με την ηχογράφηση, τη μετατροπή φωνής σε κείμενο και τη μετάφραση σε πραγματικό χρόνο.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB. Ένα μήνυμα επαλήθευσης ή ασφάλειας εμφανίζεται όταν επιλέγετε «Μεταφορά φωτογραφιών» ή «Μεταφορά αρχείων/Android Auto», αντί για «Μόνο φόρτιση», εξασφαλίζοντας πιο ασφαλή μεταφορά δεδομένων.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Αύγουστος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update brings new features, including AI Eraser and Face-to-face translation. Additionally, user authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. This release also optimises Camera and the user experience of HONOR Notes. Moreover, a security patch is incorporated.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>The new AI Eraser can help you intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images with a single tap. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select a photo > Edit > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face Translation">
<feature>In a turn-taking situation, it can provide mutual translation between Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, and Arabic. It also supports voice and text input, as well as translation broadcast. You can try it out by going to: Settings > Assistant > Face-to-face Translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Harcourt style is included in Portrait mode.
You can double-press the power button to quickly access the camera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes can help you with recording, voice-to-text, and real-time translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files/Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android security patch (Aug 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada implementa nuevas funcionalidades, como Goma de borrar de IA y Traducción cara a cara. Además, se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Esta versión también optimiza la cámara y la experiencia del usuario de Notas de HONOR. Además, se incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>El nuevo Goma de borrar de IA puede ayudarte a eliminar de forma inteligente los transeúntes y otros elementos no deseados de las imágenes con un solo toque. Pruébelo en: Galería > Seleccionar una foto > Editar > Goma de borrar de IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducción cara a cara">
<feature>En una situación de turnos, puede proporcionar traducción mutua entre chino, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malayo y árabe. También admite la introducción de voz y texto, así como la emisión de traducciones. Puede probarlo yendo a: Ajustes > Asistente > Traducción cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>El estilo Harcourt está incluido en el modo Retrato.
Puede pulsar dos veces el botón de encendido para acceder rápidamente a la cámara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas de HONOR">
<feature>Notas de HONOR puede ayudarle con la grabación, la conversión de voz a texto y la traducción en tiempo real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (agosto de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada implementa nuevas funcionalidades, como Goma IA y Traducción cara a cara. Además, se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Esta versión también optimiza la función Cámara y la experiencia de usuario de Notas de HONOR. Además, se incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>La nueva Goma IA puede ayudarlo a eliminar de forma inteligente a los transeúntes y otros elementos no deseados de las imágenes con solo presionar una vez. Pruébelo accediendo a: Galería > Seleccionar una foto > Editar > Goma IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducción cara a cara">
<feature>En una situación por turnos, puede proporcionar traducción mutua entre chino, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malayo y árabe. También admite la entrada de voz y texto, así como la transmisión de traducción. Puede probarlo accediendo a: Ajustes > Asistente > Traducción cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>El estilo Harcourt está incluido en el modo Retrato.
Puede presionar dos veces el botón de encendido para acceder rápidamente a la cámara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas de HONOR">
<feature>Notas de HONOR puede ayudarlo con la grabación, la conversión de voz a texto y la traducción en tiempo real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (agosto de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus lisab uusi funktsioone, sh AI-kustutaja ja näost näkku tõlke. Lisaks on ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel vajalik kasutaja autentimine. See väljalase optimeerib ka kaamera ja HONORi Märkmete kasutajakogemust. Lisatud on ka turvapaik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerii">
<feature>Uus AI-kustutaja aitab juhuslikult kaadrisse jalutajad ja muu soovimatu piltidelt ühe puudutusega eemaldada. Proovige: Galerii > valige foto > Redigeeri > AI-kustutaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Näost näkku tõlge">
<feature>Vahelduvate kõnelejatega vestluses võib see tõlkida hiina, inglise, prantsuse, saksa, hispaania, itaalia, vene, türgi, malai ja araabia keelt. See toetab nii hääl- kui ka tekstsisestust ning tõlke teadustamist. Proovimiseks avage Sätted > Assistent > Näost näkku tõlge.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaamera">
<feature>Harcourti stiili saab kasutada portreerežiimis.
Kaamerale kiireks juurdepääsuks saate topeltvajutada toitenuppu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONORi Märkmed">
<feature>HONORi Märkmed saab aidata teil salvestada, hääle tekstiks transkribeerida ja reaalajas tõlkida.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>Ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. Kui valite funktsiooni Ainult laadimine asemel Fotode edastamine või Failide edastamine / Android Auto, kuvatakse kinnitus- või turvaviip, mis tagab turvalisema andmeedastuse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvalisus">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (august 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori: gomendatutako eguneratze honek AA borragoma, Aurrez aurreko itzulpena eta antzeko eginbide berriak ditu barne. Gainera, erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa beharrezkoa da USB bidez konektatzeko. Bertsio honek Kamera eta HONOR Oharren erabiltzaile-esperientzia ere optimizatzen ditu. Are gehiago, segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>AA borragoma berriari esker, modu adimendunean ezaba ditzakezu argazkietatik nahi ez dituzun pertsonak eta elementuak sakatze bakarrarekin. Hori probatzeko, joan Galeria > Hautatu argazki bat > Editatu > AA borragoma aukerara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aurrez aurreko itzulpena">
<feature>Txanda-egoeretan, elkarren arteko itzulpenak eman ditzake txineraz, ingelesez, frantsesez, alemanaz, gaztelaniaz, italieraz, errusieraz, turkieraz, malaysieraz eta arabieraz. Halaber, ahots- eta testu-sarrerak eta itzulpenen transmisioak onartzen ditu. Hori probatzeko, joan Ezarpenak > Laguntzailea > Aurrez aurreko itzulpena aukerara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt estiloa gehituta dago Erretratu moduan.
Kamera bizkor atzitzeko, sakatu bi aldiz piztu/itzali botoia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Oharrak">
<feature>HONOR Oharrak erabil ditzakezu grabaketak egiteko, ahotsa testu bihurtzeko eta denbora errealeko itzulpenak egiteko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa beharrezkoa da USB bidezko konexiora aldatzen duzunean. Egiaztapen- edo segurtasun-gonbita bat bistaratuko da Transferitu argazkiak edo Transferitu fitxategiak/Android Auto aukera hautatzen duzunean, Kargatu bakarrik aukeratu beharrean; horri esker datuok segurtasunez transferituko dira.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko abu.) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna bermatzeko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago lortzeko, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی قابلیت‌های جدیدی، ازجمله «پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» و «ترجمۀ رودررو» را ارائه می‌دهد. علاوه‌بر‌این، هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر نیاز خواهد بود. این نسخه همچنین «دوربین» و تجربه کاربر در استفاده از «یادداشت‌های HONOR» را بهینه می‌سازد. همچنین، حاوی یک وصله امنیتی است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="گالری">
<feature>‏‏قابلیت جدید «پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» می‌تواند به شما کمک کند تا رهگذران و سایر عناصر ناخواسته را فقط با یک بار ضربه زدن به‌صورت هوشمندانه از تصاویر حذف کنید. با رفتن به «گالری > انتخاب عکس > ویرایش > پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» می‌توانید آن را امتحان کنید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ترجمۀ رودررو">
<feature>در شرایط صحبت کردن به نوبت، قادر است ترجمه متقابل بین زبان‌های چینی، انگلیسی، فرانسوی، آلمانی، اسپانیایی، ایتالیایی، روسی، ترکی، مالایی و عربی را ارائه دهد. همچنین از ورودی گفتاری و نوشتاری و همچنین پخش ترجمه پشتیبانی می‌کند. با رفتن به «تنظیمات > دستیار > ترجمۀ رودررو» می‌توانید آن را امتحان کنید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="دوربین">
<feature>سبک هارکورت در حالت «پرتره» گنجانده شده است.
برای دسترسی سریع به دوربین، می‌توانید دکمه روشن/خاموش را دو بار فشار دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="یادداشت‌های HONOR">
<feature>‏‏«یادداشت‌های HONOR» می‌تواند در ضبط صدا، تبدیل گفتار به متن و ترجمه هم‌زمان به شما کمک کنند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر نیاز است. هنگامی‌که «انتقال تصاویر» یا «انتقال فایل‌ها/Android Auto» را به‌جای «فقط شارژ» انتخاب می‌کنید، یک پیام‌واره تأیید یا امنیتی ظاهر می‌شود تا داده‌های خود را با امنیت بیشتری انتقال دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (اوت ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys tarjoaa uusia ominaisuuksia, kuten AI-pyyhekumin ja Kasvotusten suoritettavan käännöksen. Lisäksi käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitännän tarkoitusta vaihdetaan. Tämä päivitys myös optimoi Kameran ja HONOR Muistiinpanojen käyttökokemuksen ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Uusi AI-pyyhekumi poistaa ohikulkijat ja muut ei-toivotut kohteet älykkäästi kuvista yhdellä napautuksella. Voit kokeilla sitä kohdassa Galleria > Valitse valokuva > Muokkaa > AI-pyyhekumi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kasvotusten suoritettava käännös">
<feature>Tarjoaa vuoropuhelun aikana molemminpuolisen käännöksen kiinan, englannin, ranskan, saksan, espanjan, italian, venäjän, turkin, malaijin ja arabian välillä. Se tukee myös ääni- ja tekstisyötettä sekä käännösten lähetystä. Voit kokeilla sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Avustaja > Kasvotusten suoritettava käännös.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt-tyyli on lisätty muotokuvatilaan.
Voit käyttää kameraa nopeasti painamalla virtapainiketta kaksi kertaa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Muistiinpanot">
<feature>HONOR Muistiinpanot tarjoaa avuksesi tallennuksen, puheen muuntamisen tekstiksi ja reaaliaikaisen käännöksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitännän tarkoitusta vaihdetaan. Kun valitset Siirrä valokuvia tai Siirrä tiedostoja / Android Auto sen sijaan, että valitsisit Vain lataus -vaihtoehdon, tarkastus- tai turvallisuuskehote avautuu, mikä varmistaa turvallisemman tiedonsiirron.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (elokuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctionnalités, dont Gomme IA et Traduction face à face. De plus, l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Cette version optimise également l'Appareil photo et l'expérience utilisateur de HONOR Notes. Par ailleurs, un patch de sécurité est intégré.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>La nouvelle Gomme IA peut vous aider à supprimer intelligemment les passants et les autres éléments indésirables des images d'un simple appui. Essayez-la en accédant à : Galerie > Sélectionner une photo > Retoucher > Gomme IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduction face à face">
<feature>Dans une situation de tour de parole, elle peut fournir une traduction mutuelle entre le chinois, l'anglais, le français, l'allemand, l'espagnol, l'italien, le russe, le turc, le malais et l'arabe. Elle prend également en charge la saisie vocale et textuelle, ainsi que la diffusion de traduction. Vous pouvez l'essayer en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Traduction face à face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Le style Harcourt est inclus dans le mode Portrait.
En appuyant deux fois sur le bouton d'alimentation, vous pouvez accéder rapidement à l'Appareil photo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes peut vous aider pour l'enregistrement, la transcription et la traduction en temps réel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (août 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctionnalités, dont Gomme IA et Traduction face à face. De plus, l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Cette version optimise également l'Appareil photo et l'expérience utilisateur de HONOR Notes. Par ailleurs, un patch de sécurité est intégré.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>La nouvelle Gomme IA peut vous aider à supprimer intelligemment les passants et les autres éléments indésirables des images d'un simple appui. Essayez-la en accédant à : Galerie > Sélectionner une photo > Retoucher > Gomme IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduction face à face">
<feature>Dans une situation de tour de parole, elle peut fournir une traduction mutuelle entre le chinois, l'anglais, le français, l'allemand, l'espagnol, l'italien, le russe, le turc, le malais et l'arabe. Elle prend également en charge la saisie vocale et textuelle, ainsi que la diffusion de traduction. Vous pouvez l'essayer en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Traduction face à face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Le style Harcourt est inclus dans le mode Portrait.
En appuyant deux fois sur le bouton d'alimentation, vous pouvez accéder rapidement à l'Appareil photo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes peut vous aider pour l'enregistrement, la transcription et la traduction en temps réel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (août 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Esta actualización recomendada inclúe novas funcións, entre as que están Goma de borrar con IA e Tradución cara a cara. Ademais, ao cambiar de conexión USB, é necesaria a autenticación de usuario. Esta actualización tamén optimiza a Cámara e a experiencia do usuario de Notas de HONOR. Tamén engade un parche de seguranza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>A nova Goma de borrar con IA pode axudarlle a quitar de xeito intelixente os espontáneos e outros elementos non desexados das imaxes cun só toque. Para probala, vaia a: Galería > Seleccionar unha foto > Editar > Goma de borrar con IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradución cara a cara">
<feature>Ao falar por quendas, pode traducir conversas entre os seguintes idiomas: chinés, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malaio e árabe. Tamén é compatible con entradas de texto e voz e coa transmisión da tradución. Para probala, vaia a: Configuración > Asistente > Tradución cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Engade o estilo Harcourt no modo Retrato.
Prema dúas veces o botón de acendido para acceder rapidamente á cámara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas de HONOR">
<feature>Notas de HONOR pode axudarlle cando utilice as funcións de gravación, voz a texto e tradución en tempo real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Requírese a autenticación do usuario ao cambiar de conexión USB. Aparece unha mensaxe de verificación ou seguranza ao seleccionar Transferir fotos ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, en lugar de Só carga, o que garante unha transferencia de datos máis segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (agosto de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ AI ઇરેઝર અને સામ-સામે અનુવાદ સહિત નવી સુવિધાઓ લાવે છે. વધુમાં, USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. આ પ્રકાશન કૅમેરા અને HONOR નોંધોના વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને પણ શ્રેષ્ઠ બનાવે છે. વધુમાં, એક સુરક્ષા પેચ સામેલ છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગૅલેરી">
<feature>નવું AI ઇરેઝર તમને એક જ ટૅપ વડે છબીમાંથી પસાર થતા લોકો અને અન્ય અનિચ્છનીય તત્વોને બુદ્ધિપૂર્વક દૂર કરવામાં મદદ કરી શકે છે. અહીં જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: ગૅલેરી > ફોટો પસંદ કરો > સંપાદિત કરો > AI ઇરેઝર.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સામ-સામે અનુવાદ">
<feature>ટર્ન-ટેકિંગ પરિસ્થિતિમાં, તે ચાઇનીઝ, અંગ્રેજી, ફ્રેન્ચ, જર્મન, સ્પેનિશ, ઇટાલિયન, રશિયન, ટર્કિશ, મલય અને અરબી વચ્ચે પરસ્પર અનુવાદ પ્રદાન કરી શકે છે. તે વૉઇસ અને ટેક્સ્ટ ઇનપુટ તેમજ અનુવાદ પ્રસારણને પણ સમર્થન કરે છે. તમે તેને અહીં જઈને અજમાવી શકો છો: સેટિંગ્સ > સહાયક > સામ-સામે અનુવાદ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કૅમેરા">
<feature>પોર્ટ્રેટ મોડમાં હાર્કોર્ટ શૈલી શામેલ છે.
તમે કૅમેરાને ઝડપથી ઍક્સેસ કરવા માટે પાવર બટનને બે વાર દબાવી શકો છો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR નોંધો">
<feature>HONOR નોંધો તમને રેકોર્ડિંગ, વૉઇસ-ટુ-ટેક્સ્ટ અને વાસ્તવિક સમય પર અનુવાદમાં મદદ કરી શકે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. જ્યારે તમે સુરક્ષિત ડેટા ટ્રાન્સફરને સુનિશ્ચિત કરવા માટે માત્ર ચાર્જ કરોને બદલે, ફોટા ટ્રાન્સફર કરો અથવા ફાઇલો/Android આપમેળે ટ્રાન્સફર કરો પસંદ કરો ત્યારે ચકાસણી અથવા સુરક્ષા પ્રોમ્પ્ટ દેખાય છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ઑગસ્ટ 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, यह अनुशंसित अद्यतन AI इरेज़र और आमने-सामने अनुवाद सहित नई सुविधाएँ लाता है। इसके अतिरिक्त, USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। यह रिलीज़ कैमरा और HONOR नोट्स के उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव को भी अनुकूलित करता है। इसके अलावा, एक सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया गया है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>नए AI इरेज़र से आपको एक टैप में स्मार्ट तरीके से छवियों से अनावश्यक और अन्य अनचाही चीज़ों को निकालने में सहायता मिल सकती है। इसे यहाँ जाकर आज़माएँ: गैलरी > फ़ोटो चुनें > संपादित करें > AI इरेज़र।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आमने-सामने अनुवाद">
<feature>बारी-बारी से बातचीत वाली स्थिति में, इसमें चीनी, अंग्रेज़ी, फ़्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पैनिश, इतालवी, रूसी, तुर्की, मलय और अरबी के बीच पारस्परिक अनुवाद की सुविधा मिल सकती है। इसमें वॉइस और पाठ इनपुट के साथ-साथ अनुवाद प्रसारण का भी समर्थन किया जाता है। आप यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़मा सकते हैं: सेटिंग्स > सहायक > आमने-सामने अनुवाद।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>पोर्ट्रेट मोड में हरकोर्ट शैली शामिल है।
कैमरे तक तुरंत पहुँच प्राप्त करने के लिए आप पावर बटन को दो बार दबा सकते हैं।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR नोट्स">
<feature>HONOR नोट्स आपको रिकॉर्डिंग, आवाज़ से पाठ और वास्तविक समय अनुवाद में मदद कर सकते हैं।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। जब आप सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करने के लिए केवल चार्ज के बजाय फ़ोटो स्थानांतरित करें या फ़ाइल स्थानांतरित करें/Android Auto को चुनते हैं, तो एक सत्यापन या सुरक्षा संकेत दिखाई देता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अगस्त, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 पर जाएँ</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode nove značajke, uključujući AI gumicu i Prijevod licem u lice. Osim toga, potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a. Ovim izdanjem optimizira se i Fotoaparat i korisničko iskustvo upotrebe aplikacije HONOR Bilješke. Nadalje, implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova značajka AI gumica može vam pomoći jednim dodirom inteligentno ukloniti prolaznike i druge neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Galerija > Odaberi fotografiju > Uredi > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prijevod licem u lice">
<feature>U situaciji kada se govornici izmjenjuju, može svim stranama pružiti prijevod s kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, njemačkog, španjolskog, talijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Podržava i glasovni i tekstualni unos te emitiranje prijevoda. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Pomoćnik > Prijevod licem u lice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Harcourt stil uključen je u portretni način rada.
Za brzi pristup fotoaparatu dvaput pritisnite gumb za uključivanje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Bilješke">
<feature>Aplikacija HONOR Bilješke može vam pomoći sa snimanjem, pretvaranjem glasa u tekst i prijevodom u stvarnom vremenu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android Auto, umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, pojavljuje se upit za provjeru ili sigurnost, čime se osigurava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (kolovoz 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés új funkciókat vezet be, ilyen például az AI-radír és a Szinkrontolmácsolás. Ezenfelül az USB-kapcsolat típusának módosításához mostantól felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ez a verzió a Kamera működését és a HONOR Jegyzetek felhasználói élményét is optimalizálja. Ezenfelül egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Az új AI-radír segítségével egyetlen koppintással intelligensen eltávolíthatja a képekről a járókelőket és más nem kívánt elemeket. Próbálja ki: Galéria > Válasszon ki egy fényképet > Szerkesztés > AI-radír.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Szinkrontolmácsolás">
<feature>Ha felváltva beszélget valakivel, ez a funkció fordítást tud biztosítani a kínai, az angol, a francia, a német, a spanyol, az olasz, az orosz, a török, a maláj és az arab nyelv között. A hang- és a szövegbevitelt egyaránt támogatja, valamint a fordítás továbbítását is. Próbálja ki: Beállítások > Asszisztens > Szinkrontolmácsolás.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Mostantól Portré módban elérhető a Harcourt stílus.
A kamera gyors eléréséhez nyomja meg kétszer a bekapcsológombot.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Jegyzetek">
<feature>A HONOR Jegyzetek segítséget nyújt a hangrögzítésben, a hang szöveggé alakításában és a valós idejű fordításban.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Az USB-kapcsolat váltásakor felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ha a Csak töltés opció helyett a Fotók átvitele vagy Fájlok átvitele/Android Auto opciót választja, megjelenik egy hitelesítési vagy biztonsági üzenet, amelynek célja, hogy az adatátvitel garantáltan biztonságos legyen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. augusztus). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini membawakan fitur baru, termasuk Penghapus AI dan Terjemahan tatap muka. Selain itu, autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan Kamera dan pengalaman pengguna HONOR Catatan. Kemudian, penambal keamanan juga disertakan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Penghapus AI yang baru dapat membantu Anda menghapus orang yang lewat atau elemen lainnya yang tidak diinginkan dari gambar dengan sekali ketuk. Cobalah dengan membuka: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Penghapus AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Terjemahan Tatap Muka">
<feature>Dalam situasi bersahutan, layanan ini dapat menyediakan penerjemahan bersama antara bahasa Mandarin, Inggris, Prancis, Jerman, Spanyol, Italia, Rusia, Turki, Melayu, dan Arab. Layanan ini juga mendukung masukan suara dan teks, serta siaran penerjemahan. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Terjemahan Tatap Muka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Gaya Harcourt disertakan dalam mode Potret.
Anda dapat menekan dua kali tombol daya untuk mengakses kamera dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Catatan">
<feature>HONOR Catatan dapat membantu dengan perekaman, ucapan ke teks, dan penerjemahan waktu nyata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat mengganti tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Ags 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini membawakan fitur baru, termasuk Penghapus AI dan Terjemahan tatap muka. Selain itu, autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Rilis ini juga mengoptimalkan Kamera dan pengalaman pengguna HONOR Catatan. Kemudian, penambal keamanan juga disertakan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Penghapus AI yang baru dapat membantu Anda menghapus orang yang lewat atau elemen lainnya yang tidak diinginkan dari gambar dengan sekali ketuk. Cobalah dengan membuka: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Penghapus AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Terjemahan Tatap Muka">
<feature>Dalam situasi bersahutan, layanan ini dapat menyediakan penerjemahan bersama antara bahasa Mandarin, Inggris, Prancis, Jerman, Spanyol, Italia, Rusia, Turki, Melayu, dan Arab. Layanan ini juga mendukung masukan suara dan teks, serta siaran penerjemahan. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Terjemahan Tatap Muka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Gaya Harcourt disertakan dalam mode Potret.
Anda dapat menekan dua kali tombol daya untuk mengakses kamera dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Catatan">
<feature>HONOR Catatan dapat membantu dengan perekaman, ucapan ke teks, dan penerjemahan waktu nyata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat mengganti tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Ags 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni, incluse Gomma AI e Traduzione faccia a faccia. Introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB. Questa versione ottimizza inoltre la fotocamera e l'esperienza utente di HONOR Note e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>La nuova Gomma AI può aiutarti a rimuovere in modo intelligente intrusi e altri elementi indesiderati dalle immagini con un solo tocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Galleria > Seleziona una foto > Modifica > Gomma AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduzione faccia a faccia">
<feature>In scenari di conversazione alternata, può fornire la traduzione bidirezionale tra cinese, inglese, francese, tedesco, spagnolo, italiano, russo, turco, malese e arabo. Inoltre, supporta l'immissione di voce e di testo, nonché la trasmissione di traduzioni. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Traduzione faccia a faccia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>È stato incluso lo stile Harcourt nella modalità Ritratto.
È possibile accedere rapidamente alla fotocamera premendo due volte il pulsante di accensione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note di HONOR">
<feature>HONOR Note offre funzioni di registrazione, riconoscimento vocale e traduzione in tempo reale.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferimento foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (agosto 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni, incluse Gomma AI e Traduzione faccia a faccia. Introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB. Questa versione ottimizza inoltre la fotocamera e l'esperienza utente di HONOR Note e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>La nuova Gomma AI può aiutarti a rimuovere in modo intelligente intrusi e altri elementi indesiderati dalle immagini con un solo tocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Galleria > Seleziona una foto > Modifica > Gomma AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduzione faccia a faccia">
<feature>In scenari di conversazione alternata, può fornire la traduzione bidirezionale tra cinese, inglese, francese, tedesco, spagnolo, italiano, russo, turco, malese e arabo. Inoltre, supporta l'immissione di voce e di testo, nonché la trasmissione di traduzioni. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Traduzione faccia a faccia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>È stato incluso lo stile Harcourt nella modalità Ritratto.
È possibile accedere rapidamente alla fotocamera premendo due volte il pulsante di accensione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note di HONOR">
<feature>HONOR Note offre funzioni di registrazione, riconoscimento vocale e traduzione in tempo reale.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferimento foto o Trasferisci file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (agosto 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מביא עימו תכונות חדשות, כולל 'מחק AI' ו'תרגום פנים אל פנים'. בנוסף, אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את 'מצלמה' ואת חוויית המשתמש של 'הערות של HONOR'. יתר על כן, משולב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>‏‏'מחק AI' החדש יכול לעזור לך להסיר בצורה חכמה את העוברים ושבים ורכיבים לא רצויים אחרים מהתמונות בהקשה אחת. נסה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'גלריה' > 'בחר תמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'מחק AI'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="תרגום פנים אל פנים">
<feature>במצב של לקיחת תורות, אפשרות זו יכולה לספק תרגום הדדי בין סינית, אנגלית, צרפתית, גרמנית, ספרדית, איטלקית, רוסית, טורקית, מלאית וערבית. הוא תומך גם בהזנת קול וטקסט, וכן בשידור תרגום. תוכל לנסות זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'תרגום פנים אל פנים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>סגנון Harcourt כלול במצב 'דיוקן'.
אפשר ללחוץ פעמיים על לחצן ההפעלה כדי לגשת במהירות למצלמה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות של HONOR">
<feature>‏'הערות של HONOR' יכול לעזור לך בהקלטה, קול לטקסט ותרגום בזמן אמת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוג' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מביא עימו תכונות חדשות, כולל 'מחק AI' ו'תרגום פנים אל פנים'. בנוסף, אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. כמו כן, שחרור זה ממטב את 'מצלמה' ואת חוויית המשתמש של 'הערות של HONOR'. יתר על כן, משולב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>‏‏'מחק AI' החדש יכול לעזור לך להסיר בצורה חכמה את העוברים ושבים ורכיבים לא רצויים אחרים מהתמונות בהקשה אחת. נסה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'גלריה' > 'בחר תמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'מחק AI'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="תרגום פנים אל פנים">
<feature>במצב של לקיחת תורות, אפשרות זו יכולה לספק תרגום הדדי בין סינית, אנגלית, צרפתית, גרמנית, ספרדית, איטלקית, רוסית, טורקית, מלאית וערבית. הוא תומך גם בהזנת קול וטקסט, וכן בשידור תרגום. תוכל לנסות זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'תרגום פנים אל פנים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>סגנון Harcourt כלול במצב 'דיוקן'.
אפשר ללחוץ פעמיים על לחצן ההפעלה כדי לגשת במהירות למצלמה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות של HONOR">
<feature>‏'הערות של HONOR' יכול לעזור לך בהקלטה, קול לטקסט ותרגום בזמן אמת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוג' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の推奨更新では、AI消しゴム、対面翻訳などの新機能が導入されます。また、USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。今回のリリースでは、カメラとHONORメモのユーザー体験も最適化されます。さらに、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ギャラリー">
<feature>新しいAI消しゴムによって、通行人やその他不要な要素を1回のタップで画面からインテリジェントに削除できます。[ギャラリー] > [写真を選択] > [編集] > [AI消しゴム]に移動して試してみてください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="対面翻訳">
<feature>発話交代状況で、中国語、英語、フランス語、ドイツ語、スペイン語、イタリア語、ロシア語、トルコ語、マレー語、アラビア語を交互に翻訳します。また、音声とテキストの入力、翻訳ブロードキャストもサポートされます。[設定] > [アシスタント] > [対面翻訳]に移動して試してみてください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="カメラ">
<feature>ポートレートモードにアルクールスタイルが含まれています。
電源ボタンを2回押してカメラにクイックアクセスできます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONORメモ">
<feature>HONORメモは、録音、音声文字起こし、リアルタイム翻訳で役立ちます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。[充電のみ]ではなく、[写真の転送]または[ファイルの転送/Android Auto]を選択すると、認証またはセキュリティプロンプトが表示され、より安全なデータ転送が保証されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年8月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください： https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ამ რეკომენდებულ განახლებაში შედის ახალი ფუნქციები, მათ შორის, AI საშლელი და პირისპირ თარგმანი. ამასთან, მოითხოვება მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია USB კავშირის გადართვის დროს. ამ გამოშვებაში ოპტიმიზებულია კამერა და HONOR შენიშვნების სერვისიც. დამატებით ჩაშენებულია უსაფრთხოების შესწორებაც.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გალერეა">
<feature>ახალი AI საშლელი დაგეხმარებათ, ერთი შეხებით, ჭკვიანურად ამოშალოთ სურათებიდან გამვლელები და სხვა არასასურველი ელემენტები. გამოცადეთ ის მენიუდან: გალერეა > ფოტოს არჩევა > რედაქტირ. > AI საშლელი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="პირისპირ თარგმანი">
<feature>თანმიმდევრული საუბრის სიტუაციებში მას შეუძლია, უზრუნველყოს ორმხრივი თარგმანი ჩინურ, ინგლისურ, ფრანგულ, გერმანულ, ესპანურ, იტალიურ, რუსულ, თურქულ, მალაიურ და არაბულ ენებს შორის. გარდა ამისა, მას აქვს ხმოვანი და ტექსტური შეყვანის, ასევე თარგმანის გადაცემის მხარდაჭერა. მისი ცდა შეგიძლიათ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > ასისტენტი > პირისპირ თარგმანი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="კამერა">
<feature>პორტრეტის რეჟიმში შედის ჰარკორტის სტილი.
კამერაზე სწრაფად წვდომა შეგიძლიათ ჩართვის ღილაკზე ორჯერ დაჭერით.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR შენიშვნები">
<feature>HONOR შენიშვნები დაგეხმარებათ ჩაწერაში, ხმის ტექსტად გარდაქმნასა და სინქრონულ თარგმანში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>აუცილებელია მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია USB კავშირის გადართვის დროს. შემოწმების ან უსაფრთხოების მოთხოვნა გამოჩნდება, როცა აირჩევთ ფოტოების გადაცემას ან ფაილების გადაცემას / Android Auto-ს, მხოლოდ დამუხტვის ნაცვლად, რაც უზრუნველყოფს მონაცემთა უსაფრთხო გადაცემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის აგვისტო). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту жаңа мүмкіндіктер (оның ішінде «ЖИ өшіргіші» және «Бетпе-бет аудару») береді. Сондай-ақ USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым «Камера» мен «HONOR Ескертпелер» пайдаланушы тәжірибесін оңтайландырады. Сондай-ақ қауіпсіздік патчы біріктірілген.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Жаңа «ЖИ өшіргіші» мүмкіндігі бір рет түрту арқылы кескіндерден жүргіншілер мен басқа қажетсіз элементтерді зерделі түрде жоюға көмектеседі. «Галерея» > «Фотосуретті таңдау» > «Өңдеу» > «ЖИ өшіргіші» тармағына өту арқылы қолданып көріңіз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бетпе-бет аудару">
<feature>Кезекті жағдайда ол қытай, ағылшын, француз, неміс, испан, итальян, орыс, түрік, малай және араб тілдері арасында өзара аударманы қамтамасыз ете алады. Сондай-ақ ол дауыстық және мәтіндік енгізілімді, сонымен бірге аударманы таратуды қолдайды. «Параметрлер» > «Көмекші» > «Бетпе-бет аудару» тармағына өту арқылы қолданып көруге болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Harcourt мәнері «Портрет» режиміне қосылған.
Камераға жылдам қатынасу үшін қуат түймесін екі рет басуға болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Ескертпелер">
<feature>«HONOR Ескертпелер» сізге жазумен, дауысты мәтінге түрлендірумен және нақты уақыттағы аудармамен көмектеседі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Деректерді қауіпсіз тасымалдауды қамтамасыз ететін «Тек зарядтау» орнына «Фотосуреттерді тасымалдау» немесе «Файлдарды тасымалдау/Android Auto» параметрін таңдаған кезде растау немесе қауіпсіздік сұрауы пайда болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (тамыз, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ជូនចំពោះអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ ការអាប់ដេតដែលបានណែនាំនេះនាំមកនូវមុខងារថ្មីៗ រួមទាំងប្រដាប់លុប AI និងការបកប្រែមុខទល់មុខគ្នាផងដែរ។ លើសពីនេះ ការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ត្រូវបានទាមទារនៅពេលប្តូរគោលបំណងនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB ។ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះក៏ធ្វើឱ្យកាមេរ៉ា និងបទពិសោធន៍អ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ HONOR Notes ប្រសើរឡើងផងដែរ។ លើសពីនេះទៅទៀត បំណះសុវត្ថិភាពត្រូវបានដាក់បញ្ចូល។</feature>
</features>
<features module="វិចិត្រសាល">
<feature>ប្រដាប់លុប AI ថ្មីអាចជួយអ្នកយកអ្នកឆ្លងកាត់ និងធាតុផ្សំដែលមិនចង់បានផ្សេងទៀតចេញពីរូបភាពបានយ៉ាងឆ្លាតវៃត្រឹមមួយប៉ះ។ សាកល្បងប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ វិចិត្រសាល > ជ្រើសរើសរូបថត > កែ > ប្រដាប់លុប AI។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ការបកប្រែមុខទល់មុខគ្នា">
<feature>ក្នុងស្ថានភាពប្ដូរវេនគ្នា វាអាចផ្ដល់ការបកប្រែទៅវិញទៅមករវាងភាសាចិន ភាសាអង់គ្លេស ភាសាបារាំង ភាសាអាល្លឺម៉ង់ ភាសាអេស្ប៉ាញ ភាសាអ៊ីតាលី ភាសារុស្ស៊ី ភាសាតួកគី ភាសាម៉ាឡេ និងភាសាអារ៉ាប់។ វាក៏អាចប្រើការបញ្ចូលសំឡេង និងអត្ថបទ ក៏ដូចជាការផ្សាយការបកប្រែបានផងដែរ។ អ្នកអាចសាកល្បងប្រើវាបានដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ជំនួយការ > ការបកប្រែមុខទល់មុខគ្នា។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កាមេរ៉ា">
<feature>រចនាប័ទ្ម Harcourt ត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូលនៅក្នុងរបៀបបញ្ឈរ។
អ្នកអាចចុចប៊ូតុងថាមពលពីរដង ដើម្បីចូលប្រើកាមេរ៉ាបានយ៉ាងឆាប់រហ័ស។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់ HONOR">
<feature>HONOR Notes អាចជួយអ្នកក្នុងការថតសំឡេង ប្រែសំឡេងទៅអត្ថបទ និងការបកប្រែតាមពេលវេលាជាក់ស្តែង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>ការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ត្រូវបានទាមទារនៅក្នុងគោលបំណងផ្លាស់ប្តូរនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB។ ការបញ្ជាក់ ឬសារសុវត្ថិភាពបង្ហាញនៅពេលអ្នកជ្រើសរើសផ្ទេររូបថត ឬផ្ទេរឯកសារ/Android Auto ជំនួសឱ្យការសាកថ្មតែប៉ុណ្ណោះ ដែលធានាបាននូវការផ្ទេរទិន្នន័យដែលមានសុវត្ថិភាពជាងមុន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (សីហា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង៖ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು AI ಎರೇಸರ್ ಮತ್ತು ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ ಸೇರಿದಂತೆ ಹೊಸ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ತರುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ ಮತ್ತು HONOR ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಸಹ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇದಲ್ಲದೆ, ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ">
<feature>ಹೊಸ AI ಎರೇಸರ್ ನಿಮಗೆ ಒಂದೇ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ ಚಿತ್ರಗಳಲ್ಲಿರುವ ದಾರಿಹೋಕರು ಮತ್ತು ಇತರ ಅನಗತ್ಯ ಅಂಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬುದ್ಧಿವಂತಿಕೆಯಿಂದ ತೆಗೆದುಹಾಕಲು ಸಹಾಯ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ > ಫೋಟೋ ಆಯ್ಕೆಮಾಡಿ > ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಿ > AI ಎರೇಸರ್.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ">
<feature>ಸರದಿ ಕ್ರಮದ ಪರಿಸ್ಥಿತಿಯಲ್ಲಿ, ಇದು ಚೈನೀಸ್, ಇಂಗ್ಲೀಷ್, ಫ್ರೆಂಚ್, ಜರ್ಮನ್, ಸ್ಪ್ಯಾನಿಶ್, ಇಟಾಲಿಯನ್, ರಷ್ಯನ್, ಟರ್ಕಿಶ್, ಮಲಯ ಮತ್ತು ಅರೇಬಿಕ್ ನಡುವೆ ಪರಸ್ಪರ ಅನುವಾದವನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸಬಹುದು. ಇದು ಧ್ವನಿ ಮತ್ತು ಪಠ್ಯ ಇನ್‌ಪುಟ್‌ನ ಜೊತೆಗೆ ಅನುವಾದ ಪ್ರಸಾರವನ್ನು ಸಹ ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನೀವು ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಬಹುದು: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಸಹಾಯಕ > ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
<feature>ಹಾರ್ಕೋರ್ಟ್ ಶೈಲಿಯನ್ನು ಭಾವಚಿತ್ರ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಸೇರಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ.
ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾವನ್ನು ತ್ವರಿತವಾಗಿ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಮಾಡಲು ನೀವು ಪವರ್ ಬಟನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎರಡು ಬಾರಿ ಒತ್ತಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು">
<feature>HONOR ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು ನಿಮಗೆ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್, ಧ್ವನಿಯಿಂದ ಪಠ್ಯ ಮತ್ತು ನೈಜ-ಸಮಯದ ಅನುವಾದದ ಕುರಿತು ಸಹಾಯ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿದೆ. ನೀವು ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಮಾತ್ರ ಎಂಬುದರ ಬದಲಿಗೆ ಫೋಟೊಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ ಅಥವಾ ಫೈಲ್ಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ/Android Auto ವನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಿದಾಗ ಪರಿಶೀಲನೆ ಅಥವಾ ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ರಾಂಪ್ಟ್ ಕಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಡೇಟಾ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಆಗಸ್ಟ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트에는 AI 지우개와 대면식 번역을 비롯한 새로운 기능이 추가되었습니다. 또한 USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 이번 릴리스에서는 카메라와 HONOR 노트의 사용자 경험도 최적화되었습니다. 거기에 보안 패치가 통합되어 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="갤러리">
<feature>새로운 AI 지우개는 한 번의 탭으로 이미지에서 지나가는 사람이나 기타 원치 않는 요소를 지능적으로 제거할 수 있도록 도와줍니다. 갤러리 > 사진 선택 > 편집 > AI 지우개로 이동해서 사용해 보세요.</feature>
</features>
<features module="대면식 번역">
<feature>차례를 기다리는 상황에서 중국어, 영어, 프랑스어, 독일어, 스페인어, 이탈리아어, 러시아어, 터키어, 말레이어, 아랍어 간의 상호 번역을 제공할 수 있습니다. 또한 음성 및 텍스트 입력은 물론 번역 방송도 지원합니다. 설정 > 어시스턴트 > 대면식 번역으로 이동하면 사용해 볼 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="카메라">
<feature>Harcourt 스타일은 포트레이트 모드에 포함되어 있습니다.
전원 버튼을 두 번 누르면 카메라에 빠르게 액세스할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR 노트">
<feature>HONOR 노트는 녹음, 음성 텍스트 변환 및 실시간 번역에 도움을 줄 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 충전 전용 대신 사진 전송 또는 파일 전송/Android Auto를 선택하면 인증 또는 보안 메시지가 표시되어 더욱 안전하게 데이터를 전송할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 8월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້​ນຳ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ໃໝ່​ມາ​ໃຫ້, ເຊິ່ງ​ລວມ​ມີ ຢາງລຶບ AI ແລະ ການ​ແປ​​ພາ​ສາແບບ​ເຊິ່ງ​ໜ້າ. ນອກ​ຈາກ​ນີ້, ຍັງຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວ​ນີ້​ຍັງ​ປັບ​ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​​ຮູບ ແລະ ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້ HONOR Notes ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ. ນອກ​ຈາກນັ້ນ, ຍັງ​ລ​ວມ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ​ນຳ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ">
<feature>​ຢາງລຶບ AI ໃໝ່​ສາ​ມາດ​ຊ່ວຍ​ທ່ານ​ເອົາຄົນ​ຍ່າງ​ຜ່ານ​ ແລະ ອົງ​ປະ​ກອບ​ທີ່​ບໍ່​ຕ້ອງ​ການ​ອື່ນໆອອກ​ຈາກ​ຮູບ​ພາບ​ໄດ້​ຢ່າງ​ອັດ​ສະ​ລິ​ຍະ​ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ແຕະ​ຄັ້ງ​ດຽວ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ > ​ເ​ລືອກ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ > ​ແກ້​ໄຂ > ​ຢາງລຶບ AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ການ​ແປ​​ພາ​ສາແບບ​ເຊິ່ງ​ໜ້າ">
<feature>ໃນ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ​ຜັດ​ປ່ຽນ​ກັນ​ເວົ້າ, ມັນ​ສາ​ມາດ​ປັບ​​ປຸງ​ການ​ແປ​ພາ​ສາຮ່ວມ​ກັນ​ລະ​ຫວ່າງ​ພາ​ສາ​ຈີນ, ພາ​ສາ​ອັງ​ກິດ, ​ພາ​ສາ​ຝ​ຣັ່ງ, ພາ​ສາ​ເຢຍ​ລະ​ມັນ, ພາ​ສາ​ສະ​ເປນ, ພາ​ສາ​ອີ​ຕາ​ລີ, ຣັດເຊຍ, ພາ​ສາ​ຕູ​ລະ​ກີ, ພາ​ສາ​ມາ​ເລ​ ແລະ ພາ​ສາ​ອາ​ຣັບ. ນອກນັ້ນ ມັນ​ຍັງ​ຮອງ​ຮັບ​ກາ​ນ​ປ້ອ​ນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ດ້ວຍ​ສຽງ ແລະ ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ, ພ້ອມ​ທັງການ​ອອກ​ອາ​ກາດ​ການ​ແປ​ພາ​ສາ. ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຜູ້ຊ່ວຍ > ການແປພາສາແບບເຊິ່ງໜ້າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
<feature>Harcourt ຮູບ​ແບບຖືກ​ລວມ​ເຂົ້າ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ຮູບ​ເຄິ່ງ​ຕົວ.
ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ກົດ​ປຸ່ມ​ເປີດ​ປິດເຄື່ອງ​ສອງ​ເທື່ອ​ ເພື່ອ​ເຂົ້າ​ເ​ຖິງ​ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​ຢ່າງ​ໄວ​ວາ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes ສາ​ມາດ​ຊ່ວຍ​ທ່ານ​ເລື່ອງ​ການ​ບັນ​ທຶກ, ສຽງ​ເປັນ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ ແລະ ການ​ແປ​ພາ​ສາ​ໃນ​ເວ​ລາ​ຈິງ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ການກວດ​ສອບ ຫຼື ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ປະ​ກົດຂຶ້ນ​ເມື່ອ​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ ໂອນ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ ຫຼື ໂອນ​ໄຟ​ລ໌/Android ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ, ແທນ​ການ​ສາກ​ເທົ່າ​ນັ້ນ, ເຊິ່ງ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ການ​ໂອນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ທີ່​ປອດ​ໄພ​ກວ່າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ສິງ​ຫາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu įtraukiama naujų funkcijų, įskaitant DI trintuką ir nuoseklųjį vertimą. Be to, perjungiant USB jungtį reikia nustatyti tapatumą. Šioje versijoje taip pat optimizuojama Kamera ir naudotojo patirtis HONOR pastabose. Taip pat įtraukta saugumo pataisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Naujasis DI trintukas gali padėti vienu lietimu išmaniai pašalinti praeivius ir kitus nepageidaujamus elementus iš vaizdų. Išbandykite jį nuėję į Galeriją: ten pasirinkite nuotrauką ir tada „Redaguoti > DI trintukas“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nuoseklusis vertimas">
<feature>Kalbant po vieną, ji gali atlikti abipusį vertimą iš (į) kinų, anglų, prancūzų, vokiečių, ispanų, italų, rusų, turkų, malajų ir arabų kalbų (-as). Taip pat ji dera su balso ir teksto įvestimi bei vertimo transliavimo funkcija. Ją galite išbandyti nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pagelbiklis > Nuoseklusis vertimas“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Į portreto režimą įtrauktas „Harcourt“ stilius.
Galite dukart paspausti maitinimo mygtuką, kad greitai pasiektumėte kamerą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR pastabos">
<feature>HONOR pastabos gali padėti įrašyti, balsą paversti tekstu ir versti tikruoju laiku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Keičiant USB jungties paskirtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Pasirinkus „Persiųsti nuotraukas“ arba „Persiųsti failus („Android Auto“)“, o ne „Tik įkrauti“, pateikiamas patvirtinimo arba saugumo raginimas, užtikrinantis saugesnį duomenų persiuntimą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. rugpjūčio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek ieviestas jaunas funkcijas, tostarp AI dzēšgumija un Klātienes tulkošana. Turklāt, pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Šajā laidienā ir arī optimizēta kamera un lietotnes HONOR Piezīmes lietošanas iespējas. Turklāt ir iekļauts drošības ielāps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Jaunā AI dzēšgumija var palīdzēt jums ar vienu pieskārienu viedi noņemt garāmgājējus un citus nevēlamus elementus no attēliem. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Galerija > Atlasīt fotoattēlu > Rediģēt > AI dzēšgumija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Klātienes tulkošana">
<feature>Situācijā, kad runā pēc kārtas, tā var nodrošināt savstarpēju tulkojumu starp ķīniešu, angļu, franču, vācu, spāņu, itāliešu, krievu, turku, malajiešu un arābu valodu. Tā atbalsta arī balss un teksta ievadi, kā arī tulkošanas apraidi. Varat to izmēģināt, atverot: Iestatījumi > Palīgs > Klātienes tulkošana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Hārkorta stils ir iekļauts portreta režīmā.
Varat divreiz nospiest barošanas pogu, lai ātri piekļūtu kamerai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR piezīmes">
<feature>Lietotne HONOR Piezīmes var palīdzēt ar ierakstīšanu, balss pārveidošanu tekstā un reāllaika tulkošanu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Izvēloties Pārsūtītu fotoattēlus vai Pārsūtīt failus/Android Auto, nevis Tikai uzlādētu, tiek parādīta verifikācijas vai drošības uzvedne, garantējot drošāku datu pārsūtīšanu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada augusts). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट AI इरेजर आ आमने-सामने अनुवाद समेत नव विशेषता सभ अनैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। ई रिलीज कैमरा आओर HONOR नोट्स केर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव केँ सेहो अनुकूलित करैत अछि। एकर अलावा, एकटा सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट कयल अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>नव AI इरेजर अहाँ केँ एकहि टैप सँ इमेज सभ सँ राहगीर आ अन्य अवांछित तत्व सभ केँ बुद्धिमानी सँ हटाबए मे मदति कए सकैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: गैलरी > फोटो चयन करू > संपादित करू > AI इरेजर।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आमने-सामने अनुवाद">
<feature>बेरा-बेरी सँ बजबाक स्थिति मे, ई चीनी, अंग्रेजी, फ्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पैनिश, इतालवी, रूसी, तुर्की, मलय आ अरबी केर बीच पारस्परिक अनुवाद प्रदान कए सकैत अछि। ई वॉयस आ टेक्स्ट इनपुट केर संगहि अनुवाद प्रसारण केर सेहो सपोर्ट करैत अछि। अहाँ एकरा सेटिंग्स > सहायक > आमने-सामने अनुवाद पर जा कए आजमा सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>पोर्ट्रेट मोड मे Harcourt शैली सम्मिलित अछि।
अहाँ कैमरा धरि त्वरित पहुँच केर लेल पावर बटन केँ दू-बेर दबा सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR नोट्स">
<feature>HONOR नोट्स अहाँ केँ रिकॉर्डिंग, वॉयस-टू-टेक्स्ट आ वास्तविक समय मे अनुवाद करए मे मदति कए सकैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। जखन अहाँ मात्र चार्ज करबाक बजाय फोटो सभ केँ स्थानांतरित करू वा फाइल सभ ट्रांसफर करू/Android ऑटो चुनैत छी, तखन एकटा सत्यापन वा सुरक्षा संकेत देखाय पड़ैत अछि, जाहि सँ सुरक्षित डेटा ट्रांसफर सुनिश्चित होइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अगस्त 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka kawea mai e tēnei whakahōutanga taunaki ngā āhuahira hōu, tae atu ki te Ūkui AI me te Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi. Tērā anō, ka hiahiatia he motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take hononga USB. Ka arotautia hoki e tēnei putanga te Kāmera me te wheako kaiwhakamahi o Ngā Tuhipoka HONOR. Tērā anō, ka whakaurua he āpure haumarutanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Taiwhanga">
<feature>Ka taea e te Ūkui AI hōu te āwhina i a koe ki te tango mōhio i ngā kaihipa me tētahi atu huānga tē hiahiatia mai i ngā atahanga mā tētahi pato kotahi. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Taiwhanga > Tīpakohia tētahi whakaahua > Whakatika > Ūkui AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi">
<feature>I roto i tētahi āhuatanga huri noa, ka taea e ia te whakarato i te whakamāoritanga tahi i waenganui i te Hainamana, Ingarihi, Wīwī, Tiamana, Pāniora, Ītariana, Rūhiana, Reo Tākei, Mareia, me te Arapi. E tautoko ana hoki i te tāuru reo me te kuputuhi, tae atu ki te pāohotanga whakawhitinga. Ka taea e koe te whakamātau mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga > Kaiāwhina > Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kāmera">
<feature>Kei roto i te aratau poutū te kāhua Harcourt.
Ka taea e koe te pēhi-taurua i te pātene hiko kia tere te uru ki te kāmera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka HONOR">
<feature>Ka taea e Ngā Tuhipoka HONOR te āwhina i a koe ki te tāhopu, te reo-ki-te-kupu, me te whakamāoritanga wā tūturu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take hononga USB. Ka puta mai tētahi manatokonga, tohuāki haumarutanga rānei ina tīpako koe i Whakawhiti whakaahua, Whakawhitia ngā kōnae / Android Auto rānei, kaua ko te Whakahiko anake, me whakarite kia haumaru ake te whakawhiti raraunga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te āpure haumarutanga Android (Akuhata 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање воведува нови карактеристики, вклучувајќи ги Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција и Преведување лице в лице. Дополнително, потребна е автентикација на корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB. Исто така ги оптимизира Камерата и корисничкото искуство со Белешки од HONOR. Дополнително, вградена е безбедносна крпеница.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерија">
<feature>Новата Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција може да ви помогне интелигентно да ги отстраните случајните минувачи и другите несакани елементи од сликите со еден допир. Испробајте ја така што ќе отидете до: Галерија > Изберете фотографија > Уреди > Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Преведување лице в лице">
<feature>Во ситуација на консекутивен разговор, може да обезбеди преводи помеѓу кинески, англиски, француски, германски, шпански, италијански, руски, турски, малајски и арапски. Исто така, поддржува говорно внесување и внесување текст, како и емитување на преводот. Може да ја испробате така што ќе отидете до: Нагодување > Помошник > Преведување лице в лице.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Фризурата е вклучена во режимот на Портрет.
Може двапати да го притиснете копчето за вклучување/исклучување за брзо да пристапите до камерата.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки од HONOR">
<feature>Белешки од HONOR може да ви помогне со снимки, претворање глас во текст и преведување во реално време.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Потребна е автентикација на корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB. Се појавува барање за потврдување или безбедносно барање кога ќе изберете Пренесувајте фотографии или Пренос на датотеки/Android Auto наместо Само полнење, за да се осигури безбеден пренос на податоците.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (август 2024 година) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но, се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако се појават проблеми во текот на ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് AI ഇറേസർ, മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം എന്നിവ ഉൾപ്പെടെയുള്ള പുതിയ സവിശേഷതകൾ അവതരിപ്പിക്കുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടതും ആവശ്യമാണ്. കൂടാതെ, ഈ റിലീസ് ക്യാമറയും 'HONOR കുറിപ്പുകൾ' എന്നതിന്റെ ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവവും ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു. മാത്രമല്ല, ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ചും ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിട്ടുണ്ട്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഗാലറി">
<feature>ഇമേജുകളിൽ നിന്ന് വഴിപ്പോക്കരെയും മറ്റ് അനാവശ്യ ഘടകങ്ങളെയും ഒരൊറ്റ ടാപ്പിൽ സമർത്ഥമായി നീക്കംചെയ്യാൻ പുതിയ AI ഇറേസറിന് നിങ്ങളെ സഹായിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ഗാലറി > ഒരു ഫോട്ടോ തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുക > എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക > AI ഇറേസർ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം">
<feature>മറ്റുള്ളവരോട് സംസാരിക്കേണ്ടി വരുന്ന സാഹചര്യത്തിൽ, ഇതിന് ചൈനീസ്, ഇംഗ്ലീഷ്, ഫ്രഞ്ച്, ജർമ്മൻ, സ്‌പാനിഷ്, ഇറ്റാലിയൻ, റഷ്യൻ, ടർക്കിഷ്, മലായ്, അറബിക്ക് എന്നീ ഭാഷകളുടെ പരസ്‌പര വിവർത്തനം നൽകാൻ കഴിയും. കൂടാതെ, ഇത് ശബ്‌ദ, ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് ഇൻപുട്ടിനെയും വിവർത്തനം ബ്രോഡ്‌കാസ്റ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിനെയും പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു. നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കാവുന്നതാണ്: ക്രമീകരണം > അസിസ്റ്റന്റ് > മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ക്യാമറ">
<feature>Harcourt ശൈലിയിൽ പോർട്രെയ്‌റ്റ് മോഡ് ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു.
നിങ്ങൾക്ക് പവർ ബട്ടണിൽ രണ്ടുതവണ അമർത്തി ക്യാമറ ദ്രുതഗതിയിൽ ആക്‌സസ് ചെയ്യാവുന്നതാണ്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR കുറിപ്പുകൾ">
<feature>റെക്കോർഡ് ചെയ്യാനും ശബ്‌ദത്തെ ടെക്‌സ്റ്റായി പരിവർത്തനം ചെയ്യാനും തത്സമയ വിവർത്തനം നടത്താനും HONOR കുറിപ്പുകൾക്ക് നിങ്ങളെ സഹായിക്കാൻ കഴിയും.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ ആവശ്യമാണ്. 'ചാർജ് ചെയ്യാൻ മാത്രം' എന്നതിന് പകരം, നിങ്ങൾ 'ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈമാറുക' അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 'ഫയലുകൾ കൈമാറുക/Android Auto' എന്നത് തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുമ്പോൾ ഒരു പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സുരക്ഷാ നിർദ്ദേശം ദൃശ്യമാകുന്നു, ഇത് സുരക്ഷിതമായ ഡാറ്റാ കൈമാറ്റം ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഓഗസ്റ്റ് 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, санал болгож буй энэхүү шинэчлэлт нь AI Баллуур, Нүүр тулсан орчуулга зэрэг шинэ онцлогуудыг авчирна. Түүнчлэн, USB-г холбох зорилгоор сэлгэхэд хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардлагатай. Энэ хувилбар нь HONOR Тэмдэглэлийн Камер болон хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг оновчилдог. Мөн хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтсан болно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерей">
<feature>Шинэ AI Баллуур нь өнгөрч буй хүмүүс болон бусад хүсээгүй элементийг зургаас нэг товшилтоор ухаалгаар арилгахад тусална. Үүнийг Галерей > Зураг сонгох > Засах > AI Баллуур луу орж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нүүр тулсан орчуулга">
<feature>Ээлжилсэн харилцан ярианд энэ нь хятад, англи, франц, герман, испани, итали, орос, турк, малай, араб хэлний хооронд харилцан орчуулга хийх боломжтой. Энэ нь дуу хоолой, бичвэрийн оролт, орчуулгын нэвтрүүлгийг дэмждэг. Та үүнийг Тохиргоо > Туслах > Нүүр тулсан орчуулга хэсэг рүү очиж туршиж үзэх боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камер">
<feature>Харкортын хэв маяг Хөрөг зургийн горимд орсон.
Та камерт гялс хандахын тулд асаах товчийг хоёр удаа дарж болно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Тэмдэглэл">
<feature>HONOR Тэмдэглэл нь бичлэг хийх, дууг текст болгон хөрвүүлэх, бодит цагийн орчуулга хийхэд танд тусална.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>USB-г холбох зорилгоор сэлгэх үед хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардлагатай. Зөвхөн цэнэглэхийн оронд, Зургуудыг дамжуулах эсвэл Файл шилжүүлэх/Андройд автоматыг сонгох үед баталгаажуулах эсвэл хамгаалалтын сануулга гарч ирж, өгөгдөл дамжуулах аюулгүй байдлыг хангана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны наймдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтаар зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन AI इरेजर आणि समोरासमोर भाषांतरासह नवीन वैशिष्ट्ये आणते. याव्यतिरिक्त, USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशांनी स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. हे रिलीझ कॅमेरा आणि HONOR नोट्सचा वापरकर्ता अनुभव देखील ऑप्टिमाइझ करते. शिवाय, एक सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट केला आहे.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गॅलरी">
<feature>नवीन AI इरेजर आपल्याला एका टॅपने प्रतिमांमधून जाणारे आणि अन्य अवांछित घटक हुशारीने काढण्यास मदत करू शकते. येथे जाऊन वापरून पहा: गॅलरी > एक फोटो निवडा > संपादित करा > AI इरेजर.</feature>
</features>
<features module="समोरासमोर भाषांतर">
<feature>बदलत्या परिस्थितीत, ते चीनी, इंग्रजी, फ्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पॅनिश, इटालियन, रशियन, तुर्की, मलय आणि अरबीमध्ये परस्पर भाषांतर प्रदान करू शकते. हे व्हॉइस आणि मजकूर इनपुट, तसेच भाषांतर प्रक्षेपणास देखील सपोर्ट करते. आपण येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पाहू शकता: सेटिंग्ज > सहाय्यक > समोरासमोर भाषांतर.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कॅमेरा">
<feature>हार्कोर्ट स्टाइल पोर्ट्रेट मोडमध्ये समाविष्ट केली आहे.
कॅमेऱ्यात त्वरित ॲक्सेस करण्यासाठी आपण पॉवर बटण दोनदा दाबू शकता.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR नोट्स">
<feature>HONOR नोट्स आपल्याला रेकॉर्डिंग, व्हॉइस-टू-टेक्स्ट आणि रिअल-टाइम भाषांतर करण्यास मदत करू शकतात.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशांनी स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. जेव्हा आपण फोटो स्‍थानांतरित करा किंवा फाइल्स/Android स्वयं स्‍थानांतरित करा निवडता तेव्हा एक सत्यापन किंवा सुरक्षितता सूचना दिसते, केवळ चार्ज करण्याऐवजी, सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (ऑगस्ट 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini memperkenalkan ciri baharu, termasuk Pemadam AI dan Penterjemahan bersemuka. Selain itu, pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB. Keluaran ini juga mengoptimumkan Kamera dan pengalaman pengguna Nota HONOR. Selain itu, tampalan keselamatan telah dimasukkan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Pemadam AI baharu boleh membantu anda mengeluarkan orang yang lalu-lalang dan elemen lain yang tidak diingini daripada imej dengan satu ketikan. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Pemadam AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penterjemahan Bersemuka">
<feature>Secara bergiliran, ia boleh menyediakan penterjemahan menyaling antara Bahasa Cina, Inggeris, Perancis, Jerman, Sepanyol, Itali, Rusia, Turki, Melayu dengan Arab. Ia juga menyokong input suara dan teks serta siaran penterjemahan. Anda boleh mencuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Pembantu > Penterjemahan Bersemuka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Gaya Harcourt disertakan dalam mod Potret.
Anda boleh menekan dua kali butang kuasa untuk mengakses kamera dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota HONOR">
<feature>Nota HONOR boleh membantu anda membuat rakaman, menukarkan suara kepada teks dan penterjemahan masa nyata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB. Pengesahan atau gesaan keselamatan muncul apabila anda memilih Pindahkan foto atau Pindahkan fail/Android Auto, bukannya Cas sahaja, demi memastikan pemindahan data yang lebih selamat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan keselamatan Android (Ogos 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် AI Eraser နှင့် မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန် အပါအဝင် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်အသစ်များကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။ ထို့အပြင် USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှု အပြောင်းအလဲလုပ်သည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်သည် ကင်မရာနှင့် HONOR Notes သုံးစွဲရသည့် အတွေ့အကြုံကိုလည်း အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။ လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကိုလည်း ထပ်ဆောင်း ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံပြခန်း">
<feature>AI Eraser အသစ်သည် တစ်ချက်နှိပ်ရုံဖြင့် ရုပ်ပုံများထဲရှိ ဖြတ်သန်းသွားလာသူများနှင့် အခြား မလိုလားသော အရာများကို ပါးပါးနပ်နပ် ဖယ်ရှားနိုင်စေသည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ ၎င်းကို စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ပုံပြခန်း > ဓာတ်ပုံရွေးချယ်မည် > တည်းဖြတ်မည် > AI Eraser။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန်">
<feature>အပြန်အလှန် စကားပြောကြသည့်အခါ ၎င်းသည် တရုတ်၊ အင်္ဂလိပ်၊ ပြင်သစ်၊ ဂျာမန်၊ စပိန်၊ အီတလီ၊ ရုရှား၊ တူရကီ၊ မလေးနှင့် အာရဗီတို့အကြား အပြန်အလှန် ဘာသာပြန်ခြင်းကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးနိုင်သည်။ ၎င်းသည် အသံဖြင့် စာရိုက်သွင်းမှုအပြင် ဘာသာပြန် ထုတ်လွှင့်မှုကိုလည်း ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။ သင်သည် ဖော်ပြပါသို့သွား၍ ၎င်းကိုစမ်းကြည့်နိုင်သည်- ဆက်တင် > အကူ > မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင်မရာ">
<feature>အလှပုံစနစ်တွင် Harcourt စတိုင် ပါဝင်သည်။
ပါဝါခလုတ်ကို နှစ်ချက်နှိပ်၍ ကင်မရာကို အမြန် ဝင်ရောက် သုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes ဖြင့် သင်သည် မှတ်တမ်းတင်ခြင်း၊ အသံမှ စာသားပြောင်းခြင်းနှင့် အချိန်နှင့် တစ်ပြေးညီ ဘာသာပြန်ခြင်းတို့ကို လုပ်ဆောင်နိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှု အပြောင်းအလဲလုပ်သည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ "အားသွင်းရန်သာ" အစား ပုံများ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် သို့မဟုတ် ဖိုင်များ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် / Android Auto ကို ရွေးချယ်သည့်အခါ အတည်ပြုမှု သို့မဟုတ် လုံခြုံရေး ညွှန်ကြားချက် ပေါ်လာပြီး ဒေတာ လွှဲပြောင်းမှုကို ပို၍လုံခြုံစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဩဂုတ် 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ AI Eraser ႏွင့္ မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္ အပါအဝင္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္အသစ္မ်ားကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ အေျပာင္းအလဲလုပ္သည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္သည္ ကင္မရာႏွင့္ HONOR Notes သုံးစြဲရသည့္ အေတြ႕အႀကဳံကိုလည္း အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။ လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကိုလည္း ထပ္ေဆာင္း ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံျပခန္း">
<feature>AI Eraser အသစ္သည္ တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္႐ုံျဖင့္ ႐ုပ္ပုံမ်ားထဲရွိ ျဖတ္သန္းသြားလာသူမ်ားႏွင့္ အျခား မလိုလားေသာ အရာမ်ားကို ပါးပါးနပ္နပ္ ဖယ္ရွားႏိုင္ေစသည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ ၎ကို စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ပုံျပခန္း > ဓာတ္ပုံေ႐ြးခ်ယ္မည္ > ျပင္ဆင္မည္ > AI Eraser။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္">
<feature>အျပန္အလွန္ စကားေျပာၾကသည့္အခါ ၎သည္ တရုတ္၊ အဂၤလိပ္၊ ျပင္သစ္၊ ဂ်ာမန္၊ စပိန္၊ အီတလီ၊ ႐ုရွား၊ တူရကီ၊ မေလးႏွင့္ အာရဗီတို႔အၾကား အျပန္အလွန္ ဘာသာျပန္ျခင္းကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးႏိုင္သည္။ ၎သည္ အသံျဖင့္ စာ႐ိုက္သြင္းမႈအျပင္ ဘာသာျပန္ ထုတ္လႊင့္မႈကိုလည္း ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။ သင္သည္ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔သြား၍ ၎ကိုစမ္းၾကည့္ႏိုင္သည္- ဆက္တင္ > အကူ > မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင္မရာ">
<feature>အလွပုံစနစ္တြင္ Harcourt စတိုင္ ပါဝင္သည္။
ပါဝါခလုတ္ကို ႏွစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္၍ ကင္မရာကို အျမန္ ဝင္ေရာက္ သုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes ျဖင့္ သင္သည္ မွတ္တမ္းတင္ျခင္း၊ အသံမွ စာသားေျပာင္းျခင္းႏွင့္ အခ်ိန္ႏွင့္ တစ္ေျပးညီ ဘာသာျပန္ျခင္းတို႔ကို လုပ္ေဆာင္ႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ အေျပာင္းအလဲလုပ္သည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ "အားသြင္းရန္သာ" အစား ပုံမ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ဖိုင္မ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ / Android Auto ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္သည့္အခါ အတည္ျပဳမႈ သို႔မဟုတ္ လုံၿခဳံေရး ၫႊန္ၾကားခ်က္ ေပၚလာၿပီး ေဒတာ လႊဲေျပာင္းမႈကို ပို၍လုံၿခဳံေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဩဂုတ္ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen gir deg nye funksjoner, inkludert KI-viskelær og Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse. I tillegg kreves brukerbekreftelse når du bytter USB-tilkoblingsformål. Denne utgaven optimerer også Kamera og brukeropplevelsen med HONOR Notater. En sikkerhetsoppdatering er også inkludert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Den nye KI-viskelær kan hjelpe deg med å fjerne forbipasserende og andre elementer fra bilder på intelligent vis med ett trykk. Prøv den ut ved å gå til: Galleri > Velg et bilde > Rediger > KI-viskelær.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse">
<feature>I en turtakingssituasjon kan den gi gjensidig oversettelse mellom kinesisk, engelsk, fransk, tysk, spansk, italiensk, russisk, tyrkisk, malaysisk og arabisk. Den støtter også tale- og tekstinndata, samt oversettelsessendinger. Du kan prøve det ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Assistent > Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt-stil er inkludert i Portrett-modus.
Du kan trykke to ganger på av/på-knappen for å raskt få tilgang til kameraet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notater">
<feature>HONOR Notater kan hjelpe deg med opptak, tale-til-tekst og oversettelse i sanntid.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brukerbekreftelse kreves ved bytting av USB-tilkoblingsformål. En bekreftelse eller sikkerhetsmelding dukker opp når du velger Overfør bilder eller Overfør filer / Android Auto istedenfor bare Bare opplading, og sikrer dermed tryggere dataoverføring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (aug 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले AI इरेजर र फेस टु फेस अनुवाद गर्ने सुविधालगायतका नयाँ सुविधाहरू ल्याएको छ । साथै, USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । यो रिलिजले क्यामेरा र HONOR Notes को प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभव पनि अप्टिमाइज गर्छ । साथै, सुरक्षा प्याच पनि समावेश गरिएको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्यालरी">
<feature>तपाईं नयाँ AI इरेजरका सहायताले फोटोमा भएका अनावश्यक व्यक्ति र अन्य अनावश्यक वस्तुहरू स्मार्ट तरिकाले हटाउन सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: ग्यालरी > फोटो चयन गर्नुहोस् > सम्पादन गर्नुहोस् > AI इरेजर ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="फेस टु फेस अनुवाद">
<feature>यसले तपाईंलाई आवश्यक परेको अवस्थामा चिनियाँ, अङ्ग्रेजी, फ्रेन्च, जर्मन, स्पेनिस, इटालियन, रसियन, टर्किस, मलाय र अरबी भाषाका बिचमा अनुवाद गर्ने सुविधा प्रदान गर्न सक्छ । यसमा भ्वाइस र टेक्स्ट इन्पुट पनि दिन मिल्छ र अनुवाद पढेर सुनाउने सुविधा उपलब्ध छ । तपाईं यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्न सक्नुहुन्छ: सेटिङहरू > सहायक > फेस टु फेस अनुवाद ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="क्यामेरा">
<feature>पोर्ट्रेट मोडमा Harcourt शैली समावेश गरिएको छ ।
तपाईं पावर बटनमा दुई पटक थिचेर द्रुत रूपमा क्यामेराको पहुँच गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes ले तपाईंलाई रेकर्ड गर्न, भ्वाइसबाट पाठमा रूपान्तरण गर्न र वास्तविक समयमा अनुवाद गर्न मद्दत गर्न सक्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । तपाईंले चार्ज मात्र गर्नुहोस् विकल्पको साटो फोटोहरू स्थानान्तरण गर्नुहोस् वा फाइल स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् / Android Auto चयन गर्नुभयो भने प्रमाणीकरण वा सुरक्षा प्रम्प्ट देखिने छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अगस्ट 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update biedt nieuwe functies, waaronder AI-gum en Face-to-face vertaling. Bovendien is gebruikersauthenticatie vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden. Deze release optimaliseert ook de Camera en de gebruikerservaring van HONOR Notities. Bovendien is er een beveiligingspatch opgenomen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Foto's">
<feature>De nieuwe AI-gum kan u helpen om met één tik op een intelligente manier de voorbijgangers en andere ongewenste elementen uit afbeeldingen te verwijderen. Probeer het uit via: Foto's > Selecteer een foto > Bewerken > AI-gum.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face vertaling">
<feature>In een om-de-beurt-situatie kan het wederzijdse vertaling bieden tussen Chinees, Engels, Frans, Duits, Spaans, Italiaans, Russisch, Turks, Maleis en Arabisch. Het ondersteunt ook spraak- en tekstinvoer, evenals uitzending van vertalingen. U kunt het uitproberen via: Instellingen > Assistent > Face-to-face vertaling.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Harcourt-stijl is opgenomen in de Portretmodus.
U kunt twee keer drukken op de aan/uit-knop om snel toegang te krijgen tot de camera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notities">
<feature>HONOR Notities kan u helpen met opnemen, spraak-naar-tekst en realtime vertaling.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden. Er verschijnt een verificatie- of beveiligingsprompt wanneer u Foto's overdragen of Bestanden overdragen / Android Auto selecteert, in plaats van Alleen opladen, wat zorgt voor een veiligere gegevensoverdracht.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (augustus 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ AI ଇରେଜର୍ ଏବଂ ଫେସ୍‌ ଟୁ ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରି ନୂତନ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ରହିଛି। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍ କ୍ୟାମେରା ଏବଂ HONOR ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତି ମଧ୍ୟ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ। ଏହାସହ, ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ">
<feature>ନୂତନ AI ଇରେଜର୍ ଗୋଟିଏ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ରେ ପଥଚାରୀ ଏବଂ ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ଅବାଞ୍ଛିତ ଉପାଦାନଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରୁ ଚତୁରତାର ସହ ଅପସାରଣ କରିପାରେ। ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ > ଏକ ଫଟୋ ଚୟନ କରନ୍ତୁ > ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରନ୍ତୁ > AI ଇରେଜର୍।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଫେସ୍‌ ଟୁ ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ">
<feature>କଥା କହିବା ପାଳି ପରି ସ୍ଥିତିରେ, ଏହା ଚାଇନିଜ୍, ଇଂରାଜୀ, ଫ୍ରେଞ୍ଚ, ଜର୍ମାନ, ସ୍ପାନୀୟ, ଇଟାଲୀୟ, ଋଷିୟ, ତୁର୍କିସ, ମଳୟ ଏବଂ ଆରବୀୟ ଭାଷାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ମଧ୍ୟରେ ମ୍ୟୁଚ୍ୟୁଆଲ ଅନୁବାଦ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରିପାରିବ। ଏହା ଭଏସ୍ ଏବଂ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍ ଇନପୁଟ୍, ତଥା ଅନୁବାଦ ବ୍ରୋଡକାଷ୍ଟ ମଧ୍ୟ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ପାରିବେ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସହାୟକ > ଫେସ୍‌ ଟୁ ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
<feature>ପୋର୍ଟ୍ରେଟ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ ହାରକୋର୍ଟ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ।
କ୍ୟାମେରା ତୁରନ୍ତ ଆକସେସ୍ କରିବାକୁ ଆପଣ ପାୱାର୍ ବଟନ୍ ଦ୍ୱିବାର-ଦବାଇ ପାରିବେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ">
<feature>HONOR ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ରେକର୍ଡିଂ, ଭଏସ୍‌-ଟୁ-ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍, ଏବଂ ରିଅଲ୍‌-ଟାଇମ୍ ଅନୁବାଦରେ ସହାୟତା କରିପାରିବ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଆପଣ ଫଟୋଗୁଡିକ ସ୍ଥାନାନ୍ତର କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ/Android Auto ଚୟନ କରିବା ବେଳେ, କେବଳ ଚାର୍ଜ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ ବଦଳରେ ସୁରକ୍ଷିତ ଡାଟା ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି ଏହା ଯାଞ୍ଚ କିମ୍ବା ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ରମ୍ପଟ୍‌ ଦେଖାଯଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅଗଷ୍ଟ 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਨਵੀਆਂ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀਆਂ ਗਈਆਂ ਹਨ, ਜਿਨ੍ਹਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ ਅਤੇ ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹਨ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਲੋੜੀਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੈਮਰਾ ਅਤੇ HONOR ਨੋਟਸ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਨਾਲ ਹੀ, ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਗੈਲਰੀ">
<feature>ਨਵਾਂ AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਇੱਕ ਟੈਪ ਨਾਲ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਤੋਂ ਰਾਹਗੀਰਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਅਣਚਾਹੇ ਐਲੀਮੈਂਟਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਝਦਾਰੀ ਨਾਲ ਹਟਾਉਣ ਵਿੱਚ ਮਦਦ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਗੈਲਰੀ > ਇੱਕ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਚੁਣੋ > AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ > ਸੋਧੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ">
<feature>ਇੱਕ ਮੋੜ ਲੈਣ ਵਾਲੀ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਵਿੱਚ, ਇਹ ਚੀਨੀ, ਅੰਗ੍ਰੇਜ਼ੀ, ਫਰਾਂਸੀਸੀ, ਜਰਮਨ, ਸਪੈਨਿਸ਼, ਇਤਾਲਵੀ, ਰੂਸੀ, ਤੁਰਕੀ, ਮਲਯ, ਅਤੇ ਅਰਬੀ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਆਪਸੀ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ. ਇਹ ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਅਤੇ ਟੈਕਸਟ ਇਨਪੁੱਟ ਦੇ ਨਾਲ-ਨਾਲ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਬ੍ਰੌਡਕਾਸਟ ਦਾ ਵੀ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸਹਾਇਕ > ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
<feature>ਹਾਰਕੋਰਟ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ ਨੂੰ ਪੋਰਟ੍ਰੇਟ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਤੁਸੀਂ ਕੈਮਰੇ 'ਤੇ ਤੇਜ਼ੀ ਨਾਲ ਪਹੁੰਚ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਪਾਵਰ ਬਟਨ ਨੂੰ ਦੋ ਵਾਰ ਦਬਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ਨੋਟਸ">
<feature>HONOR ਨੋਟਸ ਐਪ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗ, ਆਵਾਜ਼-ਤੋਂ-ਟੈਕਸਟ, ਅਤੇ ਅਸਲ-ਸਮਾਂ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਡੇਟਾ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ, ਸਿਰਫ਼ ਚਾਰਜ ਕਰੋ ਦੀ ਬਜਾਏ, ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ/Android Auto ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਨੂੰ ਚੁਣਦੇ ਹੋ ਤਾਂ ਤਸਦੀਕ ਜਾਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪ੍ਰੌਂਪਟ ਦਿਖਾਈ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਗਸਤ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja wprowadza nowe funkcje, w tym Gumkę AI i Tłumaczenie twarzą w twarz. Ponadto uwierzytelnianie użytkownika jest wymagane podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB. To wydanie optymalizuje działanie aparatu i komfort użytkowania Notatek HONOR. Zawiera ono także poprawkę bezpieczeństwa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Nowa funkcja Gumka AI może pomóc w inteligentnym usuwaniu przechodniów i niechcianych elementów ze zdjęć jednym dotknięciem. Wypróbuj ją, przechodząc do: Galeria > Wybierz zdjęcie > Edytuj > Gumka AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tłumaczenie twarzą w twarz">
<feature>Kiedy rozmówcy mówią po kolei, może zapewnić wzajemne tłumaczenie między językami chińskim, angielskim, francuskim, niemieckim, hiszpańskim, włoskim, rosyjskim, tureckim, malajskim i arabskim. Obsługuje również wprowadzanie głosu i tekstu, a także transmisje tłumaczeń. Funkcję tę możesz wypróbować, przechodząc do: Ustawienia > Asystent > Tłumaczenie twarzą w twarz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aparat">
<feature>Styl Harcourt jest dostępny w trybie portretowym.
Aby uzyskać szybki dostęp do aparatu, można nacisnąć dwukrotnie przycisk zasilania.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notatki HONOR">
<feature>Notatki HONOR mogą pomóc w nagrywaniu, zamianie głosu na tekst i tłumaczeniu w czasie rzeczywistym.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Wymagane jest uwierzytelnienie użytkownika podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB. Monit o weryfikację lub monit dotyczący bezpieczeństwa pojawia się po wybraniu opcji Transferowanie zdjęć lub Transferowanie plików / Android Auto zamiast opcji Tylko ładowanie, zapewniając bezpieczniejszy transfer danych.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (sierpień 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, esta atualização recomendada traz novos recursos, incluindo o Apagador de IA e a Tradução face a face. Além disso, a autenticação de usuário passou a ser necessária ao mudar o propósito da conexão USB. Esta versão também otimiza a Câmera e a experiência de usuário do Notas HONOR. Um patch de segurança também foi incorporado.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>O novo Apagador de IA pode ajudar você a remover os transeuntes e outros elementos indesejados das imagens de forma inteligente com um único toque. Experimente acessando: Galeria > Selecionar uma foto > Editar > Apagador de IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradução face a face">
<feature>Em uma situação de revezamento, ele pode fornecer tradução mútua entre chinês, inglês, francês, alemão, espanhol, italiano, russo, turco, malaio e árabe. Ele também suporta entrada de voz e texto, bem como transmissão de tradução. Você pode experimentar acessando: Configurações > Assistente > Tradução face a face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmera">
<feature>O estilo Harcourt está incluso no modo Retrato.
Você pode pressionar duas vezes o botão ligar/desligar para acessar a câmera rapidamente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas HONOR">
<feature>O Notas HONOR pode ajudar você com gravação, conversão de fala em texto e tradução em tempo real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>A autenticação de usuário é necessária ao mudar o propósito da conexão USB. Uma mensagem de verificação ou segurança aparece quando você seleciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir arquivos/Android Auto, em vez de Carregar apenas, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (agosto de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada oferece novas funcionalidades, incluindo o Apagador por IA e a Tradução frente a frente. Além disso, é necessária a autenticação do utilizador ao mudar para a ligação USB. Esta versão também otimiza a Câmara e a experiência do utilizador das Notas HONOR. Foi também integrada uma correção de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>O novo Apagador por IA pode ajudar a remover, de forma inteligente, os transeuntes e outros elementos indesejados das imagens com um único toque. Experimente acedendo a: Galeria > Selecionar uma fotografia > Editar > Apagador por IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradução frente a frente">
<feature>Numa situação inesperada, pode fornecer a tradução mútua entre chinês, inglês, francês, alemão, espanhol, italiano, russo, turco, malaio e árabe. Também suporta a entrada de voz e texto, bem como a transmissão da tradução. Pode experimentar acedendo a: Definições > Assistente > Tradução frente a frente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmara">
<feature>O estilo Harcourt é incluído no modo Retrato.
Pode premir duas vezes o botão para ligar/Desligar para aceder rapidamente à câmara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas HONOR">
<feature>A Notas HONOR podem ajudar a gravar, conversão de voz para texto e tradução em tempo real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>É necessária a autenticação do utilizador ao mudar para a ligação USB. É apresentado um comando de verificação ou segurança ao selecionar Transferir fotografias ou Transferir ficheiros / Android Auto em vez de Apenas carregar, garantindo a transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (agosto de 2024) para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não apaga os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată aduce noi funcții, inclusiv Radieră AI și Traducere față în față. În plus, este necesară autentificarea utilizatorului atunci când schimbați scopul conexiunii prin USB. Această versiune îmbunătățește, de asemenea, aplicația Cameră foto și experiența utilizatorului în aplicația Notițe HONOR. În plus, este încorporată o corecție de securitate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Noua aplicație Radieră AI vă poate ajuta să eliminați în mod inteligent trecătorii și alte elemente nedorite din imagini cu o singură atingere. O puteți încerca din Galerie > Selectați o fotografie > Editare > Radieră AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducere față în față">
<feature>Într-o situație în care se discută pe rând, aplicația poate oferi traducere reciprocă între limbile chineză, engleză, franceză, germană, spaniolă, italiană, rusă, turcă, malaeză și arabă. De asemenea, acceptă introducerea de informații sub formă de voce și text, precum și difuzarea traducerii. O puteți încerca din Setări > Asistent > Traducere față în față.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cameră foto">
<feature>Stilul Harcourt este inclus în modul Portret.
Puteți apăsa de două ori butonul de pornire pentru a accesa rapid camera foto.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notițe HONOR">
<feature>Aplicația Notițe HONOR vă poate ajuta cu înregistrarea, conversia voce-text și traducerea în timp real.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentificarea utilizatorului este necesară când schimbați scopul conexiunii prin USB. Un mesaj de verificare sau de securitate apare atunci când selectați Transfer de fotografii sau Transfer de fișiere/Android Auto, în loc de Doar încărcare, asigurând un transfer de date mai sigur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (august 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea actualizării nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь, это рекомендуемое обновление предлагает новые функции, включая «Удаление с помощью ИИ» и «Перевод диалога». Кроме того, при переключении USB-соединения требуется аутентификация пользователя. В этом выпуске также оптимизированы Камера и опыт использования Заметок HONOR. Кроме того, в обновление включено исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Новая функция «Удаление с помощью ИИ» поможет вам одним нажатием автоматически удалить прохожих и нежелательные элементы с изображений. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел «Галерея > Выбор фото > Изменить > Удаление с помощью ИИ».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Перевод диалога">
<feature>В ситуации последовательного диалога обеспечивает взаимный перевод между китайским, английским, французским, немецким, испанским, итальянским, русским, турецким, малайским и арабским языками. Кроме того, функция поддерживает голосовой и текстовый ввод, а также трансляцию перевода. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел: «Настройки > Ассистент > Перевод диалога».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>В режиме портрета добавлен стиль Арко.
Дважды нажмите на кнопку включения, чтобы быстро открыть камеру.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заметки HONOR">
<feature>Заметки HONOR помогут вам в записи голоса, преобразовании голоса в текст и переводе в режиме реального времени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При переключении USB-соединения требуется аутентификация пользователя. При выборе режима «Передача фото», «Передача файлов/Android Auto» вместо режима «Только зарядка» появляется запрос проверки или безопасности, что обеспечивает более безопасную передачу данных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (август 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය AI මකනය සහ මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය ඇතුළු නව විශේෂාංග ලබා දෙයි. මීට අමතරව, USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. මෙම නිකුතුව කැමරාව සහ HONOR Notes හි පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම ද ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි. ඊටත් අමතරව, ආරක්ෂක පිළියමක් ඇතුළත් කර ඇත.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ගැලරිය">
<feature>නව AI මකනයට එහා මෙහා යන අය සහ අනෙකුත් අනවශ්‍ය දේවල් එක තට්ටු කිරීමකින් රූපවලින් බුද්ධිමත්ව ඉවත් කිරීමට ඔබට උපකාර කළ හැකි ය. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: ගැලරිය > ඡායාරූපයක් තෝරා ගන්න > සංස්කරණය කරන්න > AI මකනය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය">
<feature>වාරය ගැනීමේ තත්වයක් තුළ දී, එයට චීන, ඉංග්‍රීසි, ප්‍රංශ, ජර්මානු, ස්පාඤ්ඤ, ඉතාලි, රුසියානු, තුර්කි, මැලේ සහ අරාබි අතර අන්‍යෝන්‍ය පරිවර්තනයක් සැපයීමට හැකිය. එය කටහඬ සහ පෙළ ආදානයට මෙන්ම පරිවර්තන විකාශනය කරන්නට ද සහය දක්වයි. ඔබට මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කළ හැකිය: සැකසුම් > සහායක > මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කැමරාව">
<feature>හාකට් විලාසය ආලේඛ්‍යය ප්‍රකාරයේ ඇතුළත්ව ඇත.
ඔබට ඉක්මනින් කැමරාවට පිවිසීමට බලය බොත්තම ද්වි-ඔබන්නට හැකිය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>HONOR Notes හට ඔබට පටිගත කිරීම, කටහඬ පෙළ වෙත, සහ තත්‍ය කාලීන පරිවර්තනය මගින් උපකාර කළ හැකිය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. ඔබ ආරෝපණය පමණි වෙනුවට ඡායාරූප මාරු කරන්න හෝ ගොනු හුවමාරු කරන්න/Android Auto තෝරාගත් විට, වඩා ආරක්ෂිත දත්ත මාරුව තහවුරු කරමින් සත්‍යාපන හෝ ආරක්ෂක ප්‍රේරණයක් දිස්වේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 අගෝ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia prináša nové funkcie vrátane AI gumy a Osobného prekladu. Pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB sa navyše vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Toto vydanie tiež optimalizuje Fotoaparát a používateľskú skúsenosť s aplikáciou HONOR Notes. Súčasťou je aj bezpečnostná oprava.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Nová funkcia AI guma vám pomôže jedným ťuknutím inteligentne odstrániť okoloidúcich a iné nežiaduce prvky z obrázkov. Vyskúšajte to v ponuke Galéria > Vybrať fotografiu > Upraviť > AI guma.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Osobný preklad">
<feature>Pri konverzácii dokáže zabezpečiť vzájomný preklad medzi čínštinou, angličtinou, francúzštinou, nemčinou, španielčinou, taliančinou, ruštinou, turečtinou, malajčinou a arabčinou. Podporuje aj hlasový a textový vstup, ako aj vysielanie prekladu. Môžete to vyskúšať v ponuke Nastavenia > Asistent > Osobný preklad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Súčasťou režimu Portrét je štýl Harcourt.
Na rýchly prístup k fotoaparátu môžete dvakrát stlačiť tlačidlo napájania.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notes">
<feature>Aplikácia HONOR Notes vám môže pomôcť so záznamom, prevodom hlasu na text a prekladom v reálnom čase.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Keď namiesto možnosti Len nabíjanie vyberiete možnosť Prenos fotografií alebo Prenos súborov/Android Auto, zobrazí sa výzva na overenie alebo zabezpečenie, čím sa zaručuje bezpečnejší prenos dát.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z augusta 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta priporočena posodobitev prinaša nove funkcije, vključno s funkcijo Brisanje z UI in prevajanjem v živo. Obenem je pri preklopu povezave USB potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. V tej izdaji sta optimizirana tudi kamera in uporabniška izkušnja pri uporabi aplikacije Zapiski HONOR. Vključen je tudi varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Z novo funkcijo Brisanje z UI lahko z enim samim dotikom pametno odstranite mimoidoče in druge neželene elemente s slik. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete razdelek Galerija > Izberi fotografijo > Uredi > Brisanje z UI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prevajanje v živo">
<feature>V primeru dialoga lahko zagotovi vzajemno prevajanje med kitajščino, angleščino, francoščino, nemščino, španščino, italijanščino, ruščino, turščino, malajščino in arabščino. Podpira tudi glasovni in besedilni vnos ter oddajanje prevodov. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tako, da odprete razdelek Nastavitve > Pomočnik > Prevajanje v živo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>V portretnem načinu je vključen slog Harcourt.
Če želite hitro dostopiti do kamere, lahko dvakrat pritisnite gumb za vklop/izklop.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zapiski HONOR">
<feature>Aplikacija Zapiski HONOR omogoča lažje snemanje, pretvorbo govora v besedilo in sprotno prevajanje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pri preklopu povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ko izberete možnost Prenos fotografij ali Prenos datotek/Android Auto, se namesto možnosti Samo polnjenje prikaže poziv za preverjanje ali varnostni poziv, s tem pa je zagotovljen varnejši prenos podatkov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravek za Android (avgust 2024) je vključen za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem naletite na težave, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen innehåller nya funktioner, som AI-radergummi och Översättning ansikte mot ansikte. Användarautentisering krävs dessutom när du byter USB-anslutning. I den här utgåvan optimeras också Kamera och användarupplevelsen av HONOR Noteringar. Dessutom har en säkerhetskorrigering implementerats.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Nya AI-radergummi kan hjälpa dig att på ett smart sätt ta bort förbipasserande och andra oönskade element från bilder med ett enda tryck. Prova genom att gå till: Galleri > Välj ett foto > Redigera > AI-radergummi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Översättning ansikte mot ansikte">
<feature>I situationer med turtagning kan den tillhandahålla översättning för flera mellan kinesiska, engelska, franska, tyska, spanska, italienska, ryska, turkiska, malajiska och arabiska. Den stöder också röst- och textinmatning samt översättningssändning. Du kan prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Assistent > Översättning ansikte mot ansikte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt-stil ingår i Porträttläge.
Du kan dubbeltrycka på strömknappen för att snabbt komma åt kameran.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Noteringar">
<feature>HONOR Noteringar kan hjälpa dig med inspelning, röst till text och översättning i realtid.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Användarautentisering krävs när du byter USB-anslutning. En verifierings- eller säkerhetsuppmaning visas när du väljer Överföra foton eller Överföra filer/Android Auto i stället för Endast laddning, vilket ger en säkrare dataöverföring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (augusti 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaleta vipengele vipya, vikijumuisha Kifutio cha AI na Tafsiri ya ana kwa ana. Pia, uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB. Toleo hili pia linaboresha Kamera na uzoefu wa mtumiaji wa Madokezo ya HONOR. Zaidi ya hayo, rekebisho la usalama limejumuishwa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matunzio">
<feature>Kifutio kipya cha AI kinaweza kukusaidia kuondoa kwa umaizi wapita njia na vipengele vingine visivyotakikana kutoka kwenye picha kwa kugusa tu. Kijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Matunzio > Chagua picha > Hariri > Kifutio cha AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tafsiri ya Ana kwa Ana">
<feature>Katika hali ya kuchukua zamu, kinaweza kukupa tafsiri ya kusaidiana kati ya Kichina, Kiingereza, Kifaransa, Kijerumani, Kihispania, Kiitaliano, Kirusi, Kituruki, Kimalei na Kiarabu. Pia kinaruhusu ingizo la usemi na maandishi, pamoja na utangazaji wa tafsiri. Unaweza kukijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Kisaidizi > Tafsiri ya Ana kwa Ana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Mtindo wa Harcourt umejumuishwa kwenye hali ya Picha.
Unaweza kubonyeza mara mbili kitufe cha kuwasha/kuzima ili kufikia kamera kwa haraka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo ya HONOR">
<feature>Madokezo ya HONOR yanaweza kukusaidia kurekodi, usemi hadi maandishi na tafsiri ya wakati halisi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB. Kidokezo cha uthibitishaji au usalama hutokea unapochagua Hamisha picha au Hamisha faili/Android Auto, badala ya Chaji pekee, hivyo basi kuhakikisha uhamishaji salama wa data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Ago 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு AI அழிப்பான் மற்றும் நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு போன்ற புதிய அம்சங்களைக் கொண்டு வருகிறது. கூடுதலாக, USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. இந்த வெளியீடு கேமரா மற்றும் HONOR குறிப்புகளின் பயனர் அனுபவத்தையும் மேம்படுத்துகிறது. அத்துடன், ஒரு பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேலரி">
<feature>புதிய AI அழிப்பான் ஒரே தட்டலில் வழிப்போக்கர்கள் மற்றும் பிற தேவையற்ற கூறுகளைப் படங்களிலிருந்து அறிவார்ந்த முறையில் அகற்ற உதவும். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: கேலரி > புகைப்படத்தைத் தேர்ந்தெடு > திருத்து > AI அழிப்பான்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு">
<feature>ஊடாடும் சூழ்நிலையில், இது சீனம், ஆங்கிலம், பிரெஞ்சு, ஜெர்மன், ஸ்பானிஷ், இத்தாலியன், ரஷ்யன், துருக்கி, மலாய் மற்றும் அரபு மொழிகளுக்கு இடையில் பரஸ்பர மொழிபெயர்ப்பை வழங்குகிறது. இது குரல் மற்றும் உரை டயலிங்குடன், மொழிபெயர்ப்பு ஒளிபரப்பையும் ஆதரிக்கிறது. இதற்குச் சென்று நீங்கள் அதை முயலலாம்: அமைப்புகள் > உதவியாளர் > நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேமரா">
<feature>போர்ட்ரெயிட் முறையில் Harcourt ஸ்டைல் சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது.
சேர்த்த பிறகு, கேமராவை அணுக பவர் பொத்தானை இருமுறை அழுத்தவும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR குறிப்புகள்">
<feature>பதிவுசெய்தல், குரலிலிருந்து உரை மற்றும் நிகழ் நேர மொழிபெயர்ப்பு ஆகியவற்றில் HONOR குறிப்புகள் உங்களுக்கு உதவும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. பாதுகாப்பான தரவுப் பரிமாற்றத்தை உறுதிசெய்யும் வகையில், சார்ஜ் மட்டும் என்பதற்குப் பதிலாக, புகைப்படங்களைப் பரிமாற்று அல்லது கோப்புகளைப் பரிமாற்று/Android Auto என்பதைத் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கும்போது சரிபார்ப்பு அல்லது பாதுகாப்புத் தூண்டுதல் தோன்றும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (ஆக 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేసిన నవీకరణ AI ఎరేజర్ మరియు ముఖాముఖి అనువాదంతో సహా కొత్త ఫీచర్‌లను అందిస్తుంది. అదనంగా, USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చేటప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రమాణీకరణ అవసరం. ఈ విడుదల కెమెరా మరియు HONOR గమనికల యొక్క వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని కూడా ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది. అంతేకాకుండా, ఒక భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ చేర్చబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గ్యాలరీ">
<feature>కొత్త AI ఎరేజర్ ఒక ట్యాప్‌తో చిత్రాల నుండి పరిసరాల్లో వ్యక్తులు మరియు ఇతర అవాంఛిత అంశాలను తెలివిగా తీసివేయడానికి మీకు సహాయపడుతుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దీనిని ప్రయత్నించండి: గ్యాలరీ > ఫోటోను ఎంచుకోండి > సవరించు > AI ఎరేజర్.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ముఖాముఖి అనువాదం">
<feature>మలుపు తీసుకునే పరిస్థితిలో, ఇది చైనీస్, ఇంగ్లీష్, ఫ్రెంచ్, జర్మన్, స్పానిష్, ఇటాలియన్, రష్యన్, టర్కీష్, మలయ్ మరియు అరబిక్ భాషల మధ్య ఉమ్మడి అనువాదాన్ని అందిస్తుంది. ఇది వాయిస్ మరియు టెక్స్ట్ ఇన్‌పుట్ అలాగే అనువాదం ప్రసారానికి మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది. మీరు ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దీనిని ప్రయత్నించవచ్చు: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > సహాయకం > ముఖాముఖి అనువాదం.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కెమెరా">
<feature>హార్కోర్ట్ శైలి పోర్ట్రెయిట్ మోడ్‌లో చేర్చబడింది.
మీరు కెమెరాను త్వరగా యాక్సెస్ చేయడానికి పవర్ బటన్‌ను రెండుసార్లు నొక్కవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR గమనికలు">
<feature>రికార్డింగ్, వాయిస్-టు-టెక్స్ట్ మరియు నిజ-సమయ అనువాదంలో HONOR గమనికలు మీకు సహాయపడతాయి.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చేటప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రమాణీకరణ అవసరం. మీరు ఛార్జ్ మాత్రమే కాకుండా, సురక్షితమైన డేటా బదిలీని నిర్ధారిస్తూ ఫోటోలను బదిలీ చేయండి లేదా ఫైల్స్‌ను బదిలీ చేయండి/Android ఆటోను బదిలీ చేయడాన్ని ఎంచుకున్నప్పుడు ధృవీకరణ లేదా భద్రతా ప్రాంప్ట్ కనిపిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (ఆగష్టు 2024) చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำนี้มอบฟีเจอร์ใหม่ ๆ ซึ่งรวมถึงยางลบ AI และการแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว นอกจากนี้ จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB รีลีสนี้ยังปรับปรุงกล้องถ่ายรูปและการใช้งานของผู้ใช้ของ HONOR โน้ต นอกจากนี้ยังรวมแพตช์ความปลอดภัยอีกด้วย</feature>
</features>
<features module="แกลเลอรี">
<feature>ยางลบ AI ใหม่ช่วยให้คุณลบผู้ที่ผ่านไปมาและส่วนประกอบที่ไม่ต้องการอื่น ๆ ออกจากรูปภาพได้อย่างง่ายดายด้วยการแตะครั้งเดียว ลองใช้โดยไปที่: แกลเลอรี > เลือกภาพถ่าย > แก้ไข > ยางลบ AI</feature>
</features>
<features module="การแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว">
<feature>ในสถานการณ์ที่สลับกันพูด บริการนี้จะมอบการแปลภาษาร่วมกันระหว่างภาษาจีน ภาษาอังกฤษ ภาษาฝรั่งเศส ภาษาเยอรมัน ภาษาสเปน ภาษาอิตาลี ภาษารัสเซีย ภาษาตุรกี ภาษามาเลย์ และภาษาอาหรับ และยังรองรับการป้อนข้อมูลด้วยเสียงและข้อความ รวมถึงการออกอากาศการแปลภาษาอีกด้วย คุณสามารถลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ผู้ช่วย > การแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว</feature>
</features>
<features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
<feature>รวมรูปแบบฮาร์คอร์ตในโหมดภาพบุคคล
คุณสามารถกดปุ่มเปิด/ปิดสองครั้งเพื่อเข้าถึงกล้องถ่ายรูปได้อย่างรวดเร็ว</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR โน้ต">
<feature>HONOR โน้ตช่วยคุณในการบันทึกเสียง แปลงคำพูดเป็นข้อความ และการแปลในเวลาจริง</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB การยืนยันหรือข้อความแจ้งเตือนความปลอดภัยจะปรากฏเมื่อคุณเลือกถ่ายโอนรูปภาพหรือถ่ายโอนไฟล์/Android Auto แทนที่จะชาร์จเท่านั้นเพื่อให้แน่ใจถึงการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลที่ปลอดภัยขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ส.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, naghahatid ang inirerekomendang update na ito ng mga bagong feature, kabilang ang AI na Pambura at Harapang pagsasalin. Bukod pa rito, kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize ng release na ito ang Camera at karanasan ng user ng Mga Tala ng HONOR. Gayundin, isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang bagong AI na Pambura na matalinong alisin ang mga dumadaan at iba pang hindi gustong elemento mula sa mga larawan sa isang tap. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Gallery > Pumili ng larawan > I-edit > AI na Pambura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Harapang Pagsasalin">
<feature>Sa isang turn-taking na sitwasyon, puwede itong magbigay ng parehong pagsasalin sa pagitan ng Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, at Arabic. Sinusuportahan din nito ang pag-input gamit ang boses at text, pati na rin ang pag-broadcast ng pagsasalin. Puwede mo itong subukan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Harapang Pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Kasama ang Harcourt na estilo sa Portrait mode.
Puwede mong pindutin nang dalawang beses ang power button para mabilisang i-access ang camera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala ng HONOR">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang Mga Tala ng HONOR sa recording, voice-to-text, at real-time na pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file/Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ago 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, naghahatid ang inirerekomendang update na ito ng mga bagong feature, kabilang ang AI na Pambura at Harapang pagsasalin. Bukod pa rito, kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Ino-optimize ng release na ito ang Camera at karanasan ng user ng Mga Tala ng HONOR. Gayundin, isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang bagong AI na Pambura na matalinong alisin ang mga dumadaan at iba pang hindi gustong elemento mula sa mga larawan sa isang tap. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Gallery > Pumili ng larawan > I-edit > AI na Pambura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Harapang Pagsasalin">
<feature>Sa isang turn-taking na sitwasyon, puwede itong magbigay ng parehong pagsasalin sa pagitan ng Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, at Arabic. Sinusuportahan din nito ang pag-input gamit ang boses at text, pati na rin ang pag-broadcast ng pagsasalin. Puwede mo itong subukan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Harapang Pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Kasama ang Harcourt na estilo sa Portrait mode.
Puwede mong pindutin nang dalawang beses ang power button para mabilisang i-access ang camera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala ng HONOR">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang Mga Tala ng HONOR sa recording, voice-to-text, at real-time na pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file/Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ago 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sayın kullanıcı, bu önerilen güncelleme AI Silgi ve Yüz Yüze Çeviri gibi yeni özellikler getiriyor. Ayrıca, artık USB bağlantı amacı değiştirildiğinde kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekmektedir. Bu sürüm, aynı zamanda Kamera ve HONOR Notlar uygulamalarını da optimize ediyor. Güvenlik açısından da bir yama bu güncellemeye dahil edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Yeni AI Silgi tek dokunuşla görsellerde arka planda yer alan kişileri ve diğer istenmeyen unsurları akıllı şekilde kaldırmanıza yardımcı olabilir. Galeri > Bir fotoğraf seç > Düzenle > AI Silgi bölümüne giderek deneyebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Yüz Yüze Çeviri">
<feature>Sırayla olmak üzere Çince, İngilizce, Fransızca, Almanca, İspanyolca, İtalyanca, Rusça, Türkçe, Malayca ve Arapça arasında çeviri gerçekleştirir. Ayrıca ses ve metin girişini destekler, bununla birlikte çeviriyi yayınlayabilir. Ayarlar > Asistan > Yüz Yüze Çeviri bölümüne giderek deneyebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt tarzı Portre moduna dahil edilmiştir.
Güç tuşuna iki kez basarak kameraya hızlı bir şekilde erişebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Notlar">
<feature>HONOR Notlar, kayıt, konuşmayı metne çevirme ve anlık çeviri konusunda yardımcı olur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı amacı değiştirilirken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekir. Sadece şarj yerine Fotoğraf aktarımı veya Dosya aktarma/Android Auto'yu seçtiğinizde bir doğrulama veya güvenlik istemi görünür ve bu da daha güvenli veri aktarımı sağlar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yamasını (Ağustos 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا AI يوقىتىش ۋە يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، كامېرا ۋە روڭياۋ خاتىرىسىنى ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئ‍ۆزگەرتكەن ۋاقىتتا ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ئامبار»">
<feature>‏AI يوقىتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، رەسىمدىكى يولدا مېڭىۋاتقان ئادەم، باشقا نەرسە قاتارلىقلارنى ئاڭلىق يوقىتىپ، بىر كۇنۇپكا بىلەن رەسىمنى قۇتقۇزۇپ قالالايسىز، سىناش يولى: ئامبار > رەسىم > تەھرىرلەش > AI يوقىتىش.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە قىلىش»">
<feature>‏نۆۋەتلىشىپ سۆزلىشىش كۆرۈنۈشىدە، خەنزۇچە، ئىنگلىزچە، فىرانسۇزچە، گېرمانچە، ئىسپانچە، ئىتالىيانچە، رۇسچە، تۈركچە، مالايچە ۋە ئەرەبچە ئارىسىدا ئۆزئارا تەرجىمە قىلىشنى قوللايدۇ. ئاۋازلىق ۋە خەتلىك كىرگۈزۈش، تەرجىمە نەتىجىسىنى ئاڭلىتىشنى قوللايدۇ، سىناش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئاڭلىق ياردەمچى > يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«كامېرا»">
<feature>‏پورترېت ھالىتى پۈتۈنلەي يېڭى خاركورت ئۇسلۇبىنى قوللايدۇ.
توك كۇنۇپكىسىنى قوش چېكىپ كامېرانى تېزلىكتە قوزغىتىشقا بولىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«روڭياۋ خاتىرە»">
<feature>‏ئۈنگە ئېلىش، ئاۋازنى تېكىستكە ئايلاندۇرۇش ۋە ئۈنگە ئېلىپ ئەمەلىي ۋاقىتتا تەرجىمە قىلىش ئىقتىدارلىرى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«سىستېما»">
<feature>‏USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئۆزگەرتكەندە ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، «پەقەت توكلاش» تىن «رەسىم يوللاش» ياكى «ھۆججەت يوللاش/Android Auto» ھالىتىگە ئالماشتۇرغاندا دەلىللەش كۆرۈنمە يۈزى ياكى بىخەتەرلىك ئەسكەرتمىسى پەيدا بولۇپ، مەلۇمات يوللىشىڭىزنى تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر قىلىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>‏ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 8-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це рекомендоване оновлення дає змогу працювати з новими функціями, зокрема "ШІ-гумка" й "Переклад тет-а-тет". Крім того, у разі змінення цілей підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. У цьому випуску також оптимізовано додаток "Камера" й взаємодію з користувачем у додатку "Нотатки HONOR". На додаток до цього впроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>За допомогою нової функції "ШІ-гумка" можна інтелектуально вилучати перехожих та інші небажані елементи із зображень одним дотиком. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Галерея" > "Вибрати фото" > "Змінити" > "ШІ-гумка".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Переклад тет-а-тет">
<feature>Використовуйте цю функцію по черзі зі співрозмовником, щоб перекладати такими мовами: китайська, англійська, французька, німецька, іспанська, італійська, російська, турецька, малайська й арабська. Ця функція також підтримує голосове й текстове введення та трансляцію перекладу. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Помічник" > "Переклад тет-а-тет".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>У режим "Портрет" включено стиль "Аркур".
Для швидкого доступу до камери можна двічі натискати кнопку живлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нотатки HONOR">
<feature>Додаток "Нотатки HONOR" може допомагати вам із записуванням, перетворенням мовлення на текст і перекладом у реальному часі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>У разі змінення цілей підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. Якщо замість цілі "Тільки заряджання" вибирається ціль "Передавання фото" або "Передавання файлів / Android Auto", з’являється підказка для проходження перевірки чи контролю безпеки, що зменшує ризик під час передавання даних.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від серпня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ نئی خصوصیات، بشمول AI مٹانے والی شے اور آمنے سامنے ترجمہ لاتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو سوئچ کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ یہ ریلیز کیمرہ اور HONOR نوٹس کے صارف کے تجربے کو بھی بہتر بناتی ہے۔ اس کے علاوہ، ایک سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="گیلری">
<feature>نئی AI مٹانے والی شے آپ کو ایک ہی ٹیپ سے تصاویر سے غیر ضروری اور دیگر ناپسندیدہ عناصر کو ذہانت سے ہٹانے میں مدد کر سکتی ہے۔ یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: گیلری > تصویر منتخب کریں > ترمیم کریں > AI مٹانے والی شے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="آمنے سامنے ترجمہ">
<feature>اپنی باری آنے والی صورت حال میں، یہ چینی، انگریزی، فرانسیسی، جرمن، ہسپانوی، اطالوی، روسی، ترکی، مالے اور عربی کے درمیان باہمی ترجمہ فراہم کر سکتی ہے۔ یہ آواز اور متنی ان پٹ نیز ترجمہ براڈ کاسٹ کرنے میں بھی تعاون کرتی ہے۔ آپ اسے یہاں جا کر آزما سکتے ہیں: ترتیبات > اسِسٹنٹ > آمنے سامنے ترجمہ۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کیمرہ">
<feature>ہارکورٹ اسٹائل پورٹریٹ موڈ میں شامل ہے۔
آپ کیمرہ تک تیزی سے رسائی کے لیے پاور بٹن کو دو بار دبا سکتے ہیں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏‏‏HONOR نوٹس">
<feature>‏‏HONOR نوٹس ریکارڈنگ، آواز سے متن اور حقیقی وقت میں ترجمہ میں آپ کی مدد کر سکتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>‏USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو سوئچ کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ جب آپ ڈیٹا کی محفوظ منتقلی کو یقینی بناتے ہوئے، صرف چارج کریں کی بجائے، تصاویر منتقل کریں یا فائلز منتقل کریں / Android خود کار کو منتخب کرتے ہیں تو تصدیق یا سکیورٹی اشارہ ظاہر ہوتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اگست 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda yangi funksiyalar, jumladan, AI tozalagich va Yuzma-yuz tarjima funksiyalari taqdim etildi. Bundan tashqari, USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. Bu nashrda Kamera hamda HONOR Qaydlar foydalanuvchi taassuroti optimallandi. Undan tashqari, xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galereya">
<feature>Yangi AI tozalagich funksiyasi sizga rasmlardan begonalar va boshqa keraksiz narsalarni osonlik bilan intellektual olib tashlash imkonini beradi. Uni bu yerda sinang: Galereya > Surat tanlash > Tahrirlash > AI tozalagich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Yuzma-yuz tarjima">
<feature>Oʻz navbatida, u xitoy, ingliz, fransuz, nemis, ispan, italyan, rus, turk, malay va arab tillari orasida oʻzaro tarjima qilish imkonini beradi. U ovozli va matnli maʼlumotlarni, shuningdek, ovozli tarjimani ham dastaklaydi. Uni bu yerda sinashingiz mumkin: Sozlamalar > Assistent > Yuzma-yuz tarjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Harcourt uslubi Portret rejimiga kiritilgan.
Kameraga quvvat tugmasini ikki marta bosib tezkor kirishingiz mumkin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Qaydlar">
<feature>HONOR Qaydlar sizga yozib olish, ovozni matnga aylantirish va real vaqtda tarjima qilishda yordam beradi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. “Faqat quvvatlash” oʻrniga “Suratlarni o‘tkazish” yoki “Fayllarni uzatish/Android Auto” tanlaganida, maʼlumotlarni xavfsiz uzatishni taʼminlash uchun tasdiqlash yoki xavfsizlik haqida ogohlantirish oynasi ochiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, avgust) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này mang đến các tính năng mới, bao gồm AI Eraser và Dịch trực tiếp. Ngoài ra, cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB. Bản phát hành này cũng tối ưu hóa Máy ảnh và trải nghiệm người dùng về HONOR Ghi chú. Hơn nữa, bản cập nhật này tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bộ sưu tập">
<feature>Tính năng AI Eraser mới có thể giúp bạn xóa người qua đường và các thành phần không mong muốn khác một cách thông minh khỏi hình ảnh chỉ với một thao tác chạm. Hãy dùng thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Bộ sưu tập > Chọn ảnh > Sửa > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Dịch trực tiếp">
<feature>Trong tình huống thay phiên nhau, tính năng này có thể cung cấp bản dịch lẫn nhau giữa tiếng Trung, tiếng Anh, tiếng Pháp, tiếng Đức, tiếng Tây Ban Nha, tiếng Ý, tiếng Nga, tiếng Thổ Nhĩ Kỳ, tiếng Malay và tiếng Ả Rập. Tính năng này cũng hỗ trợ nhập giọng nói và văn bản, cũng như phát bản dịch. Bạn có thể dùng thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Trợ lý > Dịch trực tiếp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Máy ảnh">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp phong cách Harcourt trong chế độ Ảnh chân dung.
Bạn có thể nhấn đúp nút nguồn để truy cập nhanh vào máy ảnh.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Ghi chú">
<feature>HONOR Ghi chú có thể giúp bạn ghi âm, chuyển lời nói thành văn bản và dịch theo thời gian thực.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB. Một thông báo nhắc xác minh hoặc bảo mật sẽ xuất hiện khi bạn chọn Truyền tải ảnh hoặc Truyền tệp tin/Android Auto, thay vì Chỉ sạc pin, giúp truyền dữ liệu an toàn hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 8 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增了 AI 消除和面對面翻譯功能，優化了相機和榮耀記事使用體驗，更改了 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，並整合了安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增 AI 消除功能，智能消除相片中的路人、雜物等，一鍵拯救廢片，體驗路徑：圖片庫 > 圖片 > 編輯 > AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面對面翻譯】">
<feature>支援在輪流對話場景下，中文、英文、法文、德文、西班牙文、意大利文、俄文、土耳其文、馬來西亞文和阿拉伯文之間的互譯。支援語音和文字輸入，以及翻譯結果廣播。體驗路徑：設定 > 智能助手 > 面對面翻譯。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>人像模式支援全新雅顧風格。
支援輕觸兩下電源鍵快速啟動相機。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【榮耀記事】">
<feature>新增錄音、語音轉文字和錄音實時翻譯功能。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>更改 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸相片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」模式時，彈出驗證介面或安全提示，讓您的數據傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 8 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增 AI 消除和面對面翻譯功能，最佳化相機和榮耀筆記使用體驗，變更 USB 連接方式時新增使用者身分驗證，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增 AI 消除功能，智慧消除相片中的路人、雜物等，一鍵拯救廢片，體驗路徑：圖片庫 > 圖片 > 編輯 > AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面對面翻譯】">
<feature>在支援輪流對話場景下，中文、英文、法文、德文、西班牙文、義大利文、俄文、土耳其文、馬來西亞文、阿拉伯文之間的互譯。支援語音和文字輸入，以及翻譯結果播報，體驗路徑：設定 > 智慧助手 > 面對面翻譯。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>人像模式支援全新雅顧風格。
支援輕觸兩下電源鍵快速啟動相機。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【榮耀筆記】">
<feature>新增錄音、語音轉文字和錄音即時翻譯功能。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>變更 USB 連接方式時增加使用者身分驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸照片」或「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」模式時，彈出驗證畫面或安全提示，讓您的資料傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 8 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
