<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新预置LinkedIn应用，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="应用">
<feature>•  预置LinkedIn。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  合入安卓2024年12月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update pre-installs LinkedIn and incorporates a security patch. Update to enjoy the improvements.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• Pre-installs LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>• Android Security Patch (Dec 2024) has been incorporated for the system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any issues during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ LinkedInን ቅድሚያ ይጭናል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="መተግበሪያዎች">
<feature>• LinkedInን ቅድሚያ ይጭናል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>• ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ዴሴ 2024) ተካትቷል። ስለHONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በግል ውሂብዎ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ እንዲያስቀምጡ ይመከራል።
2. በዝማኔው ጊዜ ማናቸውም ችግሮች ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎ ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ የHONOR አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ወደ የHONOR ደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، هذا التحديث يثبّت لينكدإن بشكل مسبق ويضمّن تصحيح أمان. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="التطبيقات">
<feature>• يثبّت لينكدإن بشكل مسبق.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (ديسمبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটে LinkedIn পূৰ্বে-ইনষ্টল কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল\'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="এপ্প্‌সমূহ">
<feature>• LinkedIn পূৰ্বে-ইনষ্টল আছে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (ডিচেম্বৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰক বা সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাওক।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə LinkedIn-i əvvəlcədən quraşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketini ehtiva edir. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən zövq almaq üçün yeniləyin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proqramlar">
<feature>• LinkedIn-i əvvəlcədən quraşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>• Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Dekabr 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki wis nginstal LinkedIn lan nggabungake patch keamanan. Anyarake kanggo nikmati pangapikan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apl">
<feature>• Wis nginstal LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Patch Keamanan Android (Desember 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dhukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem je predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ , a takođe sadrži i bezbednosnu zakrpu. Ažurirajte i uživajte u poboljšanjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ .</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (dec 2024.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem je predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ , a takođe sadrži i bezbednosnu zakrpu. Ažurirajte i uživajte u poboljšanjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ .</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (dec 2024.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem je predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ , a takođe sadrži i bezbednosnu zakrpu. Ažurirajte i uživajte u poboljšanjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Predinstaliran „LinkedIn“ .</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (dec 2024.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне дадае папярэдне ўстаноўленую праграму LinkedIn і ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Абнавіце, каб выкарыстоўваць палепшаныя функцыі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Праграмы">
<feature>• Гэта абнаўленне дадае папярэдне ўстаноўленую праграму LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (снежань 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация предварително инсталира LinkedIn и включва корекция на сигурността. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Приложения">
<feature>• Инсталира предварително LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>• Корекцията за сигурност на Android (декември 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивирането им преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি আগে থেকেই LinkedIn ইনস্টল করে এবং এতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="অ্যাপস">
<feature>• আগে থেকেই LinkedIn ইনস্টল করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (ডিসেম্বর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ LinkedIn ཉེར་སྤྱོད་སྔོན་སྒྲིག་བྱས་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="ཉེར་སྤྱོད།">
<feature>• LinkedIn སྔོན་སྒྲིག་བྱས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="བདེ་འཇགས།">
<feature>• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 12 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་གཏོང་། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/12 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་སྔར་བཞིན་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ལེགས་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje predinstalira LinkedIn i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Predinstalirani LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>• Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (decembar 2024.) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakvi problemi tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització preinstal·la LinkedIn i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicacions">
<feature>• Preinstal·la LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>• S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (desembre del 2024) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però, així i tot, us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace předinstaluje aplikaci LinkedIn a obsahuje bezpečnostní opravu. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikace">
<feature>• Předinstaluje aplikaci LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (prosinec 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forudinstallerer LinkedIn og inkorporerer en sikkerhedsrettelse. Opdater for at få glæde af forbedringerne.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• Forudinstallerer LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>• Android sikkerhedsrettelse (dec 2024) er blevet integreret for øget systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung installiert LinkedIn vor und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• LinkedIn wird vorinstalliert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Dez. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Kundenhotline an oder suchen Sie das HONOR-Kunden-Service-Center auf, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung installiert LinkedIn vor und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• LinkedIn wird vorinstalliert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Dez. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Kundenhotline an oder suchen Sie das HONOR-Kunden-Service-Center auf, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung installiert LinkedIn vor und beinhaltet einen Sicherheitspatch. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• LinkedIn wird vorinstalliert.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Dez. 2024) für die Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Kundenhotline an oder suchen Sie das HONOR-Kunden-Service-Center auf, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση προεγκαθιστά το LinkedIn και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εφαρμογές">
<feature>• Προεγκαθιστά το LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Δεκέμβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε τυχόν προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update pre-installs LinkedIn and incorporates a security patch. Update to enjoy the improvements.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• Pre-installs LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>• Android Security Patch (Dec 2024) has been incorporated for the system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any issues during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización instala previamente LinkedIn e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicaciones">
<feature>• Instala LinkedIn previamente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>• Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (diciembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización preinstala LinkedIn e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicaciones">
<feature>• Preinstala LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (diciembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus eelinstallib LinkedIni ja lisab turvapaiga. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rakendused">
<feature>• Eelinstallib LinkedIni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>• Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (detsember 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, eguneratze honek LinkedIn instalatu du aurrez, eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu du. Eguneratu hobekuntzak ikusteko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikazioak">
<feature>• LinkedIn aurreinstalatzen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>• Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko abe.) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی برنامه LinkedIn را از پیش نصب می‌کند و همچنین یک بسته امنیتی اضافه کرده است. به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید و از بهبودها لذت ببرید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="برنامه‌ها">
<feature>‏• LinkedIn را از پیش تنظیم می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>‏• برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (دسامبر ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات:" type="end">
<feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys esiasentaa LinkedInin ja sisällyttää turvallisuuskorjauksen. Tee päivitys, jotta voit nauttia parannuksista.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sovellukset">
<feature>• Esiasentaa LinkedInin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (joulukuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour pré-installe LinkedIn et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Applications">
<feature>• Pré-installe LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (décembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour pré-installe LinkedIn et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Applications">
<feature>• Pré-installe LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (décembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización preinstala LinkedIn e incorpora un parche de seguranza. Actualice para gozar das melloras.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicacións">
<feature>• Preinstala LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>• Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (decembro de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ LinkedInને પહેલાંથી-ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરે છે અને તેમાં સુરક્ષા પેચ સામેલ છે. સુધારાઓનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="એપ્લિકેશન્સ">
<feature>LinkedInને પહેલાંથી-ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>• Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ડિસેમ્બર 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से LinkedIn को पूर्व-स्थापित किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता ​है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ऐप्स">
<feature>• LinkedIn पूर्व-स्थापित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (दिसंबर, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem unaprijed instalira LinkedIn, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Unaprijed se instalira LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (prosinac 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve poteškoće, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés előre telepíti a LinkedIn alkalmazást, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Frissítsen a fejlesztések eléréséhez.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Alkalmazások">
<feature>• A LinkedIn előtelepítése.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>• Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. december). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini melakukan prainstal LinkedIn dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Perbarui untuk menikmati peningkatannya.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi">
<feature>• Prainstal LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Des 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini melakukan prainstal LinkedIn dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Perbarui untuk menikmati peningkatannya.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi">
<feature>• Prainstal LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Des 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento installa LinkedIn e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Esegui l\'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App">
<feature>• Installa LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (dicembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento installa LinkedIn e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Esegui l\'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App">
<feature>• Installa LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (dicembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מתקין מראש את LinkedIn ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישומים">
<feature>‏• מתקין מראש את LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מדצמ' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה מתקין מראש את LinkedIn ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="יישומים">
<feature>‏• מתקין מראש את LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מדצמ' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の更新ではLinkedInがプリインされ、セキュリティパッチが導入されます。更新して改善された機能をご利用ください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="アプリ">
<feature>• LinkedInがプリインされます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>• システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年12月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელი, ეს განახლება წინსწრებით დააინსტალირებს LinkedIn-ს და უსაფრთხოების შესწორებას. განაახლეთ გაუმჯობესებებით სარგებლობისთვის.</feature>
</features>
<features module="აპები">
<feature>• წინსწრებით დააინსტალირებს LinkedIn-ს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>• Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (დეკემბერი, 2024) ჩაშენებულია სისტემის უსაფრთხოების უზრუნველსაყოფად. HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალაცია გავლენას არ მოახდენს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, მაგრამ მაინც რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე თქვენი მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა.
2. თუ განახლების დროს რაიმე პრობლემა შეგექმნათ, მხარდაჭერისთვის დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту LinkedIn қызметін алдын ала орнатады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қолданбалар">
<feature>• LinkedIn қызметін алдын ала орнатады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (желтоқсан, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះដំឡើង LinkedIn ជាមុន និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយជាមួយនឹងការកែលម្អ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កម្មវិធី">
<feature>• ដំឡើង LinkedIn ជាមុន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (ធ្នូ 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು LinkedIn ಅನ್ನು ಮೊದಲೇ ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳು">
<feature>• LinkedIn ಅನ್ನು ಮೊದಲೇ ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿರುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಡಿಸೆಂಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이 업데이트는 LinkedIn을 사전 설치하고 보안 패치를 통합합니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨보세요.</feature>
</features>
<features module="앱">
<feature>• LinkedIn을 사전 설치합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 12월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으세요.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ຮຽນຜູ້ໃຊ້, ການອັບເດດນີ້​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ LinkedIn ໄວ້​ກ່ອນ ແລະ ລວມເອົາໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂຄວາມປອດໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແອັບ">
<feature>• ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ LinkedIn ໄວ້​ກ່ອນ​.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ທັນ​ວາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiame naujinyje iš anksto įdiegtas „LinkedIn“ ir įtraukta saugumo pataisa. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programėlės">
<feature>• Iš anksto įdiegtas „LinkedIn“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>• Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. gruodžio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę duomenų kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu tiek iepriekš instalēts pakalpojums LinkedIn un ietverts drošības ielāps. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lietotnes">
<feature>• Iepriekš instalēts LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada decembris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मे पहिने सँ इंस्टॉल कयल LinkedIn अछि आ एकटा सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एप सभ">
<feature>• पहिने सँ इंस्टॉल कयल LinkedIn।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (दिसंबर 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणी:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ko tēnei whakahōu ngā tāuta-tōmuatia LinkedIn, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. Whakahōu kia ngahau ki ngā whakapainga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Taupānga">
<feature>• LinkedIn ngā tāuta-tōmuatia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>• Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Hakihea 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi atu mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi take i te wā o te whakahōutanga, waeawera atu koa ki te raina ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање претходно ја инсталира LinkedIn и воведува безбедносна крпеница. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Апликации">
<feature>• Претходно ја инсталира LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>• Безбедносната крпеница за Android (декември 2024 г.) е вградена за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за безбедносните ажурирања од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но, се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако се појават проблеми во текот на ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് LinkedIn പ്രി-ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ആപ്പുകൾ">
<feature>• LinkedIn പ്രി-ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഡിസംബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр LinkedIn-г урьдчилан суулгаж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаав. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээтэй танилцаарай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Апликэйшн">
<feature>• LinkedIn урьдчилан суулгав.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>• Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны арван хоёрдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन LinkedIn पूर्व-स्थापित करते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा.</feature>
</features>
<features module="अ‍ॅप्स">
<feature>• LinkedIn पूर्व-स्थापित करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (डिसेंबर 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini prapasang LinkedIn dan memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan ini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikasi">
<feature>• Prapasang LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>• Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Dis 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang isu semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် LinkedIn ကို ကြိုတင်ထည့်သွင်းပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ တိုးမြှင့်မှုများကို ရယူသုံးစွဲရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက်ပ်များ">
<feature>• LinkedIn ကို ကြိုတင်ထည့်သွင်းသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဒီဇင်ဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ LinkedIn ကို ႀကိဳတင္ထည့္သြင္းၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ တိုးျမႇင့္မႈမ်ားကို ရယူသုံးစြဲရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက္ပ္မ်ား">
<feature>• LinkedIn ကို ႀကိဳတင္ထည့္သြင္းသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဒီဇင္ဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံျခံဳေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne oppdateringen forhåndsinstallerer LinkedIn og integrerer et sikkerhetsprogram. Oppdater for å nyte forbedringene.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apper">
<feature>• Forhåndsinstallerer LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>• Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (des 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installering av denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले LinkedIn पूर्व-स्थापित गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एपहरू">
<feature>• LinkedIn पूर्व-स्थापित गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>• प्रणालीको सुरक्षाका लागि एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (डिसेम्बर 2024) समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेट गर्ने क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्या सामना गर्नुभयो भने कृपया HONOR सेवाको हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update installeert LinkedIn vooraf en bevat een beveiligingspatch. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apps">
<feature>• Installeert LinkedIn vooraf.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>• Android-beveiligingspatch (december 2024) is opgenomen voor de systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌‌ LinkedIn ପୂର୍ବ-ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରେ ଏବଂ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌‌ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ବିକାଶଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଆପସ୍‌">
<feature>• ପୂର୍ବ-ସଂସ୍ଥାପନା LinkedIn।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଡିସେମ୍ବର 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ LinkedIn ਨੂੰ ਪੂਰਵ-ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਐਪਾਂ">
<feature>• LinkedIn ਨੂੰ ਪੂਰਵ-ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਹੁੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਦਸੰਬਰ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja instaluje LinkedIn i zawiera poprawkę zabezpieczeń. Zainstaluj tę aktualizację, aby korzystać z ulepszeń.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacje">
<feature>• Instaluje LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>• Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (grudzień 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização pré-instala o LinkedIn e incorpora um patch de segurança. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicativos">
<feature>• Pré-instala o LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>• Patch de segurança do Android (dezembro de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização pré-instala o LinkedIn e incorpora uma correção de segurança. Atualize para usufruir das melhorias.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicações">
<feature>• Pré-instala o LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>• Foi incorporada uma Correção de Segurança Android (dezembro de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de Segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização de uma cópia de segurança antes da atualização.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare preinstalează aplicația LinkedIn și încorporează o corecție de securitate. Actualizați pentru a vă bucura de îmbunătățiri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplicații">
<feature>• Preinstalează LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>• Corecția de securitate Android (decembrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de Securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Это обновление предустанавливает LinkedIn и включает исправления безопасности. Рекомендуем установить его, чтобы воспользоваться этими улучшениями.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Приложения">
<feature>• Предустанавливает LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (декабрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලය LinkedIn පෙර ස්ථාපනය කර ආරක්ෂක පිළියමක් ඇතුළත් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාලීන කරන්න.</feature>
</features>
<features module="යෙදුම්">
<feature>• LinkedIn පෙර-ස්ථාපනය කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 දෙසැ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. ඔබට යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia predinštaluje LinkedIn a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikácie">
<feature>• Predinštaluje LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z decembra 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev omogoča prednamestitev aplikacije LinkedIn in vključuje varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikacije">
<feature>• Prednameščena aplikacija LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>• Varnostni popravki za Android (december 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förinstallerar LinkedIn och implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appar">
<feature>• Förinstallerar LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>• Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (december 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerheten. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen, kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs kundtjänstcenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mpendwsa mtumiaji, sasisho hili husakinisha mapema LinkedIn na hujumuisha kiraka cha usalama. Sasisha ili kufurahia maboresho.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programu">
<feature>• Husakinisha mapema LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>• Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Des 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு LinkedIn-ஐ முன்கூட்டியே நிறுவுகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="செயலிகள்">
<feature>• LinkedIn-ஐ முன்கூட்டியே நிறுவுகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (டிச 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ LinkedInని ముందే ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్‌ను చేర్చుతుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి.</feature>
</features>
<features module="అప్లికేషన్‌లు">
<feature>• LinkedInను ముందే ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>• సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రత ప్యాచ్ (డిసెంబర్ 2024) పొందుపరచబడింది. HONOR భద్రత నవీకరణల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้จะติดตั้ง LinkedIn ไว้ล่วงหน้าและรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
</features>
<features module="แอป">
<feature>• ติดตั้ง LinkedIn ไว้ล่วงหน้า</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ธ.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="หมายเหตุ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, pini-preinstall ng update na ito ang LinkedIn at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga App">
<feature>• Pini-preinstall ang LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Dis 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, pini-preinstall ng update na ito ang LinkedIn at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga App">
<feature>• Pini-preinstall ang LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Dis 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile LinkedIn önyüklemesi yapılmış ve güvenlik yaması eklenmiştir. İyileştirmelerden yararlanmak için güncelleme yapın.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uygulamalar">
<feature>• LinkedIn önyüklemesi yapar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>• Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yamasını (Aralık 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri hizmet merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا تەييار LinkedIn ئەپى قوشۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏ئەپ">
<feature>‏•تەييار LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏بىخەتەرلىك">
<feature>‏•  ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 12-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення попередньо встановлює LinkedIn і впроваджує виправлення для системи безпеки. Оновіть, щоб користуватися вдосконаленими функціями.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Додатки">
<feature>• Попередньо встановлює LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>• Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від грудня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак ми радимо створити резервну копію даних перед оновленням.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ LinkedIn کو پیشگی انسٹال کرتی ہے اور ایک سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ایپس">
<feature>‏• LinkedIn کو پیشگی انسٹال کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏• Android سکیورٹی پیچ (دسمبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish LinkedIn ilovasini avvaldan oʻrnatadi va xavfsizlik tuzatmasini oʻz ichiga oladi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ilovalar">
<feature>• LinkedIn ilovasini avvaldan oʻrnatadi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>• Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, dekabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash jarayonida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kính thưa người dùng, bản cập nhật này cài đặt sẵn LinkedIn và tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải thiện.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ứng dụng">
<feature>• Cài đặt sẵn LinkedIn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 12 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ vấn đề nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新預載 LinkedIn 應用程式，並整合了安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="應用程式">
<feature>• 預載 LinkedIn。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  整合 Android 2024年12月安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新預先安裝 LinkedIn 應用程式，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="應用程式">
<feature>• 預先安裝 LinkedIn。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  整合 Android 2024 年 12 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/12</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
